{
  "words": [
    {
      "front": "一つ",
      "back": "one (thing)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一",
      "back": "one"
    },
    {
      "front": "一般",
      "back": "general, common"
    },
    {
      "front": "これ",
      "back": "this, this one"
    },
    {
      "front": "二",
      "back": "two"
    },
    {
      "front": "二つ",
      "back": "two (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "それ",
      "back": "that, that one"
    },
    {
      "front": "三",
      "back": "three"
    },
    {
      "front": "三つ",
      "back": "three (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "四",
      "back": "four (Japanese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "四つ",
      "back": "four (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "四",
      "back": "four (Chinese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつ",
      "back": "when"
    },
    {
      "front": "五",
      "back": "five"
    },
    {
      "front": "五つ",
      "back": "five (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "六",
      "back": "six"
    },
    {
      "front": "六つ",
      "back": "six (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "する",
      "back": "do, make"
    },
    {
      "front": "七",
      "back": "seven (Japanese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "七つ",
      "back": "seven (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "七",
      "back": "seven (Chinese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "なる",
      "back": "become"
    },
    {
      "front": "八",
      "back": "eight"
    },
    {
      "front": "八つ",
      "back": "eight (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "九",
      "back": "nine"
    },
    {
      "front": "九つ",
      "back": "nine (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "九",
      "back": "nine"
    },
    {
      "front": "まだ",
      "back": "(not) yet, still"
    },
    {
      "front": "十",
      "back": "ten"
    },
    {
      "front": "二十歳",
      "back": "20 years old"
    },
    {
      "front": "百",
      "back": "hundred"
    },
    {
      "front": "千",
      "back": "thousand"
    },
    {
      "front": "あと",
      "back": "after"
    },
    {
      "front": "万",
      "back": "ten thousand"
    },
    {
      "front": "億",
      "back": "hundred million"
    },
    {
      "front": "円",
      "back": "Japanese yen"
    },
    {
      "front": "円",
      "back": "circle"
    },
    {
      "front": "そう",
      "back": "so, that way"
    },
    {
      "front": "時",
      "back": "time, moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "時々",
      "back": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "front": "寺",
      "back": "temple"
    },
    {
      "front": "一日",
      "back": "first of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "二十日",
      "back": "20 days, 20th of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "二日",
      "back": "two days, second of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "三日",
      "back": "three days, third of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "四日",
      "back": "four days, fourth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "五日",
      "back": "five days, fifth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "六日",
      "back": "six days, sixth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "七日",
      "back": "seven days, seventh of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "八日",
      "back": "eight days, eighth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "九日",
      "back": "nine days, ninth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "十日",
      "back": "ten days, tenth of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "日時",
      "back": "date and time"
    },
    {
      "front": "日",
      "back": "counter for days"
    },
    {
      "front": "日",
      "back": "(specific) day, sun, daytime"
    },
    {
      "front": "日陰",
      "back": "shade"
    },
    {
      "front": "もう",
      "back": "already, yet"
    },
    {
      "front": "どうぞ",
      "back": "please"
    },
    {
      "front": "よく",
      "back": "often, well"
    },
    {
      "front": "どう",
      "back": "how, what"
    },
    {
      "front": "金",
      "back": "money"
    },
    {
      "front": "金",
      "back": "gold"
    },
    {
      "front": "金額",
      "back": "amount of money, sum"
    },
    {
      "front": "貯金",
      "back": "savings, deposit"
    },
    {
      "front": "あげる",
      "back": "give"
    },
    {
      "front": "月",
      "back": "moon"
    },
    {
      "front": "火",
      "back": "fire"
    },
    {
      "front": "水",
      "back": "water"
    },
    {
      "front": "木",
      "back": "tree, wood"
    },
    {
      "front": "日曜日",
      "back": "Sunday"
    },
    {
      "front": "土曜日",
      "back": "Saturday"
    },
    {
      "front": "金曜日",
      "back": "Friday"
    },
    {
      "front": "月曜日",
      "back": "Monday"
    },
    {
      "front": "木曜日",
      "back": "Thursday"
    },
    {
      "front": "曜日",
      "back": "day of the week"
    },
    {
      "front": "火曜日",
      "back": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
      "front": "水曜日",
      "back": "Wednesday"
    },
    {
      "front": "こう",
      "back": "like this, such"
    },
    {
      "front": "どこ",
      "back": "where"
    },
    {
      "front": "週",
      "back": "week"
    },
    {
      "front": "週末",
      "back": "weekend"
    },
    {
      "front": "年月",
      "back": "years, period of time"
    },
    {
      "front": "年",
      "back": "year, age"
    },
    {
      "front": "もっと",
      "back": "more"
    },
    {
      "front": "十分",
      "back": "enough, plentiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "分かる",
      "back": "understand"
    },
    {
      "front": "分",
      "back": "amount, share"
    },
    {
      "front": "分ける",
      "back": "divide, share"
    },
    {
      "front": "分かれる",
      "back": "be divided, split off"
    },
    {
      "front": "随分",
      "back": "extremely, considerably"
    },
    {
      "front": "そこ",
      "back": "there"
    },
    {
      "front": "何",
      "back": "what"
    },
    {
      "front": "何",
      "back": "what (used with t, d, n consonants and counters)"
    },
    {
      "front": "何か",
      "back": "something, some"
    },
    {
      "front": "何とか",
      "back": "somehow, please"
    },
    {
      "front": "とても",
      "back": "very"
    },
    {
      "front": "先月",
      "back": "last month"
    },
    {
      "front": "先週",
      "back": "last week"
    },
    {
      "front": "先",
      "back": "ahead, first"
    },
    {
      "front": "先ず",
      "back": "first of all, to begin with"
    },
    {
      "front": "先輩",
      "back": "senior, superior"
    },
    {
      "front": "あなた",
      "back": "you"
    },
    {
      "front": "今日",
      "back": "today"
    },
    {
      "front": "今月",
      "back": "this month"
    },
    {
      "front": "今週",
      "back": "this week"
    },
    {
      "front": "今年",
      "back": "this year"
    },
    {
      "front": "今",
      "back": "now"
    },
    {
      "front": "今まで",
      "back": "until now"
    },
    {
      "front": "どれ",
      "back": "what, which"
    },
    {
      "front": "来月",
      "back": "next month"
    },
    {
      "front": "来週",
      "back": "next week"
    },
    {
      "front": "来年",
      "back": "next year"
    },
    {
      "front": "来る",
      "back": "come"
    },
    {
      "front": "未来",
      "back": "future"
    },
    {
      "front": "将来",
      "back": "future, in the future"
    },
    {
      "front": "みんな",
      "back": "everybody"
    },
    {
      "front": "行く",
      "back": "go"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き",
      "back": "going, bound for"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き",
      "back": "going, bound for (traditional reading)"
    },
    {
      "front": "できる",
      "back": "can do, be good at"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰る",
      "back": "go back home"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰り",
      "back": "return, going home"
    },
    {
      "front": "大分",
      "back": "very, greatly"
    },
    {
      "front": "大きい",
      "back": "big"
    },
    {
      "front": "大きさ",
      "back": "size, dimension"
    },
    {
      "front": "大型",
      "back": "large, large scale"
    },
    {
      "front": "拡大",
      "back": "magnification, enlargement"
    },
    {
      "front": "大統領",
      "back": "president (of a country)"
    },
    {
      "front": "大抵",
      "back": "generally, mostly"
    },
    {
      "front": "どちら",
      "back": "which"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドア",
      "back": "door"
    },
    {
      "front": "日中",
      "back": "during the day"
    },
    {
      "front": "年中",
      "back": "all year"
    },
    {
      "front": "中",
      "back": "inside, middle"
    },
    {
      "front": "途中",
      "back": "on the way, half way"
    },
    {
      "front": "やる",
      "back": "do, give"
    },
    {
      "front": "少年",
      "back": "boy (between 7 and 18 years old)"
    },
    {
      "front": "少ない",
      "back": "few, little"
    },
    {
      "front": "少し",
      "back": "a bit, a little while"
    },
    {
      "front": "少しも",
      "back": "(not) in the least"
    },
    {
      "front": "少々",
      "back": "a little, a bit"
    },
    {
      "front": "かなり",
      "back": "fairly, rather"
    },
    {
      "front": "いる",
      "back": "be present, stay"
    },
    {
      "front": "多分",
      "back": "probably, perhaps"
    },
    {
      "front": "多い",
      "back": "a lot of, many"
    },
    {
      "front": "多く",
      "back": "much, largely"
    },
    {
      "front": "年上",
      "back": "older, senior"
    },
    {
      "front": "上げる",
      "back": "raise, lift"
    },
    {
      "front": "上る",
      "back": "go up, climb"
    },
    {
      "front": "上",
      "back": "up, above"
    },
    {
      "front": "上り",
      "back": "going up, ascent"
    },
    {
      "front": "ここ",
      "back": "here"
    },
    {
      "front": "もらう",
      "back": "receive"
    },
    {
      "front": "年下",
      "back": "younger, junior"
    },
    {
      "front": "下",
      "back": "under, below"
    },
    {
      "front": "下りる",
      "back": "go down, come down"
    },
    {
      "front": "下げる",
      "back": "lower, turn down"
    },
    {
      "front": "下ろす",
      "back": "bring down, take down"
    },
    {
      "front": "下り",
      "back": "downhill, going down"
    },
    {
      "front": "下る",
      "back": "go down, go away from"
    },
    {
      "front": "廊下",
      "back": "hallway, corridor"
    },
    {
      "front": "テーブル",
      "back": "table"
    },
    {
      "front": "右",
      "back": "right"
    },
    {
      "front": "左右",
      "back": "right and left"
    },
    {
      "front": "左",
      "back": "left"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゲーム",
      "back": "game"
    },
    {
      "front": "一方",
      "back": "one way"
    },
    {
      "front": "方",
      "back": "direction, side"
    },
    {
      "front": "方",
      "back": "person (polite form)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一人",
      "back": "one person"
    },
    {
      "front": "一人で",
      "back": "by oneself, alone"
    },
    {
      "front": "二人",
      "back": "two persons"
    },
    {
      "front": "大人",
      "back": "adult"
    },
    {
      "front": "人",
      "back": "person"
    },
    {
      "front": "人々",
      "back": "people"
    },
    {
      "front": "個人",
      "back": "individual"
    },
    {
      "front": "どうして",
      "back": "why"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミーティング",
      "back": "meeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "入れる",
      "back": "put in"
    },
    {
      "front": "入る",
      "back": "enter"
    },
    {
      "front": "つける",
      "back": "switch on, turn on"
    },
    {
      "front": "出る",
      "back": "go out, leave"
    },
    {
      "front": "出す",
      "back": "take out"
    },
    {
      "front": "外人",
      "back": "foreigner, alien"
    },
    {
      "front": "外",
      "back": "outside, open air"
    },
    {
      "front": "カタカナ",
      "back": "katakana"
    },
    {
      "front": "本",
      "back": "book, volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "基本",
      "back": "basics"
    },
    {
      "front": "休日",
      "back": "holiday, day off"
    },
    {
      "front": "休む",
      "back": "take a rest, take a break"
    },
    {
      "front": "休み",
      "back": "rest, holiday"
    },
    {
      "front": "休憩",
      "back": "rest, break"
    },
    {
      "front": "あれ",
      "back": "that (over there)"
    },
    {
      "front": "力",
      "back": "strength, power"
    },
    {
      "front": "協力",
      "back": "cooperation, collaboration"
    },
    {
      "front": "努力",
      "back": "endeavor, effort"
    },
    {
      "front": "入り口",
      "back": "entrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "出口",
      "back": "exit"
    },
    {
      "front": "口",
      "back": "mouth"
    },
    {
      "front": "改札口",
      "back": "ticket gate"
    },
    {
      "front": "そば",
      "back": "side, vicinity"
    },
    {
      "front": "耳",
      "back": "ear"
    },
    {
      "front": "上手",
      "back": "good, skilled"
    },
    {
      "front": "下手",
      "back": "not good at"
    },
    {
      "front": "右手",
      "back": "right hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "左手",
      "back": "left hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "手",
      "back": "hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "拍手",
      "back": "applause, clapping"
    },
    {
      "front": "こっち",
      "back": "here"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちょっと",
      "back": "just a moment, just a little"
    },
    {
      "front": "足",
      "back": "leg, foot"
    },
    {
      "front": "足りる",
      "back": "suffice, be enough"
    },
    {
      "front": "足す",
      "back": "add (things of the same kind)"
    },
    {
      "front": "山",
      "back": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "front": "これから",
      "back": "from now on, after this"
    },
    {
      "front": "川",
      "back": "river, stream"
    },
    {
      "front": "空く",
      "back": "be empty, become less crowded"
    },
    {
      "front": "空",
      "back": "sky"
    },
    {
      "front": "空く",
      "back": "become available or vacant"
    },
    {
      "front": "海外",
      "back": "overseas, abroad"
    },
    {
      "front": "海",
      "back": "sea, ocean"
    },
    {
      "front": "海岸",
      "back": "seashore, coast"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎日",
      "back": "every day"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎月",
      "back": "every month"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎週",
      "back": "every week"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎年",
      "back": "every year (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎年",
      "back": "every year (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "いっぱい",
      "back": "full"
    },
    {
      "front": "石",
      "back": "stone, small rock"
    },
    {
      "front": "石鹸",
      "back": "soap"
    },
    {
      "front": "林",
      "back": "woods, forest"
    },
    {
      "front": "森",
      "back": "forest"
    },
    {
      "front": "少女",
      "back": "girl"
    },
    {
      "front": "女",
      "back": "woman, female"
    },
    {
      "front": "女性",
      "back": "woman, female"
    },
    {
      "front": "ため",
      "back": "sake, purpose"
    },
    {
      "front": "男",
      "back": "man, male"
    },
    {
      "front": "男の子",
      "back": "boy"
    },
    {
      "front": "女の子",
      "back": "girl"
    },
    {
      "front": "子",
      "back": "child, kid"
    },
    {
      "front": "息子",
      "back": "son"
    },
    {
      "front": "お菓子",
      "back": "sweets, snacks"
    },
    {
      "front": "帽子",
      "back": "hat, cap"
    },
    {
      "front": "椅子",
      "back": "chair"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゆっくり",
      "back": "slowly"
    },
    {
      "front": "もつ",
      "back": "last long, be durable"
    },
    {
      "front": "大好き",
      "back": "love"
    },
    {
      "front": "好き",
      "back": "favorite, liked"
    },
    {
      "front": "私",
      "back": "I (general)"
    },
    {
      "front": "私たち",
      "back": "we"
    },
    {
      "front": "私",
      "back": "I (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドル",
      "back": "dollar"
    },
    {
      "front": "友達",
      "back": "friend, companion"
    },
    {
      "front": "達する",
      "back": "attain, reach"
    },
    {
      "front": "家内",
      "back": "one's wife"
    },
    {
      "front": "家",
      "back": "home, household"
    },
    {
      "front": "家",
      "back": "house, dwelling"
    },
    {
      "front": "家族",
      "back": "family, household"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンピューター",
      "back": "computer"
    },
    {
      "front": "客",
      "back": "visitor, customer"
    },
    {
      "front": "天ぷら",
      "back": "Japanese deep-fried food"
    },
    {
      "front": "人気",
      "back": "popularity"
    },
    {
      "front": "気に入る",
      "back": "like, be pleased with"
    },
    {
      "front": "空気",
      "back": "air, atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "front": "元気",
      "back": "healthy, energetic"
    },
    {
      "front": "天気",
      "back": "weather"
    },
    {
      "front": "気",
      "back": "spirit, temperament"
    },
    {
      "front": "元旦",
      "back": "New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "front": "雪",
      "back": "snow, snowfall"
    },
    {
      "front": "青い",
      "back": "blue"
    },
    {
      "front": "青",
      "back": "blue, green"
    },
    {
      "front": "もう",
      "back": "another, again"
    },
    {
      "front": "晴れる",
      "back": "be sunny, clear up"
    },
    {
      "front": "晴れ",
      "back": "fine weather, clear sky"
    },
    {
      "front": "素晴らしい",
      "back": "excellent, wonderful"
    },
    {
      "front": "明日",
      "back": "tomorrow (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "明らか",
      "back": "clear, obvious"
    },
    {
      "front": "プログラム",
      "back": "program booklet"
    },
    {
      "front": "一昨日",
      "back": "the day before yesterday (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一昨年",
      "back": "the year before last (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨日",
      "back": "yesterday (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨年",
      "back": "last year (formal, often used in writing)"
    },
    {
      "front": "まま",
      "back": "as is, still (in the current state)"
    },
    {
      "front": "東",
      "back": "east, eastern"
    },
    {
      "front": "西",
      "back": "west, western"
    },
    {
      "front": "南",
      "back": "south"
    },
    {
      "front": "テレビ",
      "back": "television"
    },
    {
      "front": "北",
      "back": "north"
    },
    {
      "front": "方向",
      "back": "direction, course"
    },
    {
      "front": "向かう",
      "back": "face, head toward"
    },
    {
      "front": "向こう",
      "back": "over there, on the other side"
    },
    {
      "front": "向く",
      "back": "turn, face"
    },
    {
      "front": "ただ",
      "back": "free"
    },
    {
      "front": "開ける",
      "back": "open, unlock (doors, windows, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "開く",
      "back": "open (books, eyes, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "開く",
      "back": "open"
    },
    {
      "front": "これら",
      "back": "these"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉める",
      "back": "shut, close (doors, windows, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉じる",
      "back": "shut, close (books, eyes, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉まる",
      "back": "be shut, be closed"
    },
    {
      "front": "聞く",
      "back": "hear, ask"
    },
    {
      "front": "聞こえる",
      "back": "hear, be heard"
    },
    {
      "front": "あまり",
      "back": "(not) much"
    },
    {
      "front": "時間",
      "back": "time, hour"
    },
    {
      "front": "年間",
      "back": "period of one year"
    },
    {
      "front": "人間",
      "back": "human being"
    },
    {
      "front": "間",
      "back": "interval, space between things"
    },
    {
      "front": "居間",
      "back": "living room"
    },
    {
      "front": "クラス",
      "back": "class (in school)"
    },
    {
      "front": "高い",
      "back": "high, tall"
    },
    {
      "front": "高さ",
      "back": "height"
    },
    {
      "front": "バス",
      "back": "bus"
    },
    {
      "front": "安い",
      "back": "cheap, inexpensive"
    },
    {
      "front": "低い",
      "back": "low, short"
    },
    {
      "front": "最大",
      "back": "biggest, largest"
    },
    {
      "front": "最初",
      "back": "first, outset"
    },
    {
      "front": "初めて",
      "back": "for the first time"
    },
    {
      "front": "初め",
      "back": "first, beginning (in terms of time passage)"
    },
    {
      "front": "こちら",
      "back": "here, this way"
    },
    {
      "front": "今後",
      "back": "in the future, from now on"
    },
    {
      "front": "最後",
      "back": "last, final"
    },
    {
      "front": "後ろ",
      "back": "back, behind"
    },
    {
      "front": "後",
      "back": "after, afterward"
    },
    {
      "front": "パスポート",
      "back": "passport"
    },
    {
      "front": "いくつ",
      "back": "how many, how old"
    },
    {
      "front": "前",
      "back": "front, before"
    },
    {
      "front": "午前",
      "back": "morning, a.m."
    },
    {
      "front": "午後",
      "back": "afternoon, p.m."
    },
    {
      "front": "牛",
      "back": "cattle, cow"
    },
    {
      "front": "牛乳",
      "back": "milk"
    },
    {
      "front": "メニュー",
      "back": "menu"
    },
    {
      "front": "半日",
      "back": "half a day"
    },
    {
      "front": "半月",
      "back": "half a month"
    },
    {
      "front": "半年",
      "back": "half a year"
    },
    {
      "front": "半分",
      "back": "half"
    },
    {
      "front": "レシート",
      "back": "receipt"
    },
    {
      "front": "今朝",
      "back": "this morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎朝",
      "back": "every morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝",
      "back": "morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼休み",
      "back": "lunch break"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼間",
      "back": "daytime, during the day"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼前",
      "back": "in the morning, before noon"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼",
      "back": "daytime, midday"
    },
    {
      "front": "ティッシュ",
      "back": "tissue"
    },
    {
      "front": "今晩",
      "back": "this evening, tonight"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎晩",
      "back": "every evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "晩",
      "back": "evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "パート",
      "back": "part-time"
    },
    {
      "front": "今夜",
      "back": "tonight, this evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜中",
      "back": "midnight"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨夜",
      "back": "last night, last evening (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜",
      "back": "night (from sunset to sunrise)"
    },
    {
      "front": "おじさん",
      "back": "uncle"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕方",
      "back": "evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝食",
      "back": "breakfast (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼食",
      "back": "lunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕食",
      "back": "supper, dinner"
    },
    {
      "front": "食べる",
      "back": "eat"
    },
    {
      "front": "食器",
      "back": "tableware"
    },
    {
      "front": "食堂",
      "back": "cafeteria, restaurant"
    },
    {
      "front": "おばさん",
      "back": "aunt"
    },
    {
      "front": "いとこ",
      "back": "cousin"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝ご飯",
      "back": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕飯",
      "back": "evening meal, dinner"
    },
    {
      "front": "ご飯",
      "back": "meal, cooked rice"
    },
    {
      "front": "花",
      "back": "flower"
    },
    {
      "front": "花見",
      "back": "flower viewing"
    },
    {
      "front": "見る",
      "back": "see, look at"
    },
    {
      "front": "見せる",
      "back": "show"
    },
    {
      "front": "見つける",
      "back": "find"
    },
    {
      "front": "見える",
      "back": "be visible, can see"
    },
    {
      "front": "見つかる",
      "back": "be found, be caught"
    },
    {
      "front": "どっち",
      "back": "which"
    },
    {
      "front": "そっち",
      "back": "there"
    },
    {
      "front": "一言",
      "back": "single word, brief speech"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い方",
      "back": "way of speaking, expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "言う",
      "back": "say, tell"
    },
    {
      "front": "あっち",
      "back": "other side, over there"
    },
    {
      "front": "話す",
      "back": "speak, talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "話",
      "back": "talk, story"
    },
    {
      "front": "読み方",
      "back": "how to read, way of reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "読む",
      "back": "read"
    },
    {
      "front": "読み",
      "back": "reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちょうど",
      "back": "just, exactly"
    },
    {
      "front": "文句",
      "back": "complaint, grumble"
    },
    {
      "front": "文章",
      "back": "sentence, writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "ようこそ",
      "back": "welcome"
    },
    {
      "front": "文字",
      "back": "character, letter, writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "字",
      "back": "(individual) character, letter"
    },
    {
      "front": "漢字",
      "back": "Chinese character"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウェーター",
      "back": "waiter"
    },
    {
      "front": "書き方",
      "back": "how to write, way of writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "読書",
      "back": "reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "書く",
      "back": "write"
    },
    {
      "front": "覚える",
      "back": "memorize, learn"
    },
    {
      "front": "覚める",
      "back": "awake, wake up (naturally)"
    },
    {
      "front": "覚ます",
      "back": "awaken, wake up"
    },
    {
      "front": "大会",
      "back": "tournament, event"
    },
    {
      "front": "出会う",
      "back": "meet, encounter"
    },
    {
      "front": "会話",
      "back": "conversation"
    },
    {
      "front": "会う",
      "back": "meet"
    },
    {
      "front": "間に合う",
      "back": "be in time, suffice"
    },
    {
      "front": "話し合う",
      "back": "discuss, talk over"
    },
    {
      "front": "合う",
      "back": "fit, match"
    },
    {
      "front": "フォーク",
      "back": "fork"
    },
    {
      "front": "会社",
      "back": "company, corporation"
    },
    {
      "front": "社会",
      "back": "society"
    },
    {
      "front": "神社",
      "back": "Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "front": "仕方",
      "back": "way, method"
    },
    {
      "front": "スプーン",
      "back": "spoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "火事",
      "back": "fire"
    },
    {
      "front": "大事",
      "back": "importance"
    },
    {
      "front": "食事",
      "back": "meal"
    },
    {
      "front": "仕事",
      "back": "work, job"
    },
    {
      "front": "つく",
      "back": "be on, be switched on"
    },
    {
      "front": "事故",
      "back": "accident, trouble"
    },
    {
      "front": "故障",
      "back": "malfunction, breakdown"
    },
    {
      "front": "電気",
      "back": "electricity, electric light"
    },
    {
      "front": "電話",
      "back": "telephone, phone call"
    },
    {
      "front": "携帯電話",
      "back": "cellular phone"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぬるい",
      "back": "tepid, lukewarm"
    },
    {
      "front": "場合",
      "back": "situation, case"
    },
    {
      "front": "電車",
      "back": "train"
    },
    {
      "front": "車",
      "back": "car, automobile"
    },
    {
      "front": "駐車場",
      "back": "parking area, parking lot"
    },
    {
      "front": "たばこ",
      "back": "tobacco, cigarette"
    },
    {
      "front": "社員",
      "back": "staff member, employee"
    },
    {
      "front": "駅員",
      "back": "station attendant"
    },
    {
      "front": "駅",
      "back": "train station"
    },
    {
      "front": "アイスコーヒー",
      "back": "iced coffee"
    },
    {
      "front": "交通事故",
      "back": "traffic accident"
    },
    {
      "front": "通う",
      "back": "go to and from, frequent a place"
    },
    {
      "front": "通る",
      "back": "pass, go through"
    },
    {
      "front": "通り",
      "back": "street, road"
    },
    {
      "front": "交通費",
      "back": "traveling expense, transportation fee"
    },
    {
      "front": "交差点",
      "back": "crossing, intersection"
    },
    {
      "front": "なるほど",
      "back": "I see, really"
    },
    {
      "front": "水道",
      "back": "tap water"
    },
    {
      "front": "車道",
      "back": "road, roadway"
    },
    {
      "front": "道",
      "back": "road, street"
    },
    {
      "front": "土地",
      "back": "land"
    },
    {
      "front": "地下",
      "back": "underground"
    },
    {
      "front": "地下鉄",
      "back": "subway"
    },
    {
      "front": "地域",
      "back": "region, area"
    },
    {
      "front": "そのまま",
      "back": "as it is, just like that"
    },
    {
      "front": "他",
      "back": "other (Japanese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "他",
      "back": "other (Chinese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "中止",
      "back": "suspension, cancellation"
    },
    {
      "front": "止める",
      "back": "stop, give up"
    },
    {
      "front": "止まる",
      "back": "come to a stop, cease"
    },
    {
      "front": "止む",
      "back": "stop, cease"
    },
    {
      "front": "止める",
      "back": "stop (something/someone)"
    },
    {
      "front": "はっきり",
      "back": "clearly"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩道",
      "back": "sidewalk, pavement"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩く",
      "back": "walk, go on foot"
    },
    {
      "front": "散歩",
      "back": "walk, stroll"
    },
    {
      "front": "にんじん",
      "back": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "front": "走る",
      "back": "run"
    },
    {
      "front": "渡す",
      "back": "hand over, give"
    },
    {
      "front": "渡る",
      "back": "cross, go across"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジャガイモ",
      "back": "potato"
    },
    {
      "front": "年度",
      "back": "year, school year"
    },
    {
      "front": "何度",
      "back": "how many times, how many degrees"
    },
    {
      "front": "今度",
      "back": "this time, next time"
    },
    {
      "front": "ナス",
      "back": "eggplant"
    },
    {
      "front": "最近",
      "back": "recent, latest"
    },
    {
      "front": "近い",
      "back": "near, close"
    },
    {
      "front": "近く",
      "back": "near, close to"
    },
    {
      "front": "近く",
      "back": "soon, before long"
    },
    {
      "front": "やかん",
      "back": "kettle"
    },
    {
      "front": "遠い",
      "back": "far, distant"
    },
    {
      "front": "遠く",
      "back": "far away, at a distance"
    },
    {
      "front": "遠慮",
      "back": "restraint, hold back"
    },
    {
      "front": "長男",
      "back": "eldest son"
    },
    {
      "front": "長女",
      "back": "eldest daughter"
    },
    {
      "front": "会長",
      "back": "president, chairperson"
    },
    {
      "front": "社長",
      "back": "president (of a company)"
    },
    {
      "front": "長い",
      "back": "long"
    },
    {
      "front": "長さ",
      "back": "length"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごちそうする",
      "back": "treat"
    },
    {
      "front": "短い",
      "back": "short, brief"
    },
    {
      "front": "広い",
      "back": "wide, big"
    },
    {
      "front": "広さ",
      "back": "area, extent"
    },
    {
      "front": "広がる",
      "back": "spread out, extend"
    },
    {
      "front": "体",
      "back": "body, physique"
    },
    {
      "front": "全体",
      "back": "whole, total"
    },
    {
      "front": "安全",
      "back": "safety, security"
    },
    {
      "front": "全く",
      "back": "entirely, truly"
    },
    {
      "front": "くし",
      "back": "comb"
    },
    {
      "front": "部分",
      "back": "part, section"
    },
    {
      "front": "全部",
      "back": "all, whole"
    },
    {
      "front": "英語",
      "back": "English"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰国",
      "back": "return to one's country"
    },
    {
      "front": "外国人",
      "back": "foreigner"
    },
    {
      "front": "外国",
      "back": "foreign country"
    },
    {
      "front": "外国語",
      "back": "foreign language"
    },
    {
      "front": "国内",
      "back": "domestic, internal"
    },
    {
      "front": "国",
      "back": "country"
    },
    {
      "front": "国籍",
      "back": "nationality, citizenship"
    },
    {
      "front": "スポーツ",
      "back": "sport"
    },
    {
      "front": "チャンス",
      "back": "chance"
    },
    {
      "front": "世界",
      "back": "world"
    },
    {
      "front": "世紀",
      "back": "century"
    },
    {
      "front": "白い",
      "back": "white, blank"
    },
    {
      "front": "白",
      "back": "white"
    },
    {
      "front": "クリーニング",
      "back": "dry cleaning"
    },
    {
      "front": "黒い",
      "back": "black, dark"
    },
    {
      "front": "黒",
      "back": "black"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤い",
      "back": "red"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤",
      "back": "red"
    },
    {
      "front": "サービス",
      "back": "service, on the house"
    },
    {
      "front": "銀行",
      "back": "bank"
    },
    {
      "front": "銀",
      "back": "silver"
    },
    {
      "front": "牛肉",
      "back": "beef"
    },
    {
      "front": "肉",
      "back": "flesh, meat"
    },
    {
      "front": "グループ",
      "back": "group"
    },
    {
      "front": "魚",
      "back": "fish"
    },
    {
      "front": "分野",
      "back": "field, area"
    },
    {
      "front": "野菜",
      "back": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "front": "本屋",
      "back": "bookstore (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "部屋",
      "back": "room"
    },
    {
      "front": "そば屋",
      "back": "buckwheat noodle shop"
    },
    {
      "front": "屋根",
      "back": "roof"
    },
    {
      "front": "あちこち",
      "back": "all over, here and there"
    },
    {
      "front": "米",
      "back": "rice (grain)"
    },
    {
      "front": "欧米",
      "back": "Europe and America"
    },
    {
      "front": "そちら",
      "back": "there, that way"
    },
    {
      "front": "お茶",
      "back": "tea (polite)"
    },
    {
      "front": "茶",
      "back": "tea"
    },
    {
      "front": "紅茶",
      "back": "black tea"
    },
    {
      "front": "茶碗",
      "back": "rice bowl"
    },
    {
      "front": "あちら",
      "back": "over there, that way"
    },
    {
      "front": "味",
      "back": "taste, flavor"
    },
    {
      "front": "趣味",
      "back": "hobby, interest"
    },
    {
      "front": "味噌汁",
      "back": "miso soup"
    },
    {
      "front": "材料",
      "back": "material, ingredient"
    },
    {
      "front": "給料",
      "back": "salary, pay"
    },
    {
      "front": "料理",
      "back": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "front": "修理",
      "back": "repair, mending"
    },
    {
      "front": "うるさい",
      "back": "noisy, annoying"
    },
    {
      "front": "無理",
      "back": "unreasonable, impossible"
    },
    {
      "front": "無い",
      "back": "to not be"
    },
    {
      "front": "無くす",
      "back": "lose, get rid of"
    },
    {
      "front": "無くなる",
      "back": "get lost, go missing"
    },
    {
      "front": "作文",
      "back": "composition, essay"
    },
    {
      "front": "作る",
      "back": "make, create"
    },
    {
      "front": "もちろん",
      "back": "of course, no doubt"
    },
    {
      "front": "用事",
      "back": "errand, business"
    },
    {
      "front": "用",
      "back": "things to do"
    },
    {
      "front": "消す",
      "back": "switch off, turn off"
    },
    {
      "front": "消える",
      "back": "be extinguished, disappear"
    },
    {
      "front": "消しゴム",
      "back": "eraser"
    },
    {
      "front": "消防署",
      "back": "fire station"
    },
    {
      "front": "やはり",
      "back": "as expected"
    },
    {
      "front": "売る",
      "back": "sell"
    },
    {
      "front": "売れる",
      "back": "sell, be in demand"
    },
    {
      "front": "販売",
      "back": "sale, selling"
    },
    {
      "front": "よろしく",
      "back": "one's regards"
    },
    {
      "front": "店員",
      "back": "clerk, salesperson"
    },
    {
      "front": "売店",
      "back": "booth, shop"
    },
    {
      "front": "店",
      "back": "shop, store"
    },
    {
      "front": "喫茶店",
      "back": "coffee shop, café"
    },
    {
      "front": "作品",
      "back": "work of art, creation"
    },
    {
      "front": "商品",
      "back": "goods, commodities"
    },
    {
      "front": "アパート",
      "back": "apartment, flat"
    },
    {
      "front": "二階",
      "back": "second floor, upstairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "階段",
      "back": "steps, flight of stairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "値段",
      "back": "price"
    },
    {
      "front": "合格",
      "back": "pass an examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "価格",
      "back": "price, value"
    },
    {
      "front": "ホテル",
      "back": "hotel"
    },
    {
      "front": "春",
      "back": "spring"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏休み",
      "back": "summer vacation"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏",
      "back": "summer"
    },
    {
      "front": "秋",
      "back": "autumn, fall"
    },
    {
      "front": "パソコン",
      "back": "personal computer"
    },
    {
      "front": "冬休み",
      "back": "winter vacation"
    },
    {
      "front": "冬",
      "back": "winter"
    },
    {
      "front": "暑い",
      "back": "hot (of weather)"
    },
    {
      "front": "暑さ",
      "back": "heat (of weather)"
    },
    {
      "front": "うまい",
      "back": "good at"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱い",
      "back": "hot (to touch)"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱",
      "back": "heat, fever"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒気",
      "back": "chill"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒い",
      "back": "cold (temperature of the air)"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒さ",
      "back": "coldness, cold"
    },
    {
      "front": "テスト",
      "back": "test"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖かい",
      "back": "warm"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖める",
      "back": "warm (something) up"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖まる",
      "back": "get warm"
    },
    {
      "front": "気温",
      "back": "air temperature"
    },
    {
      "front": "温度",
      "back": "temperature"
    },
    {
      "front": "温泉",
      "back": "hot spring"
    },
    {
      "front": "ポスト",
      "back": "postbox, mailbox"
    },
    {
      "front": "台",
      "back": "stand, table"
    },
    {
      "front": "台風",
      "back": "typhoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "風",
      "back": "wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハンカチ",
      "back": "handkerchief"
    },
    {
      "front": "情報",
      "back": "information"
    },
    {
      "front": "報告",
      "back": "report"
    },
    {
      "front": "新年",
      "back": "New Year"
    },
    {
      "front": "新聞",
      "back": "newspaper"
    },
    {
      "front": "新しい",
      "back": "new"
    },
    {
      "front": "ブラウス",
      "back": "blouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "古い",
      "back": "old"
    },
    {
      "front": "昔",
      "back": "old times, the old days"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつか",
      "back": "some time, some day"
    },
    {
      "front": "良い",
      "back": "good (formal/written form)"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲良し",
      "back": "good friend"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪口",
      "back": "slander, abuse"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪い",
      "back": "bad"
    },
    {
      "front": "中心",
      "back": "center (of a circle, etc.), core"
    },
    {
      "front": "安心",
      "back": "peace of mind, relief"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い出す",
      "back": "recollect, recall"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い出",
      "back": "memory"
    },
    {
      "front": "思う",
      "back": "think"
    },
    {
      "front": "思わず",
      "back": "unintentionally, unconsciously"
    },
    {
      "front": "まあまあ",
      "back": "OK, not bad"
    },
    {
      "front": "考える",
      "back": "think, consider"
    },
    {
      "front": "考え",
      "back": "thought, idea"
    },
    {
      "front": "決める",
      "back": "decide, agree upon"
    },
    {
      "front": "決して",
      "back": "never, by no means"
    },
    {
      "front": "ランチ",
      "back": "lunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "知る",
      "back": "know"
    },
    {
      "front": "知らせる",
      "back": "let know, inform"
    },
    {
      "front": "りんご",
      "back": "apple"
    },
    {
      "front": "能力",
      "back": "capability, performance ability of machine, etc."
    },
    {
      "front": "可能",
      "back": "possible, potential"
    },
    {
      "front": "郵便屋さん",
      "back": "mail carrier"
    },
    {
      "front": "不便",
      "back": "inconvenient"
    },
    {
      "front": "郵便",
      "back": "mail service, postal mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "航空便",
      "back": "airmail, airfreight"
    },
    {
      "front": "みかん",
      "back": "tangerine"
    },
    {
      "front": "一番",
      "back": "most, best"
    },
    {
      "front": "交番",
      "back": "police box"
    },
    {
      "front": "番",
      "back": "one's turn, watch"
    },
    {
      "front": "順番",
      "back": "order, turn"
    },
    {
      "front": "コーヒー",
      "back": "coffee"
    },
    {
      "front": "有る",
      "back": "exist, there is"
    },
    {
      "front": "住む",
      "back": "live, reside"
    },
    {
      "front": "場所",
      "back": "place, space"
    },
    {
      "front": "近所",
      "back": "neighborhood"
    },
    {
      "front": "所有",
      "back": "ownership, own"
    },
    {
      "front": "台所",
      "back": "kitchen"
    },
    {
      "front": "住所",
      "back": "address"
    },
    {
      "front": "所",
      "back": "place"
    },
    {
      "front": "コップ",
      "back": "cup, glass"
    },
    {
      "front": "おじ",
      "back": "(one's own) uncle"
    },
    {
      "front": "名前",
      "back": "name"
    },
    {
      "front": "名字",
      "back": "surname, family name"
    },
    {
      "front": "有名",
      "back": "famous"
    },
    {
      "front": "氏名",
      "back": "name (of a person)"
    },
    {
      "front": "おば",
      "back": "(one's own) aunt"
    },
    {
      "front": "町",
      "back": "town, city"
    },
    {
      "front": "都合",
      "back": "convenience, availability"
    },
    {
      "front": "都市",
      "back": "city, town"
    },
    {
      "front": "市民",
      "back": "citizens"
    },
    {
      "front": "また",
      "back": "again, also, or"
    },
    {
      "front": "飲む",
      "back": "drink"
    },
    {
      "front": "買う",
      "back": "buy"
    },
    {
      "front": "忘れる",
      "back": "forget, leave behind"
    },
    {
      "front": "本物",
      "back": "real, truly worthy (things, people)"
    },
    {
      "front": "食べ物",
      "back": "food"
    },
    {
      "front": "飲み物",
      "back": "beverage, drink"
    },
    {
      "front": "買い物",
      "back": "shopping, purchase"
    },
    {
      "front": "見物",
      "back": "sightseeing, visit"
    },
    {
      "front": "物語",
      "back": "story, tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "品物",
      "back": "article, goods"
    },
    {
      "front": "忘れ物",
      "back": "something left behind, lost item"
    },
    {
      "front": "荷物",
      "back": "baggage, load"
    },
    {
      "front": "物",
      "back": "thing, object"
    },
    {
      "front": "うまい",
      "back": "delicious, tasty"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガス",
      "back": "gas"
    },
    {
      "front": "カメラ",
      "back": "camera"
    },
    {
      "front": "重大",
      "back": "important, serious"
    },
    {
      "front": "重い",
      "back": "heavy"
    },
    {
      "front": "重さ",
      "back": "weight"
    },
    {
      "front": "サラリーマン",
      "back": "office worker, company employee"
    },
    {
      "front": "軽い",
      "back": "light (of weight)"
    },
    {
      "front": "配達",
      "back": "delivery"
    },
    {
      "front": "心配",
      "back": "anxiety, worry"
    },
    {
      "front": "配る",
      "back": "hand out, distribute"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゴルフ",
      "back": "golf"
    },
    {
      "front": "見送る",
      "back": "see (someone) off"
    },
    {
      "front": "見送り",
      "back": "see (someone) off"
    },
    {
      "front": "送る",
      "back": "send"
    },
    {
      "front": "放送",
      "back": "broadcasting"
    },
    {
      "front": "コース",
      "back": "course, route"
    },
    {
      "front": "受ける",
      "back": "receive, accept"
    },
    {
      "front": "受け取る",
      "back": "receive, get"
    },
    {
      "front": "取る",
      "back": "take, get"
    },
    {
      "front": "取れる",
      "back": "come off, be removed"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずっと",
      "back": "all the time, all through"
    },
    {
      "front": "届く",
      "back": "reach, be received"
    },
    {
      "front": "届ける",
      "back": "deliver"
    },
    {
      "front": "金持ち",
      "back": "wealthy person"
    },
    {
      "front": "持って行く",
      "back": "take"
    },
    {
      "front": "気持ち",
      "back": "feeling, sensation"
    },
    {
      "front": "持つ",
      "back": "have, possess"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ってくる",
      "back": "bring"
    },
    {
      "front": "打つ",
      "back": "hit, strike"
    },
    {
      "front": "投げる",
      "back": "throw"
    },
    {
      "front": "先生",
      "back": "teacher"
    },
    {
      "front": "生まれる",
      "back": "be born, come into existence"
    },
    {
      "front": "生きる",
      "back": "live (one's life)"
    },
    {
      "front": "生む",
      "back": "give birth, produce"
    },
    {
      "front": "生徒",
      "back": "pupil, student"
    },
    {
      "front": "誕生日",
      "back": "birthday"
    },
    {
      "front": "タクシー",
      "back": "taxi"
    },
    {
      "front": "お土産",
      "back": "souvenir"
    },
    {
      "front": "土産",
      "back": "souvenir"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガラス",
      "back": "glass (material)"
    },
    {
      "front": "小さい",
      "back": "small"
    },
    {
      "front": "大学",
      "back": "university, college"
    },
    {
      "front": "大学生",
      "back": "university student"
    },
    {
      "front": "中学",
      "back": "junior high school"
    },
    {
      "front": "中学生",
      "back": "junior high school student"
    },
    {
      "front": "小学生",
      "back": "elementary school student"
    },
    {
      "front": "入学",
      "back": "enter a school, matriculate"
    },
    {
      "front": "通学",
      "back": "going to school"
    },
    {
      "front": "学生",
      "back": "student"
    },
    {
      "front": "つまらない",
      "back": "boring, dull"
    },
    {
      "front": "やっと",
      "back": "at last, finally (used only for a good outcome)"
    },
    {
      "front": "中学校",
      "back": "junior high school"
    },
    {
      "front": "小学校",
      "back": "elementary school"
    },
    {
      "front": "高校生",
      "back": "high school student"
    },
    {
      "front": "高校",
      "back": "high school"
    },
    {
      "front": "学校",
      "back": "school"
    },
    {
      "front": "どんどん",
      "back": "knock, bang"
    },
    {
      "front": "教会",
      "back": "church"
    },
    {
      "front": "教える",
      "back": "teach, tell"
    },
    {
      "front": "教師",
      "back": "teacher, instructor"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラジオ",
      "back": "radio"
    },
    {
      "front": "教育",
      "back": "education"
    },
    {
      "front": "育てる",
      "back": "bring up, raise"
    },
    {
      "front": "育つ",
      "back": "be brought up, grow"
    },
    {
      "front": "ニュース",
      "back": "news"
    },
    {
      "front": "勉強",
      "back": "study"
    },
    {
      "front": "強い",
      "back": "strong"
    },
    {
      "front": "強さ",
      "back": "strength"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱い",
      "back": "weak"
    },
    {
      "front": "パーティー",
      "back": "party"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き出し",
      "back": "drawer"
    },
    {
      "front": "引く",
      "back": "draw, pull"
    },
    {
      "front": "押し入れ",
      "back": "sliding-door closet"
    },
    {
      "front": "押す",
      "back": "push, press down"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビール",
      "back": "beer"
    },
    {
      "front": "練習",
      "back": "practice, training"
    },
    {
      "front": "習う",
      "back": "learn, take lessons"
    },
    {
      "front": "習慣",
      "back": "custom, habit"
    },
    {
      "front": "慣れる",
      "back": "grow accustomed to, get used to"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビデオ",
      "back": "video"
    },
    {
      "front": "研究",
      "back": "research, study"
    },
    {
      "front": "質問",
      "back": "question"
    },
    {
      "front": "問題",
      "back": "problem, question"
    },
    {
      "front": "宿題",
      "back": "homework"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビル",
      "back": "building"
    },
    {
      "front": "簡単",
      "back": "simple, easy"
    },
    {
      "front": "難しい",
      "back": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "front": "数字",
      "back": "number"
    },
    {
      "front": "数学",
      "back": "mathematics"
    },
    {
      "front": "数",
      "back": "number"
    },
    {
      "front": "数える",
      "back": "count"
    },
    {
      "front": "まとめる",
      "back": "gather together, put in order"
    },
    {
      "front": "今回",
      "back": "this time"
    },
    {
      "front": "回る",
      "back": "turn round, go around"
    },
    {
      "front": "回す",
      "back": "turn, rotate (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "セーター",
      "back": "sweater"
    },
    {
      "front": "勝つ",
      "back": "win"
    },
    {
      "front": "負ける",
      "back": "lose"
    },
    {
      "front": "当時",
      "back": "at that time"
    },
    {
      "front": "本当に",
      "back": "really, truly"
    },
    {
      "front": "本当",
      "back": "truth, reality"
    },
    {
      "front": "担当",
      "back": "person in charge"
    },
    {
      "front": "当たる",
      "back": "hit, strike"
    },
    {
      "front": "弁当",
      "back": "boxed lunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "シャツ",
      "back": "shirt"
    },
    {
      "front": "アイスクリーム<br>",
      "back": "ice cream"
    },
    {
      "front": "全然",
      "back": "(not ) at all"
    },
    {
      "front": "当然",
      "back": "natural, as a matter of course"
    },
    {
      "front": "偶然",
      "back": "by chance, coincidence"
    },
    {
      "front": "方法",
      "back": "method, procedure"
    },
    {
      "front": "法律",
      "back": "law"
    },
    {
      "front": "なかなか",
      "back": "rather, pretty"
    },
    {
      "front": "規則",
      "back": "rule, regulation"
    },
    {
      "front": "試験",
      "back": "exam"
    },
    {
      "front": "経験",
      "back": "experience, knowledge or skill gained"
    },
    {
      "front": "経つ",
      "back": "pass, elapse"
    },
    {
      "front": "経営",
      "back": "management, operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "マンション",
      "back": "apartment, residential building"
    },
    {
      "front": "企業",
      "back": "corporation, business"
    },
    {
      "front": "卒業",
      "back": "graduation"
    },
    {
      "front": "利用",
      "back": "utilization, usage"
    },
    {
      "front": "便利",
      "back": "convenience"
    },
    {
      "front": "エレベーター",
      "back": "elevator"
    },
    {
      "front": "必ず",
      "back": "without exception, always"
    },
    {
      "front": "重要",
      "back": "important, essential"
    },
    {
      "front": "必要",
      "back": "need, necessary"
    },
    {
      "front": "要る",
      "back": "need, require"
    },
    {
      "front": "トラック",
      "back": "truck"
    },
    {
      "front": "目",
      "back": "eye"
    },
    {
      "front": "時計",
      "back": "clock, watch"
    },
    {
      "front": "目覚まし時計",
      "back": "alarm clock"
    },
    {
      "front": "合計",
      "back": "sum, total"
    },
    {
      "front": "レコード",
      "back": "record"
    },
    {
      "front": "割る",
      "back": "divide, split"
    },
    {
      "front": "割れる",
      "back": "crack, split"
    },
    {
      "front": "残す",
      "back": "leave, leave undone"
    },
    {
      "front": "残る",
      "back": "remain, be left over"
    },
    {
      "front": "ページ",
      "back": "page"
    },
    {
      "front": "返事",
      "back": "answer, reply"
    },
    {
      "front": "返す",
      "back": "return, repay"
    },
    {
      "front": "繰り返す",
      "back": "repeat"
    },
    {
      "front": "借りる",
      "back": "borrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸し出す",
      "back": "lend, lend out"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸す",
      "back": "lend, lease"
    },
    {
      "front": "申し込む",
      "back": "apply, sign up"
    },
    {
      "front": "込む",
      "back": "be crowded, be congested"
    },
    {
      "front": "待つ",
      "back": "wait, wait for"
    },
    {
      "front": "時期",
      "back": "time, season"
    },
    {
      "front": "期間",
      "back": "term, period"
    },
    {
      "front": "期待",
      "back": "expectation, anticipation"
    },
    {
      "front": "限る",
      "back": "be limited to"
    },
    {
      "front": "急行",
      "back": "express train"
    },
    {
      "front": "急ぐ",
      "back": "hurry, do quickly"
    },
    {
      "front": "急に",
      "back": "suddenly, unexpectedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "急",
      "back": "urgent, steep"
    },
    {
      "front": "救急車",
      "back": "ambulance"
    },
    {
      "front": "アルバイト",
      "back": "part-time job"
    },
    {
      "front": "大切",
      "back": "important, valuable"
    },
    {
      "front": "切手",
      "back": "postage stamp"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り切れ",
      "back": "sell out"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り切れる",
      "back": "sell out, go out of stock"
    },
    {
      "front": "切る",
      "back": "cut"
    },
    {
      "front": "切れる",
      "back": "cut well, be sharp"
    },
    {
      "front": "切符",
      "back": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "コート",
      "back": "coat, jacket (loan word)"
    },
    {
      "front": "コピー",
      "back": "copy, photocopy"
    },
    {
      "front": "時代",
      "back": "age, era"
    },
    {
      "front": "代える",
      "back": "substitute for"
    },
    {
      "front": "代わり",
      "back": "substitution, alternative"
    },
    {
      "front": "カード",
      "back": "card"
    },
    {
      "front": "指",
      "back": "finger, toe"
    },
    {
      "front": "指輪",
      "back": "ring"
    },
    {
      "front": "入場券",
      "back": "entrance ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "決定",
      "back": "decision"
    },
    {
      "front": "定期券",
      "back": "commuter pass"
    },
    {
      "front": "グラム",
      "back": "gram"
    },
    {
      "front": "天気予報",
      "back": "weather forecast"
    },
    {
      "front": "予定",
      "back": "schedule, plan"
    },
    {
      "front": "予約",
      "back": "reservation, appointment"
    },
    {
      "front": "約束",
      "back": "promise, vow"
    },
    {
      "front": "スキー",
      "back": "ski, skiing"
    },
    {
      "front": "大変",
      "back": "awful, hard"
    },
    {
      "front": "変える",
      "back": "change (something), alter"
    },
    {
      "front": "変わる",
      "back": "change, turn into"
    },
    {
      "front": "変",
      "back": "strange, weird"
    },
    {
      "front": "ソフト",
      "back": "software, program"
    },
    {
      "front": "文化",
      "back": "culture"
    },
    {
      "front": "変化",
      "back": "change, alteration"
    },
    {
      "front": "化粧",
      "back": "makeup"
    },
    {
      "front": "増える",
      "back": "increase, accrue"
    },
    {
      "front": "増やす",
      "back": "increase, add"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひととき",
      "back": "some moments, a while"
    },
    {
      "front": "減る",
      "back": "decrease, diminish"
    },
    {
      "front": "減らす",
      "back": "reduce (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り物",
      "back": "vehicle, transportation"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗る",
      "back": "ride, take"
    },
    {
      "front": "カラー",
      "back": "color (loan word)"
    },
    {
      "front": "降る",
      "back": "fall, come down"
    },
    {
      "front": "降りる",
      "back": "get off, land"
    },
    {
      "front": "降ろす",
      "back": "unload, set down"
    },
    {
      "front": "すり",
      "back": "pickpocket"
    },
    {
      "front": "水着",
      "back": "bathing suit, swimsuit"
    },
    {
      "front": "上着",
      "back": "outerwear, coat, jacket"
    },
    {
      "front": "下着",
      "back": "underwear"
    },
    {
      "front": "着物",
      "back": "traditional Japanese clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "着る",
      "back": "wear, put on"
    },
    {
      "front": "着く",
      "back": "arrive at, reach"
    },
    {
      "front": "着せる",
      "back": "dress (someone)"
    },
    {
      "front": "キャンプ",
      "back": "camping, camp"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱ぐ",
      "back": "take off (clothes)"
    },
    {
      "front": "目立つ",
      "back": "stand out, be conspicuous"
    },
    {
      "front": "立場",
      "back": "standpoint, position"
    },
    {
      "front": "役に立つ",
      "back": "be useful, be helpful"
    },
    {
      "front": "立つ",
      "back": "stand, rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "立てる",
      "back": "stand, set up"
    },
    {
      "front": "立派",
      "back": "fine, elegant"
    },
    {
      "front": "オートバイ",
      "back": "motorbike, motorcycle"
    },
    {
      "front": "なかなか",
      "back": "not easily, not readily"
    },
    {
      "front": "座る",
      "back": "sit, sit down"
    },
    {
      "front": "席",
      "back": "seat, one's place"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠席",
      "back": "absence (from school, a gathering, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "さっき",
      "back": "earlier, only a moment ago"
    },
    {
      "front": "次",
      "back": "next"
    },
    {
      "front": "家賃",
      "back": "rent"
    },
    {
      "front": "運ぶ",
      "back": "carry, transport"
    },
    {
      "front": "そんなに",
      "back": "so much"
    },
    {
      "front": "運転手",
      "back": "driver"
    },
    {
      "front": "運転",
      "back": "drive"
    },
    {
      "front": "転ぶ",
      "back": "fall down, fall over"
    },
    {
      "front": "移す",
      "back": "move, transfer"
    },
    {
      "front": "移る",
      "back": "move, shift"
    },
    {
      "front": "びっくりする",
      "back": "be surprised, be startled (casual)"
    },
    {
      "front": "生活",
      "back": "life, living"
    },
    {
      "front": "不動産屋",
      "back": "real estate agent"
    },
    {
      "front": "動物",
      "back": "animal"
    },
    {
      "front": "活動",
      "back": "activity"
    },
    {
      "front": "運動",
      "back": "movement, exercise"
    },
    {
      "front": "動く",
      "back": "move"
    },
    {
      "front": "動かす",
      "back": "move (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "デパート",
      "back": "department store"
    },
    {
      "front": "働く",
      "back": "work"
    },
    {
      "front": "早口",
      "back": "speaking fast"
    },
    {
      "front": "早い",
      "back": "early"
    },
    {
      "front": "早く",
      "back": "early, soon"
    },
    {
      "front": "トイレ",
      "back": "toilet"
    },
    {
      "front": "早速",
      "back": "immediately, right away"
    },
    {
      "front": "速い",
      "back": "fast"
    },
    {
      "front": "速さ",
      "back": "speed"
    },
    {
      "front": "遅い",
      "back": "slow, late"
    },
    {
      "front": "遅れる",
      "back": "be late"
    },
    {
      "front": "遅刻",
      "back": "tardiness, lateness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶつかる",
      "back": "hit, bump into"
    },
    {
      "front": "開始",
      "back": "beginning"
    },
    {
      "front": "始める",
      "back": "start (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "始まる",
      "back": "begin"
    },
    {
      "front": "始めに",
      "back": "in the beginning, first"
    },
    {
      "front": "レストラン",
      "back": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "front": "終わり",
      "back": "end, conclusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "現金",
      "back": "cash"
    },
    {
      "front": "現在",
      "back": "the present, present time"
    },
    {
      "front": "メモ",
      "back": "memo, note"
    },
    {
      "front": "事実",
      "back": "fact, truth"
    },
    {
      "front": "実験",
      "back": "experiment"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼過ぎ",
      "back": "early afternoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "過ぎる",
      "back": "pass by, go past"
    },
    {
      "front": "パン",
      "back": "bread"
    },
    {
      "front": "去年",
      "back": "last year (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "過去",
      "back": "the past"
    },
    {
      "front": "出発",
      "back": "departure, starting"
    },
    {
      "front": "発見",
      "back": "discovery, revelation"
    },
    {
      "front": "発車",
      "back": "departure (of a vehicle)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ワイン",
      "back": "wine"
    },
    {
      "front": "代表",
      "back": "representative"
    },
    {
      "front": "表現",
      "back": "expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "発表",
      "back": "announcement"
    },
    {
      "front": "表",
      "back": "front, outside"
    },
    {
      "front": "表",
      "back": "table, list"
    },
    {
      "front": "プール",
      "back": "pool"
    },
    {
      "front": "手紙",
      "back": "letter"
    },
    {
      "front": "紙",
      "back": "paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピアノ",
      "back": "piano"
    },
    {
      "front": "複雑",
      "back": "complicated, intricate"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑誌",
      "back": "magazine, journal"
    },
    {
      "front": "音",
      "back": "sound, noise"
    },
    {
      "front": "音楽",
      "back": "music"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽しい",
      "back": "fun, enjoyable"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽しみ",
      "back": "enjoyment, something looked forward to"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボール",
      "back": "ball"
    },
    {
      "front": "ノート",
      "back": "notebook"
    },
    {
      "front": "郵便局",
      "back": "post office"
    },
    {
      "front": "薬局",
      "back": "drugstore, pharmacy"
    },
    {
      "front": "薬",
      "back": "drug, medicine"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌手",
      "back": "singer"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌う",
      "back": "sing"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌",
      "back": "song"
    },
    {
      "front": "インタビュー",
      "back": "interview"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲しい",
      "back": "want, desire"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲しがる",
      "back": "want, desire"
    },
    {
      "front": "ホーム",
      "back": "platform"
    },
    {
      "front": "計画",
      "back": "plan, project"
    },
    {
      "front": "映画",
      "back": "movie"
    },
    {
      "front": "漫画",
      "back": "comics, cartoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "写る",
      "back": "be photographed"
    },
    {
      "front": "写す",
      "back": "copy, photograph"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベッド",
      "back": "bed"
    },
    {
      "front": "暗い",
      "back": "dark, gloomy"
    },
    {
      "front": "真面目",
      "back": "serious, earnest"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ青",
      "back": "deep-blue, pale"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ暗",
      "back": "pitch-dark"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ白",
      "back": "pure-white"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ黒",
      "back": "black, jet-black"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ赤",
      "back": "deep red"
    },
    {
      "front": "写真",
      "back": "photograph"
    },
    {
      "front": "ソファー",
      "back": "sofa, couch"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボート",
      "back": "light boat, small craft"
    },
    {
      "front": "茶色",
      "back": "brown"
    },
    {
      "front": "色",
      "back": "color"
    },
    {
      "front": "プラスチック",
      "back": "plastic"
    },
    {
      "front": "形",
      "back": "shape, form"
    },
    {
      "front": "書類",
      "back": "documents, papers"
    },
    {
      "front": "種類",
      "back": "kind, type"
    },
    {
      "front": "スイッチ",
      "back": "switch"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ直ぐ",
      "back": "straight"
    },
    {
      "front": "直る",
      "back": "be repaired, get fixed"
    },
    {
      "front": "直す",
      "back": "repair, fix"
    },
    {
      "front": "面接",
      "back": "interview"
    },
    {
      "front": "直接",
      "back": "directly"
    },
    {
      "front": "プレゼント",
      "back": "present, gift"
    },
    {
      "front": "道路",
      "back": "road, street"
    },
    {
      "front": "線路",
      "back": "railway track, line"
    },
    {
      "front": "線",
      "back": "line"
    },
    {
      "front": "新幹線",
      "back": "bullet train"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつでも",
      "back": "at all times, any time"
    },
    {
      "front": "三角",
      "back": "triangle"
    },
    {
      "front": "四つ角",
      "back": "intersection"
    },
    {
      "front": "四角",
      "back": "square"
    },
    {
      "front": "四角い",
      "back": "square"
    },
    {
      "front": "角",
      "back": "corner, edge"
    },
    {
      "front": "テニス",
      "back": "tennis"
    },
    {
      "front": "曲がり角",
      "back": "corner (to turn)"
    },
    {
      "front": "曲げる",
      "back": "bend (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボタン",
      "back": "button"
    },
    {
      "front": "同じ",
      "back": "same, identical"
    },
    {
      "front": "間違える",
      "back": "mistake"
    },
    {
      "front": "間違い",
      "back": "mistake, error"
    },
    {
      "front": "違う",
      "back": "differ, be wrong"
    },
    {
      "front": "違い",
      "back": "difference, mistake"
    },
    {
      "front": "勘違い",
      "back": "misunderstanding"
    },
    {
      "front": "コート",
      "back": "sports court"
    },
    {
      "front": "似合う",
      "back": "suit, match well"
    },
    {
      "front": "似ている",
      "back": "look like, resemble"
    },
    {
      "front": "以上",
      "back": "more than, not less than"
    },
    {
      "front": "以下",
      "back": "below"
    },
    {
      "front": "以外",
      "back": "except for"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドラマ",
      "back": "drama"
    },
    {
      "front": "地図",
      "back": "map, atlas"
    },
    {
      "front": "使う",
      "back": "use"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅行",
      "back": "travel, trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "大使館",
      "back": "embassy"
    },
    {
      "front": "図書館",
      "back": "library"
    },
    {
      "front": "映画館",
      "back": "movie theater"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅館",
      "back": "Japanese inn"
    },
    {
      "front": "博物館",
      "back": "museum"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビザ",
      "back": "visa"
    },
    {
      "front": "ポケット",
      "back": "pocket"
    },
    {
      "front": "泊まる",
      "back": "stay overnight"
    },
    {
      "front": "泊める",
      "back": "let (someone) stay over"
    },
    {
      "front": "遊ぶ",
      "back": "play"
    },
    {
      "front": "遊び",
      "back": "play, amusement"
    },
    {
      "front": "そろそろ",
      "back": "soon, it's about time"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋服",
      "back": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "服",
      "back": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "窓",
      "back": "window"
    },
    {
      "front": "お父さん",
      "back": "father"
    },
    {
      "front": "父",
      "back": "(speaker's) father"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶどう",
      "back": "grapes"
    },
    {
      "front": "お母さん",
      "back": "mother"
    },
    {
      "front": "母",
      "back": "(speaker's) mother"
    },
    {
      "front": "不親切",
      "back": "unkind, inconsiderate"
    },
    {
      "front": "親切",
      "back": "kind, kindhearted"
    },
    {
      "front": "父親",
      "back": "father"
    },
    {
      "front": "母親",
      "back": "mother"
    },
    {
      "front": "親",
      "back": "parent"
    },
    {
      "front": "親しい",
      "back": "intimate, familiar"
    },
    {
      "front": "めったに",
      "back": "rarely, seldom"
    },
    {
      "front": "クリスマス",
      "back": "Christmas"
    },
    {
      "front": "姉",
      "back": "older sister"
    },
    {
      "front": "お姉さん",
      "back": "older sister"
    },
    {
      "front": "姉さん",
      "back": "older sister"
    },
    {
      "front": "ネクタイ",
      "back": "tie, necktie"
    },
    {
      "front": "妹",
      "back": "younger sister"
    },
    {
      "front": "兄",
      "back": "older brother"
    },
    {
      "front": "お兄さん",
      "back": "older brother"
    },
    {
      "front": "兄さん",
      "back": "older brother"
    },
    {
      "front": "兄弟",
      "back": "sibling"
    },
    {
      "front": "弟",
      "back": "younger brother"
    },
    {
      "front": "バイオリン",
      "back": "violin"
    },
    {
      "front": "娘",
      "back": "daughter, girl"
    },
    {
      "front": "若い",
      "back": "young"
    },
    {
      "front": "若者",
      "back": "young person, youth"
    },
    {
      "front": "患者",
      "back": "patient"
    },
    {
      "front": "バッグ",
      "back": "bag"
    },
    {
      "front": "彼女",
      "back": "she, one's girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "front": "彼",
      "back": "he, one's boyfriend"
    },
    {
      "front": "彼ら",
      "back": "they"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゴム",
      "back": "elastic, rubber"
    },
    {
      "front": "結婚",
      "back": "marriage"
    },
    {
      "front": "結構",
      "back": "quite"
    },
    {
      "front": "離婚",
      "back": "divorce"
    },
    {
      "front": "果物",
      "back": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "front": "結果",
      "back": "result, outcome"
    },
    {
      "front": "効果",
      "back": "effect, result"
    },
    {
      "front": "ギター",
      "back": "guitar"
    },
    {
      "front": "課",
      "back": "section, division"
    },
    {
      "front": "やっぱり",
      "back": "just as I thought, after all"
    },
    {
      "front": "自分",
      "back": "self, oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "自転車",
      "back": "bicycle"
    },
    {
      "front": "自動車",
      "back": "automobile"
    },
    {
      "front": "自然",
      "back": "nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "自然",
      "back": "natural"
    },
    {
      "front": "自動",
      "back": "automatic operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "カーテン",
      "back": "curtain"
    },
    {
      "front": "理由",
      "back": "reason, cause"
    },
    {
      "front": "自由",
      "back": "freedom"
    },
    {
      "front": "番号",
      "back": "number"
    },
    {
      "front": "信号",
      "back": "signal, traffic light"
    },
    {
      "front": "信じる",
      "back": "believe, trust"
    },
    {
      "front": "ナイフ",
      "back": "knife"
    },
    {
      "front": "頼む",
      "back": "order, ask for"
    },
    {
      "front": "ご主人",
      "back": "(someone else's) husband"
    },
    {
      "front": "主人",
      "back": "one's husband, master"
    },
    {
      "front": "主に",
      "back": "mostly, predominantly"
    },
    {
      "front": "会議",
      "back": "conference, meeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "不思議",
      "back": "mystery, wonder"
    },
    {
      "front": "反対",
      "back": "oppose, object"
    },
    {
      "front": "対する",
      "back": "face, be in response to"
    },
    {
      "front": "答える",
      "back": "give an answer"
    },
    {
      "front": "バイク",
      "back": "motorcycle"
    },
    {
      "front": "特急",
      "back": "super-express"
    },
    {
      "front": "特に",
      "back": "specially, particularly"
    },
    {
      "front": "特別",
      "back": "special"
    },
    {
      "front": "別",
      "back": "another, different"
    },
    {
      "front": "別々",
      "back": "separately"
    },
    {
      "front": "別れる",
      "back": "separate, part"
    },
    {
      "front": "別に",
      "back": "particularly, not really"
    },
    {
      "front": "普通",
      "back": "normal, regular"
    },
    {
      "front": "普段",
      "back": "usual, ordinary"
    },
    {
      "front": "きつい",
      "back": "tight, tough"
    },
    {
      "front": "並ぶ",
      "back": "line up, be parallel"
    },
    {
      "front": "並べる",
      "back": "line up, arrange"
    },
    {
      "front": "平和",
      "back": "peace, harmony"
    },
    {
      "front": "テキスト",
      "back": "text, textbook"
    },
    {
      "front": "病気",
      "back": "illness"
    },
    {
      "front": "大学院",
      "back": "graduate school"
    },
    {
      "front": "入院",
      "back": "be hospitalized"
    },
    {
      "front": "病院",
      "back": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビニール",
      "back": "plastic, vinyl"
    },
    {
      "front": "お医者さん",
      "back": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "front": "医者",
      "back": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯医者",
      "back": "dentist"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯",
      "back": "tooth"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯ブラシ",
      "back": "toothbrush"
    },
    {
      "front": "アルバム",
      "back": "album"
    },
    {
      "front": "教科書",
      "back": "textbook, schoolbook"
    },
    {
      "front": "理科",
      "back": "science"
    },
    {
      "front": "科学",
      "back": "science"
    },
    {
      "front": "死ぬ",
      "back": "die"
    },
    {
      "front": "スカート",
      "back": "skirt"
    },
    {
      "front": "亡くなる",
      "back": "die, pass away"
    },
    {
      "front": "忙しい",
      "back": "busy, occupied"
    },
    {
      "front": "疲れる",
      "back": "get tired, become fatigued"
    },
    {
      "front": "痛い",
      "back": "sore, painful"
    },
    {
      "front": "痛み",
      "back": "pain, ache"
    },
    {
      "front": "ペン",
      "back": "pen"
    },
    {
      "front": "禁煙",
      "back": "non-smoking"
    },
    {
      "front": "酒",
      "back": "alcohol, rice wine"
    },
    {
      "front": "払う",
      "back": "pay"
    },
    {
      "front": "酔っ払う",
      "back": "get drunk"
    },
    {
      "front": "酔っ払い",
      "back": "drunkard, drunk"
    },
    {
      "front": "おしゃべり",
      "back": "talkative, chatty"
    },
    {
      "front": "危ない",
      "back": "dangerous"
    },
    {
      "front": "危険",
      "back": "danger, dangerous"
    },
    {
      "front": "注目",
      "back": "attention, notice"
    },
    {
      "front": "注文",
      "back": "order"
    },
    {
      "front": "注射",
      "back": "injection, shot"
    },
    {
      "front": "意見",
      "back": "opinion"
    },
    {
      "front": "意味",
      "back": "meaning, significance"
    },
    {
      "front": "用意",
      "back": "preparation"
    },
    {
      "front": "注意",
      "back": "attention, care"
    },
    {
      "front": "得意",
      "back": "one's specialty, be good at"
    },
    {
      "front": "おしゃれ",
      "back": "trendy, fashionable"
    },
    {
      "front": "確か",
      "back": "for sure, for certain"
    },
    {
      "front": "確かめる",
      "back": "check, confirm"
    },
    {
      "front": "確認",
      "back": "confirmation"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジュース",
      "back": "juice"
    },
    {
      "front": "機能",
      "back": "function, feature"
    },
    {
      "front": "機械",
      "back": "machine"
    },
    {
      "front": "扇風機",
      "back": "electric fan"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゼロ",
      "back": "zero, none"
    },
    {
      "front": "目的",
      "back": "objective, purpose"
    },
    {
      "front": "具体的",
      "back": "concrete, specific"
    },
    {
      "front": "具合",
      "back": "condition, health"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピンク",
      "back": "pink"
    },
    {
      "front": "準備",
      "back": "preparation, arrangement"
    },
    {
      "front": "備える",
      "back": "provide for, prepare for"
    },
    {
      "front": "小説",
      "back": "novel"
    },
    {
      "front": "説明",
      "back": "explanation, description"
    },
    {
      "front": "グラス",
      "back": "glass"
    },
    {
      "front": "動物園",
      "back": "zoo"
    },
    {
      "front": "公園",
      "back": "park, public garden"
    },
    {
      "front": "祭り",
      "back": "festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "国際",
      "back": "international"
    },
    {
      "front": "実際",
      "back": "reality, actual state"
    },
    {
      "front": "ほぼ",
      "back": "almost, nearly"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛行機",
      "back": "airplane"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛ぶ",
      "back": "fly"
    },
    {
      "front": "船",
      "back": "ship, vessel"
    },
    {
      "front": "空港",
      "back": "airport (for public transportation)"
    },
    {
      "front": "港",
      "back": "port, harbor"
    },
    {
      "front": "島",
      "back": "island (Japanese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "平成",
      "back": "Heisei era"
    },
    {
      "front": "完成",
      "back": "completion"
    },
    {
      "front": "成功",
      "back": "success"
    },
    {
      "front": "成績",
      "back": "results, grade"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばか",
      "back": "foolish, stupid"
    },
    {
      "front": "原因",
      "back": "cause, origin"
    },
    {
      "front": "あんなに",
      "back": "that much, such"
    },
    {
      "front": "お願い",
      "back": "favor"
    },
    {
      "front": "願う",
      "back": "wish, hope"
    },
    {
      "front": "正月",
      "back": "New Year"
    },
    {
      "front": "正午",
      "back": "noon"
    },
    {
      "front": "正直",
      "back": "honest, upright"
    },
    {
      "front": "正確",
      "back": "accurate, precise"
    },
    {
      "front": "正しい",
      "back": "correct, righteous"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちゃんと",
      "back": "correctly, properly"
    },
    {
      "front": "異なる",
      "back": "differ"
    },
    {
      "front": "非常に",
      "back": "very, extremely"
    },
    {
      "front": "是非",
      "back": "by all means, please"
    },
    {
      "front": "のんびり",
      "back": "take it easy"
    },
    {
      "front": "調べる",
      "back": "investigate, check"
    },
    {
      "front": "季節",
      "back": "season"
    },
    {
      "front": "サッカー",
      "back": "soccer, football"
    },
    {
      "front": "子供",
      "back": "child, kid"
    },
    {
      "front": "案内",
      "back": "guide, guidance"
    },
    {
      "front": "提案",
      "back": "proposition, proposal"
    },
    {
      "front": "スープ",
      "back": "soup"
    },
    {
      "front": "連れて来る",
      "back": "bring (a person)"
    },
    {
      "front": "連れて行く",
      "back": "take along, bring along (a person)"
    },
    {
      "front": "連絡",
      "back": "contact, communication"
    },
    {
      "front": "手続き",
      "back": "procedure, proceeding"
    },
    {
      "front": "接続",
      "back": "connection, joining"
    },
    {
      "front": "続く",
      "back": "continue, follow"
    },
    {
      "front": "続ける",
      "back": "continue, keep up"
    },
    {
      "front": "続き",
      "back": "continuation, sequel"
    },
    {
      "front": "バナナ",
      "back": "banana"
    },
    {
      "front": "可哀相",
      "back": "poor, pitiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "相手",
      "back": "opponent, the other party"
    },
    {
      "front": "相談",
      "back": "consultation, advice"
    },
    {
      "front": "冗談",
      "back": "joke"
    },
    {
      "front": "日記",
      "back": "diary"
    },
    {
      "front": "録音",
      "back": "(sound) recording"
    },
    {
      "front": "記録",
      "back": "record, documentation"
    },
    {
      "front": "登る",
      "back": "climb, go up"
    },
    {
      "front": "関する",
      "back": "relate to, regarding"
    },
    {
      "front": "関係",
      "back": "relation, relationship"
    },
    {
      "front": "玄関",
      "back": "entrance, door"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハンバーガー",
      "back": "hamburger"
    },
    {
      "front": "状況",
      "back": "state of affairs, conditions"
    },
    {
      "front": "状態",
      "back": "state, condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "年賀状",
      "back": "New Year's card"
    },
    {
      "front": "エスカレーター",
      "back": "escalator"
    },
    {
      "front": "政治",
      "back": "politics"
    },
    {
      "front": "治る",
      "back": "be cured, get well"
    },
    {
      "front": "治す",
      "back": "cure (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "政府",
      "back": "government, administration"
    },
    {
      "front": "タオル",
      "back": "towel"
    },
    {
      "front": "選手",
      "back": "athlete, (sports) player"
    },
    {
      "front": "選ぶ",
      "back": "choose, elect"
    },
    {
      "front": "首都",
      "back": "capital"
    },
    {
      "front": "首",
      "back": "neck"
    },
    {
      "front": "悩む",
      "back": "be troubled, suffer"
    },
    {
      "front": "頭",
      "back": "head"
    },
    {
      "front": "顔",
      "back": "face"
    },
    {
      "front": "革",
      "back": "leather"
    },
    {
      "front": "命令",
      "back": "command, order"
    },
    {
      "front": "一生懸命",
      "back": "hard-working, doing one's best"
    },
    {
      "front": "ケーキ",
      "back": "cake"
    },
    {
      "front": "番組",
      "back": "program"
    },
    {
      "front": "組み立てる",
      "back": "set up, put together"
    },
    {
      "front": "進める",
      "back": "go ahead, proceed"
    },
    {
      "front": "進む",
      "back": "advance, move forward"
    },
    {
      "front": "スーツ",
      "back": "suit"
    },
    {
      "front": "責任",
      "back": "responsibility"
    },
    {
      "front": "辞書",
      "back": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "front": "辞める",
      "back": "resign, leave (one's job), quit"
    },
    {
      "front": "お辞儀",
      "back": "bow"
    },
    {
      "front": "チケット",
      "back": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "通勤",
      "back": "commute"
    },
    {
      "front": "勤める",
      "back": "serve, hold a job"
    },
    {
      "front": "チョコレート",
      "back": "chocolate"
    },
    {
      "front": "教室",
      "back": "classroom, class"
    },
    {
      "front": "事務所",
      "back": "office, one's place of business"
    },
    {
      "front": "事務室",
      "back": "office"
    },
    {
      "front": "集める",
      "back": "collect, gather"
    },
    {
      "front": "職場",
      "back": "place of work, office"
    },
    {
      "front": "職業",
      "back": "occupation, job"
    },
    {
      "front": "事件",
      "back": "affair, incident"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガソリンスタンド",
      "back": "gas station"
    },
    {
      "front": "工事",
      "back": "construction, repairing"
    },
    {
      "front": "参加",
      "back": "participation"
    },
    {
      "front": "デート",
      "back": "date"
    },
    {
      "front": "比べる",
      "back": "compare, contrast"
    },
    {
      "front": "感じる",
      "back": "feel, sense"
    },
    {
      "front": "火傷",
      "back": "burn"
    },
    {
      "front": "傷める",
      "back": "damage, spoil"
    },
    {
      "front": "傷",
      "back": "wound, scar"
    },
    {
      "front": "レモン",
      "back": "lemon"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り換える",
      "back": "change, transfer"
    },
    {
      "front": "換える",
      "back": "exchange, convert"
    },
    {
      "front": "チーズ",
      "back": "cheese"
    },
    {
      "front": "被る",
      "back": "wear, put on (on one's head)"
    },
    {
      "front": "破る",
      "back": "tear, breach"
    },
    {
      "front": "破れる",
      "back": "tear, rip open"
    },
    {
      "front": "壊れる",
      "back": "break, break down"
    },
    {
      "front": "壊す",
      "back": "break (something), destroy"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドライブ",
      "back": "drive"
    },
    {
      "front": "助ける",
      "back": "help, save"
    },
    {
      "front": "警察",
      "back": "police"
    },
    {
      "front": "盗む",
      "back": "steal, rob"
    },
    {
      "front": "殺す",
      "back": "kill"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラケット",
      "back": "racket"
    },
    {
      "front": "逃げる",
      "back": "escape, run away"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦争",
      "back": "war, battle"
    },
    {
      "front": "競争",
      "back": "competition"
    },
    {
      "front": "探す",
      "back": "search for, look for"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひげ",
      "back": "beard, mustache"
    },
    {
      "front": "捨てる",
      "back": "discard, abandon"
    },
    {
      "front": "拾う",
      "back": "pick up"
    },
    {
      "front": "電池",
      "back": "battery"
    },
    {
      "front": "池",
      "back": "pond"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐっすり",
      "back": "soundly"
    },
    {
      "front": "深い",
      "back": "deep, profound"
    },
    {
      "front": "浅い",
      "back": "shallow, superficial"
    },
    {
      "front": "水泳",
      "back": "swimming"
    },
    {
      "front": "泳ぐ",
      "back": "swim"
    },
    {
      "front": "流行る",
      "back": "be in fashion, be popular"
    },
    {
      "front": "流れる",
      "back": "flow, stream"
    },
    {
      "front": "お手洗い",
      "back": "toilet, bathroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗面所",
      "back": "washroom, bathroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗う",
      "back": "wash"
    },
    {
      "front": "トマト",
      "back": "tomato"
    },
    {
      "front": "油",
      "back": "oil"
    },
    {
      "front": "醤油",
      "back": "soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "front": "バター",
      "back": "butter"
    },
    {
      "front": "沈む",
      "back": "sink"
    },
    {
      "front": "久しぶり",
      "back": "after a long time"
    },
    {
      "front": "氷",
      "back": "ice"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷たい",
      "back": "cold (to touch)"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷める",
      "back": "cool off"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷える",
      "back": "cool down, get chilled"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷やす",
      "back": "chill (something), cool down"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷蔵庫",
      "back": "refrigerator"
    },
    {
      "front": "バレーボール",
      "back": "volleyball"
    },
    {
      "front": "おかず",
      "back": "dishes to go with the rice"
    },
    {
      "front": "凍る",
      "back": "freeze"
    },
    {
      "front": "涼しい",
      "back": "cool (of temperature)"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚い",
      "back": "dirty"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚れる",
      "back": "become dirty"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚す",
      "back": "make (something) dirty"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚れ",
      "back": "dirt, blot"
    },
    {
      "front": "カレンダー",
      "back": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "front": "影響",
      "back": "influence, effect"
    },
    {
      "front": "光る",
      "back": "shine, emit light, sparkle"
    },
    {
      "front": "太い",
      "back": "thick, fat"
    },
    {
      "front": "太る",
      "back": "grow fat, gain weight"
    },
    {
      "front": "太陽",
      "back": "sun"
    },
    {
      "front": "星",
      "back": "star, planet"
    },
    {
      "front": "地球",
      "back": "the earth"
    },
    {
      "front": "野球",
      "back": "baseball"
    },
    {
      "front": "おしゃべり",
      "back": "chatter, idle talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "雲",
      "back": "cloud"
    },
    {
      "front": "曇る",
      "back": "become cloudy"
    },
    {
      "front": "曇り",
      "back": "cloudy weather"
    },
    {
      "front": "くすぐったい",
      "back": "ticklish"
    },
    {
      "front": "地震",
      "back": "earthquake"
    },
    {
      "front": "震える",
      "back": "tremble, shake"
    },
    {
      "front": "振り向く",
      "back": "turn around, look back"
    },
    {
      "front": "振る",
      "back": "wave, shake"
    },
    {
      "front": "タイプライター",
      "back": "typewriter"
    },
    {
      "front": "揺れる",
      "back": "shake, sway"
    },
    {
      "front": "秘密",
      "back": "secret, privacy"
    },
    {
      "front": "厳しい",
      "back": "strict, severe"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄る",
      "back": "stop by, stop off"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベル",
      "back": "bell"
    },
    {
      "front": "歴史",
      "back": "history"
    },
    {
      "front": "建物",
      "back": "building, structure"
    },
    {
      "front": "建設",
      "back": "construction (of a building, road, bridge, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "建てる",
      "back": "build, erect"
    },
    {
      "front": "建つ",
      "back": "be built, be erected"
    },
    {
      "front": "クーラー",
      "back": "air conditioner (cooling)"
    },
    {
      "front": "橋",
      "back": "bridge"
    },
    {
      "front": "位置",
      "back": "position, location"
    },
    {
      "front": "置く",
      "back": "put, place"
    },
    {
      "front": "停車",
      "back": "stop (of a train)"
    },
    {
      "front": "バス停",
      "back": "bus stop"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミルク",
      "back": "milk"
    },
    {
      "front": "周辺",
      "back": "area, region"
    },
    {
      "front": "辺",
      "back": "vicinity"
    },
    {
      "front": "隣",
      "back": "next to, next door"
    },
    {
      "front": "サラダ",
      "back": "salad"
    },
    {
      "front": "黄色い",
      "back": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "front": "黄色",
      "back": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "front": "横書き",
      "back": "horizontal writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "横",
      "back": "side, width across"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベルト",
      "back": "belt"
    },
    {
      "front": "横断歩道",
      "back": "pedestrian crossing, crosswalk"
    },
    {
      "front": "判断",
      "back": "judgment, decision"
    },
    {
      "front": "断る",
      "back": "refuse, turn down"
    },
    {
      "front": "訪ねる",
      "back": "visit, call on"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラーメン",
      "back": "ramen (Chinese noodles)"
    },
    {
      "front": "文房具",
      "back": "stationery, writing materials"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖房",
      "back": "heating"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷房",
      "back": "air conditioning (cooling)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一緒に",
      "back": "together, at the same time"
    },
    {
      "front": "一緒",
      "back": "together"
    },
    {
      "front": "内緒",
      "back": "secrecy, privacy"
    },
    {
      "front": "ライター",
      "back": "lighter"
    },
    {
      "front": "緑色",
      "back": "green"
    },
    {
      "front": "緑",
      "back": "green"
    },
    {
      "front": "ワイシャツ",
      "back": "business shirt, dress shirt"
    },
    {
      "front": "易しい",
      "back": "easy, simple"
    },
    {
      "front": "復習",
      "back": "review"
    },
    {
      "front": "往復",
      "back": "round trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "停留所",
      "back": "(bus) stop"
    },
    {
      "front": "留学生",
      "back": "student studying abroad"
    },
    {
      "front": "留学",
      "back": "study abroad"
    },
    {
      "front": "シャワー",
      "back": "shower"
    },
    {
      "front": "留守",
      "back": "not at home"
    },
    {
      "front": "守る",
      "back": "protect, observe"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰宅",
      "back": "return home, come home"
    },
    {
      "front": "住宅",
      "back": "housing, residence"
    },
    {
      "front": "自宅",
      "back": "one's house, one's home"
    },
    {
      "front": "お宅",
      "back": "(someone else's) home"
    },
    {
      "front": "戻る",
      "back": "return to a point of departure"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごみ",
      "back": "trash"
    },
    {
      "front": "早起き",
      "back": "getting up early"
    },
    {
      "front": "起きる",
      "back": "get up, get out of bed"
    },
    {
      "front": "起こる",
      "back": "happen"
    },
    {
      "front": "起きる",
      "back": "occur, happen"
    },
    {
      "front": "スーパーマーケット",
      "back": "supermarket"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼寝",
      "back": "nap"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝る",
      "back": "sleep, go to sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝坊",
      "back": "oversleeping"
    },
    {
      "front": "静か",
      "back": "quiet, tranquil"
    },
    {
      "front": "暇",
      "back": "free time, spare time"
    },
    {
      "front": "着替える",
      "back": "change clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "両方",
      "back": "both"
    },
    {
      "front": "両親",
      "back": "parents"
    },
    {
      "front": "両替",
      "back": "money exchange"
    },
    {
      "front": "アナウンサー",
      "back": "announcer"
    },
    {
      "front": "右側",
      "back": "right side"
    },
    {
      "front": "左側",
      "back": "left side"
    },
    {
      "front": "外側",
      "back": "exterior, outside"
    },
    {
      "front": "内側",
      "back": "inside, interior"
    },
    {
      "front": "向こう側",
      "back": "other side"
    },
    {
      "front": "いかが",
      "back": "how"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏返す",
      "back": "turn over, turn inside out"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏",
      "back": "the back, the reverse side"
    },
    {
      "front": "ステレオ",
      "back": "stereo"
    },
    {
      "front": "週刊誌",
      "back": "weekly magazine"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝刊",
      "back": "morning edition paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕刊",
      "back": "evening edition paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "詳しい",
      "back": "detailed, complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "きらきら",
      "back": "sparkling, glittering"
    },
    {
      "front": "細い",
      "back": "thin, slender"
    },
    {
      "front": "細かい",
      "back": "minute, detailed"
    },
    {
      "front": "細か",
      "back": "minute, elaborate"
    },
    {
      "front": "載せる",
      "back": "place, put on"
    },
    {
      "front": "フィルム",
      "back": "film"
    },
    {
      "front": "積もる",
      "back": "pile up"
    },
    {
      "front": "訳",
      "back": "translation"
    },
    {
      "front": "訳す",
      "back": "translate"
    },
    {
      "front": "訳",
      "back": "reason, cause"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダンス",
      "back": "dance, dancing"
    },
    {
      "front": "誤解",
      "back": "misunderstanding"
    },
    {
      "front": "検討",
      "back": "examination and consideration"
    },
    {
      "front": "塗る",
      "back": "spread on, paint"
    },
    {
      "front": "片道",
      "back": "one way"
    },
    {
      "front": "気を付ける",
      "back": "be careful about, pay attention to"
    },
    {
      "front": "気付く",
      "back": "notice, realize"
    },
    {
      "front": "受付",
      "back": "receptionist, information office"
    },
    {
      "front": "片付ける",
      "back": "put in order, clean up"
    },
    {
      "front": "片付く",
      "back": "be put in order, be finished"
    },
    {
      "front": "付ける",
      "back": "attach, apply, put"
    },
    {
      "front": "付く",
      "back": "stick to, cling to"
    },
    {
      "front": "こんなに",
      "back": "this much, such"
    },
    {
      "front": "まあ",
      "back": "well (interjection)"
    },
    {
      "front": "メール",
      "back": "e-mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "貼る",
      "back": "stick, paste, put"
    },
    {
      "front": "記念日",
      "back": "memorial day, anniversary"
    },
    {
      "front": "残念",
      "back": "regretful, disappointing"
    },
    {
      "front": "例文",
      "back": "example sentence"
    },
    {
      "front": "例えば",
      "back": "for example"
    },
    {
      "front": "例",
      "back": "example"
    },
    {
      "front": "インターネット",
      "back": "Internet"
    },
    {
      "front": "余る",
      "back": "remain, be in excess"
    },
    {
      "front": "締める",
      "back": "tighten, fasten"
    },
    {
      "front": "スター",
      "back": "star"
    },
    {
      "front": "緩い",
      "back": "slack, loose"
    },
    {
      "front": "豊か",
      "back": "rich, ample"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦手",
      "back": "not good at, be bad at"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦しい",
      "back": "painful, agonizing"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦い",
      "back": "bitter"
    },
    {
      "front": "困る",
      "back": "be in trouble, not know what to do"
    },
    {
      "front": "甘い",
      "back": "sweet"
    },
    {
      "front": "不幸",
      "back": "unhappiness, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "front": "幸せ",
      "back": "happiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ネックレス",
      "back": "necklace"
    },
    {
      "front": "辛い",
      "back": "spicy, hot"
    },
    {
      "front": "塩辛い",
      "back": "salty"
    },
    {
      "front": "塩",
      "back": "salt"
    },
    {
      "front": "砂糖",
      "back": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "front": "濃い",
      "back": "strong, concentrated"
    },
    {
      "front": "薄い",
      "back": "thin, weak"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚い",
      "back": "thick, bulky"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚さ",
      "back": "thickness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボールペン",
      "back": "ballpoint pen"
    },
    {
      "front": "迫る",
      "back": "close in on, approach"
    },
    {
      "front": "伸びる",
      "back": "stretch, grow"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ越す",
      "back": "move, relocate"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ越し",
      "back": "moving (house)"
    },
    {
      "front": "越える",
      "back": "go over, go across"
    },
    {
      "front": "失敗",
      "back": "failure, mistake"
    },
    {
      "front": "失礼",
      "back": "rudeness, to excuse oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "お礼",
      "back": "thanks, gratitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "すいか",
      "back": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "front": "謝る",
      "back": "apologize"
    },
    {
      "front": "優しい",
      "back": "gentle, kind"
    },
    {
      "front": "誘う",
      "back": "invite, ask out"
    },
    {
      "front": "怒る",
      "back": "get angry, scold"
    },
    {
      "front": "そば",
      "back": "buckwheat noodles"
    },
    {
      "front": "出身",
      "back": "come from, origin"
    },
    {
      "front": "独身",
      "back": "single, unmarried"
    },
    {
      "front": "紹介",
      "back": "introduction"
    },
    {
      "front": "招待",
      "back": "invitation"
    },
    {
      "front": "招く",
      "back": "invite"
    },
    {
      "front": "のり",
      "back": "glue, starch"
    },
    {
      "front": "夫",
      "back": "husband"
    },
    {
      "front": "夫婦",
      "back": "husband and wife, married couple"
    },
    {
      "front": "妻",
      "back": "(speaker's) wife"
    },
    {
      "front": "バスケットボール",
      "back": "basketball"
    },
    {
      "front": "奥さん",
      "back": "(someone else's) wife, married woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "奥",
      "back": "inner part, the back"
    },
    {
      "front": "皆様",
      "back": "everyone, ladies and gentlemen"
    },
    {
      "front": "皆さん",
      "back": "everybody, everyone"
    },
    {
      "front": "どきどき",
      "back": "feel excited, feel nervous"
    },
    {
      "front": "誰",
      "back": "who"
    },
    {
      "front": "誰か",
      "back": "someone"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛",
      "back": "love"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛する",
      "back": "love, care for"
    },
    {
      "front": "サンドイッチ",
      "back": "sandwich"
    },
    {
      "front": "延ばす",
      "back": "extend, postpone"
    },
    {
      "front": "祝日",
      "back": "holiday"
    },
    {
      "front": "お祝い",
      "back": "celebrate"
    },
    {
      "front": "にこにこ",
      "back": "smile"
    },
    {
      "front": "夢",
      "back": "dream"
    },
    {
      "front": "泣く",
      "back": "cry, weep"
    },
    {
      "front": "涙",
      "back": "tear"
    },
    {
      "front": "笑う",
      "back": "laugh, smile"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウール",
      "back": "wool"
    },
    {
      "front": "喜ぶ",
      "back": "be happy, be delighted"
    },
    {
      "front": "恥ずかしい",
      "back": "embarrassed, ashamed"
    },
    {
      "front": "迷う",
      "back": "get lost"
    },
    {
      "front": "迷惑",
      "back": "trouble, annoyance"
    },
    {
      "front": "コーラ",
      "back": "cola, coke"
    },
    {
      "front": "贈り物",
      "back": "present, gift"
    },
    {
      "front": "贈る",
      "back": "offer, give"
    },
    {
      "front": "与える",
      "back": "give"
    },
    {
      "front": "預ける",
      "back": "deposit, leave (something) with (someone)"
    },
    {
      "front": "預かる",
      "back": "take care of, keep"
    },
    {
      "front": "トイレットペーパー",
      "back": "toilet paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "燃える",
      "back": "burn, catch on fire"
    },
    {
      "front": "燃やす",
      "back": "burn (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼く",
      "back": "bake, grill"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼ける",
      "back": "burn, cook"
    },
    {
      "front": "すき焼き",
      "back": "sukiyaki"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハム",
      "back": "ham"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾杯",
      "back": "toast, drink (in celebration)"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾く",
      "back": "become dry"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾かす",
      "back": "dry (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "いちご",
      "back": "strawberry"
    },
    {
      "front": "家庭",
      "back": "home, family"
    },
    {
      "front": "庭",
      "back": "garden, yard"
    },
    {
      "front": "カレーライス",
      "back": "curry rice"
    },
    {
      "front": "桜",
      "back": "cherry tree, cherry blossom"
    },
    {
      "front": "咲く",
      "back": "bloom, blossom"
    },
    {
      "front": "吹く",
      "back": "blow, play (a wind instrument)"
    },
    {
      "front": "示す",
      "back": "show, indicate"
    },
    {
      "front": "黒板",
      "back": "blackboard"
    },
    {
      "front": "掲示板",
      "back": "notice board, bulletin board"
    },
    {
      "front": "キャッシュカード",
      "back": "cash card"
    },
    {
      "front": "草",
      "back": "grass, weed"
    },
    {
      "front": "絵",
      "back": "picture, painting"
    },
    {
      "front": "言葉",
      "back": "word, language"
    },
    {
      "front": "絵葉書",
      "back": "postcard"
    },
    {
      "front": "葉書",
      "back": "postcard"
    },
    {
      "front": "葉",
      "back": "leaf"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐらぐら",
      "back": "shaky, unstable"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼ぶ",
      "back": "call, name"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジャム",
      "back": "jam"
    },
    {
      "front": "吸う",
      "back": "inhale, suck"
    },
    {
      "front": "胸",
      "back": "chest, breast"
    },
    {
      "front": "お腹",
      "back": "stomach, belly"
    },
    {
      "front": "腰",
      "back": "waist, lower back"
    },
    {
      "front": "スリッパ",
      "back": "slippers"
    },
    {
      "front": "胃",
      "back": "stomach"
    },
    {
      "front": "血",
      "back": "blood (colloquial)"
    },
    {
      "front": "景色",
      "back": "scenery, landscape"
    },
    {
      "front": "背中",
      "back": "(one's) back"
    },
    {
      "front": "背",
      "back": "height, stature"
    },
    {
      "front": "トランプ",
      "back": "playing cards"
    },
    {
      "front": "骨",
      "back": "bone"
    },
    {
      "front": "滑る",
      "back": "slide, slip"
    },
    {
      "front": "よろしい",
      "back": "all right"
    },
    {
      "front": "折れる",
      "back": "break, snap"
    },
    {
      "front": "折る",
      "back": "break (something), fold (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "健康",
      "back": "healthy"
    },
    {
      "front": "珍しい",
      "back": "rare, scarce"
    },
    {
      "front": "カップ",
      "back": "cup"
    },
    {
      "front": "撮る",
      "back": "take (a photograph), film"
    },
    {
      "front": "再来月",
      "back": "the month after next"
    },
    {
      "front": "再来週",
      "back": "the week after next"
    },
    {
      "front": "再来年",
      "back": "the year after next"
    },
    {
      "front": "再び",
      "back": "again, a second time"
    },
    {
      "front": "スケート",
      "back": "skate, skates"
    },
    {
      "front": "平仮名",
      "back": "hiragana"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮名",
      "back": "kana"
    },
    {
      "front": "鏡",
      "back": "mirror"
    },
    {
      "front": "眼鏡",
      "back": "glasses"
    },
    {
      "front": "悲しい",
      "back": "sad"
    },
    {
      "front": "悲しむ",
      "back": "feel sad, lament"
    },
    {
      "front": "固い",
      "back": "stiff, tight"
    },
    {
      "front": "マフラー",
      "back": "scarf, muffler"
    },
    {
      "front": "手術",
      "back": "surgical operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "内容",
      "back": "content"
    },
    {
      "front": "美人",
      "back": "beautiful woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "美術館",
      "back": "art museum"
    },
    {
      "front": "美容院",
      "back": "hair salon"
    },
    {
      "front": "美しい",
      "back": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "アクセサリー",
      "back": "accessories, jewelry"
    },
    {
      "front": "免許証",
      "back": "license"
    },
    {
      "front": "許す",
      "back": "permit, forgive"
    },
    {
      "front": "あくび",
      "back": "yawn"
    },
    {
      "front": "教授",
      "back": "professor"
    },
    {
      "front": "授業",
      "back": "class session, lecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "手伝う",
      "back": "help, assist"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝言",
      "back": "message"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝える",
      "back": "convey, transmit"
    },
    {
      "front": "あめ",
      "back": "candy"
    },
    {
      "front": "鳥",
      "back": "bird, poultry"
    },
    {
      "front": "鳴る",
      "back": "sound, ring"
    },
    {
      "front": "鳴く",
      "back": "sing, cry (of animals)"
    },
    {
      "front": "なるべく",
      "back": "as...as possible, if possible"
    },
    {
      "front": "声",
      "back": "voice, sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "卵",
      "back": "egg"
    },
    {
      "front": "犬",
      "back": "dog"
    },
    {
      "front": "馬",
      "back": "horse"
    },
    {
      "front": "じっと",
      "back": "without moving, still"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒ぐ",
      "back": "make a noise, make a racket"
    },
    {
      "front": "刺身",
      "back": "sliced raw fish or meat"
    },
    {
      "front": "刺す",
      "back": "sting, stab"
    },
    {
      "front": "激しい",
      "back": "violent, intense"
    },
    {
      "front": "驚く",
      "back": "be surprised, be startled"
    },
    {
      "front": "面倒",
      "back": "troublesome, difficult"
    },
    {
      "front": "倒れる",
      "back": "fall over"
    },
    {
      "front": "倒す",
      "back": "knock down, overthrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "狭い",
      "back": "narrow, small"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピクニック",
      "back": "picnic"
    },
    {
      "front": "柔らか",
      "back": "soft, gentle"
    },
    {
      "front": "柔らかい",
      "back": "soft, gentle"
    },
    {
      "front": "出張",
      "back": "business trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ張る",
      "back": "pull, drag"
    },
    {
      "front": "緊張",
      "back": "tension, strain"
    },
    {
      "front": "頑張る",
      "back": "work hard, do one's best"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハイキング",
      "back": "hiking"
    },
    {
      "front": "突き当たる",
      "back": "run into, come to the end (of a road)"
    },
    {
      "front": "突き当たり",
      "back": "end of a street"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボーイフレンド",
      "back": "boyfriend"
    },
    {
      "front": "触る",
      "back": "touch, feel"
    },
    {
      "front": "壁",
      "back": "wall, partition"
    },
    {
      "front": "弾く",
      "back": "play (instruments)"
    },
    {
      "front": "丸い",
      "back": "round"
    },
    {
      "front": "丸",
      "back": "circle, round"
    },
    {
      "front": "イヤリング",
      "back": "earrings"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶対に",
      "back": "absolutely, definitely"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶対",
      "back": "absolutely, never"
    },
    {
      "front": "大嫌い",
      "back": "hate"
    },
    {
      "front": "機嫌",
      "back": "mood, health"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫌い",
      "back": "dislike"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫌",
      "back": "dislike"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガールフレンド",
      "back": "girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "front": "大勢",
      "back": "large numbers, a lot of (people)"
    },
    {
      "front": "姿勢",
      "back": "posture, attitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "姿",
      "back": "figure, appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐ろしい",
      "back": "terrible, awful"
    },
    {
      "front": "怖い",
      "back": "scary, be afraid"
    },
    {
      "front": "孫",
      "back": "grandchild"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふらふら",
      "back": "be dizzy, lightheaded"
    },
    {
      "front": "偉い",
      "back": "great, eminent"
    },
    {
      "front": "爪",
      "back": "nail, claw"
    },
    {
      "front": "机",
      "back": "desk"
    },
    {
      "front": "本棚",
      "back": "bookshelf, bookcase"
    },
    {
      "front": "棚",
      "back": "shelf, rack"
    },
    {
      "front": "お釣り",
      "back": "change (of money)"
    },
    {
      "front": "釣る",
      "back": "fish, catch"
    },
    {
      "front": "鍵",
      "back": "key, lock"
    },
    {
      "front": "鍋",
      "back": "pan"
    },
    {
      "front": "寿司",
      "back": "sushi"
    },
    {
      "front": "浴びる",
      "back": "take (a shower)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎらぎら",
      "back": "glaring, blinding"
    },
    {
      "front": "泥棒",
      "back": "thief, burglar"
    },
    {
      "front": "湯",
      "back": "hot water"
    },
    {
      "front": "沸く",
      "back": "boil, get loud (crowd applause etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "沸かす",
      "back": "boil (water)"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗濯機",
      "back": "washing machine, washer"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗濯",
      "back": "laundry, washing"
    },
    {
      "front": "いよいよ",
      "back": "finally, any moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "濡れる",
      "back": "get wet"
    },
    {
      "front": "渇く",
      "back": "be thirsty"
    },
    {
      "front": "虫",
      "back": "insect, bug"
    },
    {
      "front": "がらがら",
      "back": "empty"
    },
    {
      "front": "怠ける",
      "back": "be lazy, slack off"
    },
    {
      "front": "畑",
      "back": "field"
    },
    {
      "front": "自炊",
      "back": "cooking (for oneself)"
    },
    {
      "front": "炊く",
      "back": "cook (rice)"
    },
    {
      "front": "どんどん",
      "back": "quickly, rapidly"
    },
    {
      "front": "皿",
      "back": "plate, counter (for plates or helpings)"
    },
    {
      "front": "灰色",
      "back": "ash color, gray"
    },
    {
      "front": "灰皿",
      "back": "ashtray"
    },
    {
      "front": "灰",
      "back": "ashes"
    },
    {
      "front": "毛",
      "back": "hair, down"
    },
    {
      "front": "髪の毛",
      "back": "hair"
    },
    {
      "front": "髪",
      "back": "hair"
    },
    {
      "front": "肩",
      "back": "shoulder"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぺらぺら",
      "back": "fluently"
    },
    {
      "front": "舌",
      "back": "tongue"
    },
    {
      "front": "鼻",
      "back": "nose"
    },
    {
      "front": "臭い",
      "back": "stinky"
    },
    {
      "front": "臭い",
      "back": "(bad) smell"
    },
    {
      "front": "匂い",
      "back": "(pleasant) smell, odor"
    },
    {
      "front": "レインコート",
      "back": "raincoat"
    },
    {
      "front": "履く",
      "back": "put on (shoes), wear (pants, skirt)"
    },
    {
      "front": "戸",
      "back": "door"
    },
    {
      "front": "君",
      "back": "you"
    },
    {
      "front": "アイス",
      "back": "ice cream"
    },
    {
      "front": "豚肉",
      "back": "pork"
    },
    {
      "front": "豚",
      "back": "pig"
    },
    {
      "front": "鶏",
      "back": "rooster, hen"
    },
    {
      "front": "肌",
      "back": "skin"
    },
    {
      "front": "セロテープ",
      "back": "scotch tape"
    },
    {
      "front": "腕時計",
      "back": "wrist watch"
    },
    {
      "front": "腕",
      "back": "arm"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉛筆",
      "back": "pencil"
    },
    {
      "front": "本箱",
      "back": "bookcase"
    },
    {
      "front": "箱",
      "back": "box, case"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばら",
      "back": "rose"
    },
    {
      "front": "手袋",
      "back": "gloves"
    },
    {
      "front": "袋",
      "back": "bag, sack"
    },
    {
      "front": "財布",
      "back": "purse, wallet"
    },
    {
      "front": "布団",
      "back": "Japanese-style padded mattress"
    },
    {
      "front": "毛布",
      "back": "blanket"
    },
    {
      "front": "ねずみ",
      "back": "rat, mouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "小包",
      "back": "parcel, package"
    },
    {
      "front": "包む",
      "back": "wrap, pack"
    },
    {
      "front": "抱える",
      "back": "hold in one's arms"
    },
    {
      "front": "しっかり",
      "back": "mature, responsible"
    },
    {
      "front": "飾る",
      "back": "decorate"
    },
    {
      "front": "手帳",
      "back": "notebook"
    },
    {
      "front": "電話帳",
      "back": "telephone book"
    },
    {
      "front": "眠い",
      "back": "sleepy"
    },
    {
      "front": "眠る",
      "back": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "すっかり",
      "back": "all, completely"
    },
    {
      "front": "眺める",
      "back": "look out, gaze"
    },
    {
      "front": "封筒",
      "back": "envelope"
    },
    {
      "front": "計算",
      "back": "calculation"
    },
    {
      "front": "出掛ける",
      "back": "go out, leave home"
    },
    {
      "front": "掛け算",
      "back": "multiplication"
    },
    {
      "front": "掛ける",
      "back": "hang, put on"
    },
    {
      "front": "掛かる",
      "back": "hang"
    },
    {
      "front": "エンジン",
      "back": "engine"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドレス",
      "back": "dress"
    },
    {
      "front": "除く",
      "back": "remove, exclude"
    },
    {
      "front": "掃除機",
      "back": "vacuum cleaner"
    },
    {
      "front": "掃除",
      "back": "cleaning"
    },
    {
      "front": "掃く",
      "back": "sweep"
    },
    {
      "front": "握手",
      "back": "handshake"
    },
    {
      "front": "握る",
      "back": "grasp, grip, hold"
    },
    {
      "front": "からから",
      "back": "very thirsty, very dry"
    },
    {
      "front": "迎える",
      "back": "welcome, greet"
    },
    {
      "front": "歓迎",
      "back": "welcome"
    },
    {
      "front": "あんまり",
      "back": "(not) that much, (not) so much"
    },
    {
      "front": "幾ら",
      "back": "how much"
    },
    {
      "front": "僕",
      "back": "I, me (usually used by young males)"
    },
    {
      "front": "穴",
      "back": "hole"
    },
    {
      "front": "寂しい",
      "back": "lonely, desolate, sad"
    },
    {
      "front": "いきなり",
      "back": "all of a sudden, suddenly"
    },
    {
      "front": "丁寧",
      "back": "polite, careful"
    },
    {
      "front": "懐かしい",
      "back": "fondly-remembered, long-forgotten"
    },
    {
      "front": "怪我",
      "back": "injury"
    },
    {
      "front": "怪しい",
      "back": "suspicious, dubious"
    },
    {
      "front": "我慢",
      "back": "patience, endurance"
    },
    {
      "front": "ざあざあ",
      "back": "pouring"
    },
    {
      "front": "稼ぐ",
      "back": "earn, make money"
    },
    {
      "front": "とんとん",
      "back": "tapping, patting"
    },
    {
      "front": "隠れる",
      "back": "hide"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつ頃",
      "back": "about when, about what time"
    },
    {
      "front": "頃",
      "back": "time"
    },
    {
      "front": "尋ねる",
      "back": "inquire, ask"
    },
    {
      "front": "パーセント",
      "back": "percent"
    },
    {
      "front": "駄目",
      "back": "no good"
    },
    {
      "front": "無駄",
      "back": "pointless, waste"
    },
    {
      "front": "缶詰",
      "back": "canned food"
    },
    {
      "front": "缶",
      "back": "can, tin"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひも",
      "back": "laces, string"
    },
    {
      "front": "納豆",
      "back": "fermented soybeans"
    },
    {
      "front": "豆腐",
      "back": "tofu"
    },
    {
      "front": "腐る",
      "back": "rot, go bad"
    },
    {
      "front": "床屋",
      "back": "barber, barbershop"
    },
    {
      "front": "床",
      "back": "floor"
    },
    {
      "front": "まく",
      "back": "scatter, sprinkle"
    },
    {
      "front": "畳",
      "back": "straw mat"
    },
    {
      "front": "畳む",
      "back": "fold, shut, close"
    },
    {
      "front": "汗",
      "back": "sweat"
    },
    {
      "front": "トレーニング",
      "back": "training, workout"
    },
    {
      "front": "敬語",
      "back": "polite speech"
    },
    {
      "front": "尊敬",
      "back": "respect, esteem"
    },
    {
      "front": "敷く",
      "back": "lay, spread"
    },
    {
      "front": "雷",
      "back": "thunder, lightning"
    },
    {
      "front": "零",
      "back": "zero"
    },
    {
      "front": "踊る",
      "back": "dance"
    },
    {
      "front": "踏切",
      "back": "railroad crossing"
    },
    {
      "front": "踏む",
      "back": "step on, tread on"
    },
    {
      "front": "マーケット",
      "back": "market"
    },
    {
      "front": "蹴る",
      "back": "kick"
    },
    {
      "front": "猫",
      "back": "cat"
    },
    {
      "front": "大丈夫",
      "back": "all right, OK"
    },
    {
      "front": "丈夫",
      "back": "healthy, sturdy"
    },
    {
      "front": "スケジュール",
      "back": "schedule"
    },
    {
      "front": "祖父",
      "back": "grandfather"
    },
    {
      "front": "祖母",
      "back": "grandmother"
    },
    {
      "front": "コック",
      "back": "cook, chef"
    },
    {
      "front": "風邪",
      "back": "cold (illness)"
    },
    {
      "front": "風邪薬",
      "back": "cold medicine"
    },
    {
      "front": "邪魔",
      "back": "disturbance, blocking"
    },
    {
      "front": "風呂屋",
      "back": "bathhouse, public bath"
    },
    {
      "front": "風呂",
      "back": "bath"
    },
    {
      "front": "ブラシ",
      "back": "brush"
    },
    {
      "front": "紫",
      "back": "purple"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨",
      "back": "rain"
    },
    {
      "front": "干す",
      "back": "hang (something) out to dry"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅雨",
      "back": "rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅干し",
      "back": "pickled plum"
    },
    {
      "front": "まとも",
      "back": "sane, reasonable"
    },
    {
      "front": "桃",
      "back": "peach"
    },
    {
      "front": "遭う",
      "back": "meet, encounter, get caught in"
    },
    {
      "front": "枕",
      "back": "pillow"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴったり",
      "back": "exactly right, perfect"
    },
    {
      "front": "嘘",
      "back": "lie"
    },
    {
      "front": "噂",
      "back": "gossip, rumor"
    },
    {
      "front": "叱る",
      "back": "scold, reprimand"
    },
    {
      "front": "田舎",
      "back": "hometown, countryside"
    },
    {
      "front": "より",
      "back": "more, further"
    },
    {
      "front": "傘",
      "back": "umbrella, parasol"
    },
    {
      "front": "お嬢さん",
      "back": "young lady, daughter"
    },
    {
      "front": "賑やか",
      "back": "lively, exciting"
    },
    {
      "front": "蚊",
      "back": "mosquito"
    },
    {
      "front": "もったいない",
      "back": "wasteful, a shame"
    },
    {
      "front": "拭く",
      "back": "wipe, dry"
    },
    {
      "front": "挨拶",
      "back": "greet, greeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "諦める",
      "back": "abandon, give up"
    },
    {
      "front": "巻く",
      "back": "roll up, wrap"
    },
    {
      "front": "たっぷり",
      "back": "fully, amply"
    },
    {
      "front": "靴下",
      "back": "socks"
    },
    {
      "front": "靴",
      "back": "shoes"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯磨き",
      "back": "brushing one's teeth"
    },
    {
      "front": "磨く",
      "back": "polish, grind"
    },
    {
      "front": "なお",
      "back": "still, in addition"
    },
    {
      "front": "瓶",
      "back": "bottle"
    },
    {
      "front": "褒める",
      "back": "praise, compliment"
    },
    {
      "front": "半袖",
      "back": "short sleeves"
    },
    {
      "front": "長袖",
      "back": "long sleeves"
    },
    {
      "front": "袖",
      "back": "sleeve"
    },
    {
      "front": "サイト",
      "back": "website"
    },
    {
      "front": "凄い",
      "back": "great, incredible"
    },
    {
      "front": "剃る",
      "back": "shave"
    },
    {
      "front": "喧嘩",
      "back": "fight, argument"
    },
    {
      "front": "叩く",
      "back": "tap, hit"
    },
    {
      "front": "マイナス",
      "back": "minus, below zero"
    },
    {
      "front": "噛む",
      "back": "bite, chew"
    },
    {
      "front": "姪",
      "back": "niece"
    },
    {
      "front": "嬉しい",
      "back": "happy, glad"
    },
    {
      "front": "膝",
      "back": "knee"
    },
    {
      "front": "サイン",
      "back": "signature, autograph"
    },
    {
      "front": "肘",
      "back": "elbow"
    },
    {
      "front": "痩せる",
      "back": "lose weight, become thin"
    },
    {
      "front": "襖",
      "back": "sliding door"
    },
    {
      "front": "箸",
      "back": "chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "front": "鞄",
      "back": "bag, handbag"
    },
    {
      "front": "一斉に",
      "back": "all together, all at once"
    },
    {
      "front": "一旦",
      "back": "once, one time"
    },
    {
      "front": "どうせ",
      "back": "anyway"
    },
    {
      "front": "日にち",
      "back": "date"
    },
    {
      "front": "日",
      "back": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "日米",
      "back": "Japan and the U.S."
    },
    {
      "front": "日韓",
      "back": "Japan and (South) Korea"
    },
    {
      "front": "あれこれ",
      "back": "this and that, one thing or another"
    },
    {
      "front": "三日月",
      "back": "crescent moon"
    },
    {
      "front": "月日",
      "back": "time, days"
    },
    {
      "front": "金もうけ",
      "back": "moneymaking"
    },
    {
      "front": "金融",
      "back": "finance"
    },
    {
      "front": "とうとう",
      "back": "at last, finally"
    },
    {
      "front": "年月日",
      "back": "date"
    },
    {
      "front": "年月",
      "back": "time, years"
    },
    {
      "front": "年々",
      "back": "year by year"
    },
    {
      "front": "年賀",
      "back": "New Year's celebration, New Year's gift"
    },
    {
      "front": "さっぱり",
      "back": "completely not"
    },
    {
      "front": "何十",
      "back": "several tens"
    },
    {
      "front": "何百",
      "back": "several hundred, hundreds"
    },
    {
      "front": "何千",
      "back": "several thousand, thousands"
    },
    {
      "front": "何で",
      "back": "why, what for"
    },
    {
      "front": "何となく",
      "back": "for some reason"
    },
    {
      "front": "何べん",
      "back": "(how) many times"
    },
    {
      "front": "ついで",
      "back": "on the way, to take the opportunity"
    },
    {
      "front": "先日",
      "back": "the other day, a few days ago"
    },
    {
      "front": "先ほど",
      "back": "some time ago, a little while ago"
    },
    {
      "front": "すっきり",
      "back": "refreshed"
    },
    {
      "front": "今日",
      "back": "these days"
    },
    {
      "front": "今ごろ",
      "back": "by now, at this time"
    },
    {
      "front": "今にも",
      "back": "at any moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "今に",
      "back": "before long, someday"
    },
    {
      "front": "来日",
      "back": "visit to Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "やって来る",
      "back": "come all the way"
    },
    {
      "front": "とんでもない",
      "back": "unthinkable, outrageous"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き来",
      "back": "comings and goings"
    },
    {
      "front": "行う",
      "back": "do, carry out"
    },
    {
      "front": "日帰り",
      "back": "a day trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰す",
      "back": "send (someone) home"
    },
    {
      "front": "大げさ",
      "back": "exaggerated"
    },
    {
      "front": "大晦日",
      "back": "new year's eve"
    },
    {
      "front": "大",
      "back": "big, large size"
    },
    {
      "front": "大いに",
      "back": "very, to the great extent"
    },
    {
      "front": "大して",
      "back": "(not) very, (not that) much"
    },
    {
      "front": "大雪",
      "back": "heavy snow"
    },
    {
      "front": "巨大",
      "back": "huge, gigantic"
    },
    {
      "front": "偉大",
      "back": "great, mighty"
    },
    {
      "front": "テント",
      "back": "tent"
    },
    {
      "front": "日中",
      "back": "Japan and China"
    },
    {
      "front": "水中",
      "back": "in water, underwater"
    },
    {
      "front": "中年",
      "back": "middle age"
    },
    {
      "front": "中",
      "back": "middle, medium size"
    },
    {
      "front": "夢中",
      "back": "be absorbed, be engrossed"
    },
    {
      "front": "中央",
      "back": "center, central position or role"
    },
    {
      "front": "ナイロン",
      "back": "nylon"
    },
    {
      "front": "大小",
      "back": "size"
    },
    {
      "front": "小",
      "back": "small size"
    },
    {
      "front": "多少",
      "back": "somewhat, to some extent"
    },
    {
      "front": "上",
      "back": "upper, superior"
    },
    {
      "front": "上",
      "back": "people in authority, government"
    },
    {
      "front": "召し上がる",
      "back": "eat (honorific)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハンドバッグ",
      "back": "handbag"
    },
    {
      "front": "下水",
      "back": "sewerage, drainage"
    },
    {
      "front": "上下",
      "back": "top and bottom (Chinese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶら下がる",
      "back": "hang down, dangle"
    },
    {
      "front": "下",
      "back": "under (someone's) supervision"
    },
    {
      "front": "下さる",
      "back": "give (honorific)"
    },
    {
      "front": "下",
      "back": "lower, bottom"
    },
    {
      "front": "下宿",
      "back": "lodging, boarding house"
    },
    {
      "front": "零下",
      "back": "below zero"
    },
    {
      "front": "アイロン",
      "back": "iron"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラッシュアワー",
      "back": "rush hour"
    },
    {
      "front": "四方",
      "back": "all directions"
    },
    {
      "front": "行方",
      "back": "one's whereabouts"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり方",
      "back": "way of doing"
    },
    {
      "front": "方々",
      "back": "people (polite)"
    },
    {
      "front": "方々",
      "back": "all directions, everywhere"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウィスキー",
      "back": "whisky"
    },
    {
      "front": "日の入り",
      "back": "sunset"
    },
    {
      "front": "一人一人",
      "back": "each and every person"
    },
    {
      "front": "日の出",
      "back": "sunrise"
    },
    {
      "front": "出来上がる",
      "back": "be completed, be finished"
    },
    {
      "front": "出来上がり",
      "back": "completion, result"
    },
    {
      "front": "人出",
      "back": "turnout, crowd"
    },
    {
      "front": "出入り",
      "back": "coming and going"
    },
    {
      "front": "出荷",
      "back": "shipping"
    },
    {
      "front": "シャープペンシル",
      "back": "mechanical pencil"
    },
    {
      "front": "外出",
      "back": "outing, going out"
    },
    {
      "front": "外す",
      "back": "remove (something), take off"
    },
    {
      "front": "外れる",
      "back": "come off"
    },
    {
      "front": "外れ",
      "back": "blank, losing"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンサート",
      "back": "concert"
    },
    {
      "front": "内",
      "back": "inside"
    },
    {
      "front": "本日",
      "back": "today"
    },
    {
      "front": "本年",
      "back": "this year"
    },
    {
      "front": "本来",
      "back": "originally, (in) true self"
    },
    {
      "front": "本人",
      "back": "the person himself, the said person"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガソリン",
      "back": "gasoline"
    },
    {
      "front": "一休み",
      "back": "rest, break"
    },
    {
      "front": "週休",
      "back": "weekly holiday"
    },
    {
      "front": "休暇",
      "back": "holiday, vacation"
    },
    {
      "front": "一体",
      "back": "what on earth"
    },
    {
      "front": "大体",
      "back": "about, anyway"
    },
    {
      "front": "パンツ",
      "back": "pants, trousers"
    },
    {
      "front": "火力",
      "back": "fire power"
    },
    {
      "front": "水力",
      "back": "water power, hydraulic power"
    },
    {
      "front": "入力",
      "back": "input, entry"
    },
    {
      "front": "出力",
      "back": "output"
    },
    {
      "front": "魅力",
      "back": "charm, attraction"
    },
    {
      "front": "そっくり",
      "back": "almost identical"
    },
    {
      "front": "目上",
      "back": "one's superiors, one's seniors"
    },
    {
      "front": "目下",
      "back": "now, at present"
    },
    {
      "front": "目下",
      "back": "one's juniors"
    },
    {
      "front": "お目にかかる",
      "back": "meet (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一口",
      "back": "mouthful, bite"
    },
    {
      "front": "人口",
      "back": "population"
    },
    {
      "front": "窓口",
      "back": "window, contact"
    },
    {
      "front": "河口",
      "back": "river mouth, estuary"
    },
    {
      "front": "口喧嘩",
      "back": "quarrel"
    },
    {
      "front": "大手",
      "back": "major company"
    },
    {
      "front": "手入れ",
      "back": "care, repair"
    },
    {
      "front": "手のひら",
      "back": "palm"
    },
    {
      "front": "しつこい",
      "back": "persistent"
    },
    {
      "front": "足下",
      "back": "step, under foot"
    },
    {
      "front": "手足",
      "back": "hands and feet, limbs"
    },
    {
      "front": "そっと",
      "back": "softly, gently"
    },
    {
      "front": "火山",
      "back": "volcano"
    },
    {
      "front": "空中",
      "back": "in the air, in the sky"
    },
    {
      "front": "空手",
      "back": "karate"
    },
    {
      "front": "空っぽ",
      "back": "empty"
    },
    {
      "front": "空",
      "back": "emptiness, hollow"
    },
    {
      "front": "空き",
      "back": "vacancy, free time"
    },
    {
      "front": "空ける",
      "back": "vacate, clear out"
    },
    {
      "front": "こっそり",
      "back": "secretly"
    },
    {
      "front": "海水",
      "back": "seawater"
    },
    {
      "front": "海上",
      "back": "on the sea, seaborne"
    },
    {
      "front": "宝石",
      "back": "gem, jewel"
    },
    {
      "front": "石炭",
      "back": "coal"
    },
    {
      "front": "うっかり",
      "back": "carelessly, accidentally"
    },
    {
      "front": "田んぼ",
      "back": "rice field"
    },
    {
      "front": "田",
      "back": "rice field, rice paddy"
    },
    {
      "front": "田畑",
      "back": "fields and rice paddies"
    },
    {
      "front": "花火",
      "back": "fireworks"
    },
    {
      "front": "花婿",
      "back": "bridegroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "花瓶",
      "back": "flower vase"
    },
    {
      "front": "森林",
      "back": "forest, woodland"
    },
    {
      "front": "男らしい",
      "back": "manly, masculine"
    },
    {
      "front": "男女",
      "back": "men and women"
    },
    {
      "front": "女らしい",
      "back": "womanly, feminine"
    },
    {
      "front": "女房",
      "back": "wife"
    },
    {
      "front": "がっかり",
      "back": "feel disappointed"
    },
    {
      "front": "男子",
      "back": "boy (usually over the age of 7), young man"
    },
    {
      "front": "女子",
      "back": "woman, girl"
    },
    {
      "front": "子孫",
      "back": "descendant, offspring"
    },
    {
      "front": "双子",
      "back": "twins"
    },
    {
      "front": "餃子",
      "back": "Chinese dumpling"
    },
    {
      "front": "好み",
      "back": "taste, preference"
    },
    {
      "front": "好む",
      "back": "like, be fond of"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぼんやり",
      "back": "vacantly, absent-mindedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "友人",
      "back": "friend"
    },
    {
      "front": "友",
      "back": "friend, companion"
    },
    {
      "front": "一家",
      "back": "household, family"
    },
    {
      "front": "大家",
      "back": "landlord"
    },
    {
      "front": "元日",
      "back": "New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "front": "お中元",
      "back": "mid-year gift, summer gift"
    },
    {
      "front": "元",
      "back": "origin, former"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちっとも",
      "back": "(not) at all (casual)"
    },
    {
      "front": "小川",
      "back": "stream, brook"
    },
    {
      "front": "天の川",
      "back": "Milky Way"
    },
    {
      "front": "天",
      "back": "sky, Heaven"
    },
    {
      "front": "天皇",
      "back": "emperor"
    },
    {
      "front": "わがまま",
      "back": "selfish"
    },
    {
      "front": "気分",
      "back": "feeling, mood"
    },
    {
      "front": "気体",
      "back": "gas"
    },
    {
      "front": "気力",
      "back": "energy, vitality"
    },
    {
      "front": "陽気",
      "back": "cheerful, merry"
    },
    {
      "front": "分析",
      "back": "analysis"
    },
    {
      "front": "まあまあ",
      "back": "now now, well well"
    },
    {
      "front": "大雨",
      "back": "heavy rain"
    },
    {
      "front": "小雨",
      "back": "drizzle"
    },
    {
      "front": "青年",
      "back": "young man"
    },
    {
      "front": "青空",
      "back": "blue sky"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふざける",
      "back": "mess around, fool around"
    },
    {
      "front": "明日",
      "back": "tomorrow (rather formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "明日",
      "back": "tomorrow (very formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "明け方",
      "back": "dawn, near daybreak"
    },
    {
      "front": "明ける",
      "back": "dawn, end"
    },
    {
      "front": "明かり",
      "back": "light"
    },
    {
      "front": "とっくに",
      "back": "long ago, already"
    },
    {
      "front": "一昨日",
      "back": "the day before yesterday (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一昨年",
      "back": "the year before last (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨日",
      "back": "yesterday (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "東西",
      "back": "east and west"
    },
    {
      "front": "南東",
      "back": "southeast"
    },
    {
      "front": "南西",
      "back": "southwest"
    },
    {
      "front": "北東",
      "back": "northeast"
    },
    {
      "front": "北西",
      "back": "northwest"
    },
    {
      "front": "南北",
      "back": "north and south"
    },
    {
      "front": "一向に",
      "back": "absolutely (not) (formal, mainly in written)"
    },
    {
      "front": "向ける",
      "back": "turn toward, point at"
    },
    {
      "front": "向かい",
      "back": "opposite side"
    },
    {
      "front": "あいにく",
      "back": "unfortunately"
    },
    {
      "front": "入門",
      "back": "admission, introduction"
    },
    {
      "front": "門",
      "back": "gate, entrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "開ける",
      "back": "develop, open up"
    },
    {
      "front": "開き",
      "back": "opening"
    },
    {
      "front": "聞き手",
      "back": "listener, audience"
    },
    {
      "front": "聞かす",
      "back": "let (someone) hear, tell (a story etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "うろうろ",
      "back": "wander, hover around"
    },
    {
      "front": "中間",
      "back": "middle, between"
    },
    {
      "front": "手間",
      "back": "time and effort"
    },
    {
      "front": "空間",
      "back": "space"
    },
    {
      "front": "客間",
      "back": "guest room"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつの間にか",
      "back": "without noticing/realizing"
    },
    {
      "front": "間もなく",
      "back": "soon, in a short time"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつの間に",
      "back": "when"
    },
    {
      "front": "間",
      "back": "interval, time (in between)"
    },
    {
      "front": "間",
      "back": "interval, meantime"
    },
    {
      "front": "間隔",
      "back": "interval, space"
    },
    {
      "front": "かじる",
      "back": "nibble, bite"
    },
    {
      "front": "円高",
      "back": "strong yen"
    },
    {
      "front": "高める",
      "back": "heighten (something), improve"
    },
    {
      "front": "せっせと",
      "back": "diligently, hard"
    },
    {
      "front": "低下",
      "back": "falling, lowering"
    },
    {
      "front": "低",
      "back": "low"
    },
    {
      "front": "最中",
      "back": "in the middle of, during"
    },
    {
      "front": "最小",
      "back": "the smallest, minimum"
    },
    {
      "front": "最上",
      "back": "best, highest"
    },
    {
      "front": "最高",
      "back": "supreme, best"
    },
    {
      "front": "最低",
      "back": "lowest, worst"
    },
    {
      "front": "最も",
      "back": "the most"
    },
    {
      "front": "からかう",
      "back": "make fun of, tease"
    },
    {
      "front": "初日",
      "back": "first day, opening day"
    },
    {
      "front": "月初め",
      "back": "the beginning of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "初詣",
      "back": "first shrine visit of the new year"
    },
    {
      "front": "ワンピース",
      "back": "dress"
    },
    {
      "front": "前年",
      "back": "the year before"
    },
    {
      "front": "前方",
      "back": "front, ahead"
    },
    {
      "front": "人前",
      "back": "in front of people"
    },
    {
      "front": "出前",
      "back": "home delivery of food"
    },
    {
      "front": "手前",
      "back": "in front"
    },
    {
      "front": "前向き",
      "back": "facing forward, positive"
    },
    {
      "front": "お前",
      "back": "you (vulgar language)"
    },
    {
      "front": "シーツ",
      "back": "bed sheet"
    },
    {
      "front": "後方",
      "back": "back, rear"
    },
    {
      "front": "後ろ向き",
      "back": "facing backward"
    },
    {
      "front": "前後",
      "back": "around, order"
    },
    {
      "front": "後輩",
      "back": "one's junior"
    },
    {
      "front": "フライパン",
      "back": "frying pan"
    },
    {
      "front": "前半",
      "back": "first half"
    },
    {
      "front": "後半",
      "back": "latter half, second half"
    },
    {
      "front": "半ば",
      "back": "middle, halfway"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝日",
      "back": "morning sun"
    },
    {
      "front": "明朝",
      "back": "tomorrow morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "晩年",
      "back": "one's later years"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨晩",
      "back": "last night, last evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴかぴか",
      "back": "shiny, glittering"
    },
    {
      "front": "月夜",
      "back": "moonlit night"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜空",
      "back": "night sky"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜明け",
      "back": "dawn, daybreak"
    },
    {
      "front": "昨夜",
      "back": "last night, last evening (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜間",
      "back": "night, nighttime"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜",
      "back": "night, evening"
    },
    {
      "front": "七夕",
      "back": "The Star Festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕日",
      "back": "setting sun"
    },
    {
      "front": "外食",
      "back": "eating out, dining out"
    },
    {
      "front": "食パン",
      "back": "loaf of bread"
    },
    {
      "front": "食う",
      "back": "eat (vulgar language)"
    },
    {
      "front": "乞食",
      "back": "beggar"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゆでる",
      "back": "boil"
    },
    {
      "front": "飯",
      "back": "cooked rice, meal (vulgar language)"
    },
    {
      "front": "一見",
      "back": "at a glance"
    },
    {
      "front": "月見",
      "back": "moon viewing"
    },
    {
      "front": "見上げる",
      "back": "look up"
    },
    {
      "front": "見下ろす",
      "back": "look down"
    },
    {
      "front": "見出し",
      "back": "headline, heading"
    },
    {
      "front": "見本",
      "back": "sample, model"
    },
    {
      "front": "見かけ",
      "back": "looks, appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "見つめる",
      "back": "stare, gaze"
    },
    {
      "front": "できるだけ",
      "back": "as (much) as possible"
    },
    {
      "front": "方言",
      "back": "dialect"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い出す",
      "back": "bring up, say"
    },
    {
      "front": "言づける",
      "back": "leave a message"
    },
    {
      "front": "外来語",
      "back": "loanword, foreign word"
    },
    {
      "front": "言語",
      "back": "language"
    },
    {
      "front": "語る",
      "back": "tell, talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "文明",
      "back": "civilization, culture"
    },
    {
      "front": "英文",
      "back": "English sentence"
    },
    {
      "front": "文",
      "back": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "front": "いつまでも",
      "back": "forever"
    },
    {
      "front": "下書き",
      "back": "draft"
    },
    {
      "front": "後書き",
      "back": "afterword"
    },
    {
      "front": "読み書き",
      "back": "reading and writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "目覚まし",
      "back": "waking up"
    },
    {
      "front": "目覚ましい",
      "back": "remarkable, marvelous"
    },
    {
      "front": "見覚え",
      "back": "recognition, remembrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "覚悟",
      "back": "readiness, resolution"
    },
    {
      "front": "おやつ",
      "back": "afternoon snack, refreshment"
    },
    {
      "front": "開会",
      "back": "opening, start (of a meeting etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉会",
      "back": "closing"
    },
    {
      "front": "会",
      "back": "meeting, association"
    },
    {
      "front": "間に合わせる",
      "back": "make do"
    },
    {
      "front": "合わせる",
      "back": "match (something), adapt (oneself)"
    },
    {
      "front": "隣り合う",
      "back": "adjoin, be next door to each other"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶつぶつ",
      "back": "in a mutter, mumble"
    },
    {
      "front": "社会人",
      "back": "working member of society"
    },
    {
      "front": "入社",
      "back": "joining a company"
    },
    {
      "front": "本社",
      "back": "head office, headquarters"
    },
    {
      "front": "すっと",
      "back": "(feel) refreshed, satisfied"
    },
    {
      "front": "一員",
      "back": "member"
    },
    {
      "front": "会員",
      "back": "member"
    },
    {
      "front": "満足",
      "back": "satisfaction, contentment"
    },
    {
      "front": "満員",
      "back": "full to capacity"
    },
    {
      "front": "満ちる",
      "back": "become full, wax"
    },
    {
      "front": "にっこり",
      "back": "smiling"
    },
    {
      "front": "出来事",
      "back": "occurrence, incident"
    },
    {
      "front": "行事",
      "back": "event"
    },
    {
      "front": "人事",
      "back": "human affairs, personnel affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "家事",
      "back": "housework, domestic duties"
    },
    {
      "front": "見事",
      "back": "splendid, admirable"
    },
    {
      "front": "事",
      "back": "thing, incident"
    },
    {
      "front": "炊事",
      "back": "cooking (for oneself or one's family)"
    },
    {
      "front": "けち",
      "back": "stingy, miser"
    },
    {
      "front": "大工",
      "back": "carpenter"
    },
    {
      "front": "人工",
      "back": "artificial"
    },
    {
      "front": "入場",
      "back": "entrance, admission"
    },
    {
      "front": "出場",
      "back": "participation"
    },
    {
      "front": "会場",
      "back": "venue, site (hall etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "工場",
      "back": "factory, plant"
    },
    {
      "front": "場",
      "back": "occasion, situation"
    },
    {
      "front": "牧場",
      "back": "stock farm, ranch"
    },
    {
      "front": "だらしない",
      "back": "untidy, sloppy"
    },
    {
      "front": "電力",
      "back": "electric power, electricity"
    },
    {
      "front": "電子",
      "back": "electron, electronic"
    },
    {
      "front": "下車",
      "back": "getting off"
    },
    {
      "front": "車内",
      "back": "inside a vehicle or a train"
    },
    {
      "front": "車輪",
      "back": "wheel"
    },
    {
      "front": "駐車",
      "back": "parking"
    },
    {
      "front": "汽車",
      "back": "train"
    },
    {
      "front": "車掌",
      "back": "train conductor"
    },
    {
      "front": "車椅子",
      "back": "wheelchair"
    },
    {
      "front": "外交",
      "back": "diplomacy, foreign relations"
    },
    {
      "front": "交じる",
      "back": "be mingled, be mixed"
    },
    {
      "front": "交ぜる",
      "back": "mix (things distinguishable)"
    },
    {
      "front": "交ざる",
      "back": "mix, mingle with"
    },
    {
      "front": "のろのろ",
      "back": "slowly"
    },
    {
      "front": "一通り",
      "back": "briefly, once over"
    },
    {
      "front": "通行",
      "back": "passage, traffic"
    },
    {
      "front": "大通り",
      "back": "main street"
    },
    {
      "front": "人通り",
      "back": "traffic"
    },
    {
      "front": "交通",
      "back": "traffic, transportation"
    },
    {
      "front": "通じる",
      "back": "pass, communicate with"
    },
    {
      "front": "通す",
      "back": "pass (someone/something) through"
    },
    {
      "front": "通帳",
      "back": "bankbook, passbook"
    },
    {
      "front": "さすが",
      "back": "just as expected, true to one's reputation"
    },
    {
      "front": "書道",
      "back": "Japanese calligraphy"
    },
    {
      "front": "道徳",
      "back": "morality, ethic"
    },
    {
      "front": "通路",
      "back": "pathway, aisle"
    },
    {
      "front": "うさぎ",
      "back": "rabbit, hare"
    },
    {
      "front": "地上",
      "back": "above ground"
    },
    {
      "front": "地下道",
      "back": "underground passage"
    },
    {
      "front": "地方",
      "back": "district, region"
    },
    {
      "front": "空き地",
      "back": "unoccupied land, vacant lot"
    },
    {
      "front": "地",
      "back": "ground, place"
    },
    {
      "front": "図書",
      "back": "books"
    },
    {
      "front": "合図",
      "back": "signal, sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "図",
      "back": "figure, diagram"
    },
    {
      "front": "他人",
      "back": "other people, stranger"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎっしり",
      "back": "tightly, closely"
    },
    {
      "front": "通行止め",
      "back": "road closed"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き止まり",
      "back": "dead end"
    },
    {
      "front": "初歩",
      "back": "beginning, basic"
    },
    {
      "front": "うがい",
      "back": "gargling"
    },
    {
      "front": "一度に",
      "back": "at a time, at once"
    },
    {
      "front": "二度と",
      "back": "never again"
    },
    {
      "front": "毎度",
      "back": "every time"
    },
    {
      "front": "高度",
      "back": "high degree"
    },
    {
      "front": "この度",
      "back": "this occasion"
    },
    {
      "front": "震度",
      "back": "seismic intensity"
    },
    {
      "front": "間近",
      "back": "up close, close at hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "近道",
      "back": "shortcut"
    },
    {
      "front": "近頃",
      "back": "recently, these days"
    },
    {
      "front": "かく",
      "back": "scratch"
    },
    {
      "front": "駅前",
      "back": "in front of the station"
    },
    {
      "front": "長年",
      "back": "many years, long time"
    },
    {
      "front": "長話",
      "back": "long conversation, long talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "駅長",
      "back": "stationmaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "長らく",
      "back": "for a long time"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずらり",
      "back": "lining up neatly"
    },
    {
      "front": "広場",
      "back": "open space, plaza"
    },
    {
      "front": "広げる",
      "back": "spread (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "広める",
      "back": "spread (information etc.), make (something) known"
    },
    {
      "front": "背広",
      "back": "business suit, business jacket"
    },
    {
      "front": "しゃがむ",
      "back": "squat down"
    },
    {
      "front": "全力",
      "back": "all one's might, full capacity"
    },
    {
      "front": "全員",
      "back": "all members, entire staff"
    },
    {
      "front": "全て",
      "back": "all, everything"
    },
    {
      "front": "大部分",
      "back": "most, large part"
    },
    {
      "front": "外部",
      "back": "outside, outer"
    },
    {
      "front": "本部",
      "back": "head office, headquarters"
    },
    {
      "front": "部長",
      "back": "department head"
    },
    {
      "front": "土",
      "back": "soil, ground"
    },
    {
      "front": "大国",
      "back": "world power, large country"
    },
    {
      "front": "入国",
      "back": "entry into a country, immigration"
    },
    {
      "front": "出国",
      "back": "departure (from a country)"
    },
    {
      "front": "国外",
      "back": "outside the country, abroad"
    },
    {
      "front": "本国",
      "back": "one's native country, home country"
    },
    {
      "front": "国家",
      "back": "state, nation"
    },
    {
      "front": "国語",
      "back": "national language, Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "国会",
      "back": "National Diet, parliament"
    },
    {
      "front": "国道",
      "back": "national highway"
    },
    {
      "front": "全国",
      "back": "the whole country"
    },
    {
      "front": "国々",
      "back": "nations, countries"
    },
    {
      "front": "諸国",
      "back": "various countries"
    },
    {
      "front": "世の中",
      "back": "the world, society"
    },
    {
      "front": "中世",
      "back": "Middle Ages, medieval age"
    },
    {
      "front": "世間",
      "back": "world, the public"
    },
    {
      "front": "世話",
      "back": "care, taking care of"
    },
    {
      "front": "青白い",
      "back": "pale"
    },
    {
      "front": "明白",
      "back": "obvious, evident"
    },
    {
      "front": "白菜",
      "back": "Chinese cabbage"
    },
    {
      "front": "白髪",
      "back": "white hair, gray hair"
    },
    {
      "front": "ケース",
      "back": "case"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤道",
      "back": "equator"
    },
    {
      "front": "私鉄",
      "back": "private railway"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄道",
      "back": "railway"
    },
    {
      "front": "国鉄",
      "back": "Japan National Railways"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄",
      "back": "iron"
    },
    {
      "front": "八百屋",
      "back": "greengrocery, vegetable shop"
    },
    {
      "front": "屋上",
      "back": "housetop, rooftop"
    },
    {
      "front": "家屋",
      "back": "house, building"
    },
    {
      "front": "たばこ屋",
      "back": "cigarette store"
    },
    {
      "front": "味方",
      "back": "ally, being on one's side"
    },
    {
      "front": "地味",
      "back": "plain, modest"
    },
    {
      "front": "味わう",
      "back": "savor, appreciate"
    },
    {
      "front": "味噌",
      "back": "soybean paste"
    },
    {
      "front": "月末",
      "back": "end of the month"
    },
    {
      "front": "年末",
      "back": "end of year"
    },
    {
      "front": "末っ子",
      "back": "youngest child"
    },
    {
      "front": "末",
      "back": "the end, in the end"
    },
    {
      "front": "末",
      "back": "last part, end"
    },
    {
      "front": "飲み水",
      "back": "drinking water"
    },
    {
      "front": "飲料水",
      "back": "drinking water"
    },
    {
      "front": "料金",
      "back": "charge, fee (for using facilities, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "食料",
      "back": "food"
    },
    {
      "front": "地理",
      "back": "geography"
    },
    {
      "front": "処理",
      "back": "handling, processing"
    },
    {
      "front": "分解",
      "back": "taking apart"
    },
    {
      "front": "見解",
      "back": "opinion, view"
    },
    {
      "front": "理解",
      "back": "understanding, comprehension"
    },
    {
      "front": "解く",
      "back": "solve (a problem), unknot"
    },
    {
      "front": "解ける",
      "back": "be solved, be resolved"
    },
    {
      "front": "解釈",
      "back": "interpretation, explanation"
    },
    {
      "front": "有料",
      "back": "fee-charging, paid"
    },
    {
      "front": "無事",
      "back": "safely, peacefully"
    },
    {
      "front": "無料",
      "back": "no charge, free"
    },
    {
      "front": "無理やり",
      "back": "forcibly, against one's will"
    },
    {
      "front": "作り上げる",
      "back": "make up, build up"
    },
    {
      "front": "作家",
      "back": "writer, novelist"
    },
    {
      "front": "作り話",
      "back": "fiction, made-up story"
    },
    {
      "front": "大使",
      "back": "ambassador"
    },
    {
      "front": "使い",
      "back": "errand"
    },
    {
      "front": "使用",
      "back": "usage"
    },
    {
      "front": "用いる",
      "back": "use, through use of"
    },
    {
      "front": "私費",
      "back": "private expense"
    },
    {
      "front": "食費",
      "back": "food expenses"
    },
    {
      "front": "会費",
      "back": "membership fee"
    },
    {
      "front": "国費",
      "back": "national expenditure, government expense"
    },
    {
      "front": "費用",
      "back": "expense, cost"
    },
    {
      "front": "消火",
      "back": "fire extinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "消費",
      "back": "consumption, spending"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り上げ",
      "back": "sales, proceeds"
    },
    {
      "front": "安売り",
      "back": "sale, bargain"
    },
    {
      "front": "売買",
      "back": "buying and selling"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り場",
      "back": "sales floor, department"
    },
    {
      "front": "小売店",
      "back": "retail store, outlet"
    },
    {
      "front": "本店",
      "back": "head office, original store"
    },
    {
      "front": "開店",
      "back": "opening of a store"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉店",
      "back": "shop closing"
    },
    {
      "front": "書店",
      "back": "bookstore (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "商人",
      "back": "merchant, trader"
    },
    {
      "front": "商社",
      "back": "trading firm"
    },
    {
      "front": "商売",
      "back": "trade, business"
    },
    {
      "front": "商店",
      "back": "shop, store"
    },
    {
      "front": "日用品",
      "back": "groceries, daily necessities"
    },
    {
      "front": "上品",
      "back": "elegant, refined"
    },
    {
      "front": "下品",
      "back": "vulgar, coarse"
    },
    {
      "front": "食品",
      "back": "food, food product"
    },
    {
      "front": "部品",
      "back": "parts, accessories"
    },
    {
      "front": "品",
      "back": "goods, item"
    },
    {
      "front": "一段と",
      "back": "more, further"
    },
    {
      "front": "手段",
      "back": "means, way"
    },
    {
      "front": "段階",
      "back": "stage"
    },
    {
      "front": "段",
      "back": "step"
    },
    {
      "front": "アルコール",
      "back": "alcohol, alcoholic beverage"
    },
    {
      "front": "値上げ",
      "back": "price hike, price increase"
    },
    {
      "front": "値上がり",
      "back": "price rise, price increase"
    },
    {
      "front": "値下がり",
      "back": "fall in price"
    },
    {
      "front": "値下げ",
      "back": "price reduction"
    },
    {
      "front": "高価",
      "back": "high-priced, expensive"
    },
    {
      "front": "地価",
      "back": "land price"
    },
    {
      "front": "価値",
      "back": "value, worth"
    },
    {
      "front": "わくわく",
      "back": "feel excited, be thrilled"
    },
    {
      "front": "格好",
      "back": "shape, appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "春分",
      "back": "vernal equinox"
    },
    {
      "front": "初夏",
      "back": "early summer"
    },
    {
      "front": "秋分",
      "back": "autumnal equinox"
    },
    {
      "front": "春夏秋冬",
      "back": "four seasons"
    },
    {
      "front": "四季",
      "back": "the four seasons"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏季",
      "back": "summer season"
    },
    {
      "front": "冬季",
      "back": "winter season"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖か",
      "back": "warm"
    },
    {
      "front": "体温",
      "back": "body temperature"
    },
    {
      "front": "高温",
      "back": "high temperature"
    },
    {
      "front": "低温",
      "back": "low temperature"
    },
    {
      "front": "温暖",
      "back": "warm, mild"
    },
    {
      "front": "北風",
      "back": "north wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "秋風",
      "back": "autumn breeze"
    },
    {
      "front": "風呂場",
      "back": "bathroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱する",
      "back": "heat (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "友情",
      "back": "friendship"
    },
    {
      "front": "事情",
      "back": "circumstances, conditions"
    },
    {
      "front": "情けない",
      "back": "pathetic, pitiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "電報",
      "back": "telegram"
    },
    {
      "front": "新聞社",
      "back": "newspaper publisher"
    },
    {
      "front": "新た",
      "back": "new, fresh"
    },
    {
      "front": "中古",
      "back": "secondhand (used) goods"
    },
    {
      "front": "古本",
      "back": "secondhand book, used book"
    },
    {
      "front": "稽古",
      "back": "practice, training"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪女",
      "back": "wicked woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "最悪",
      "back": "worst"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪用",
      "back": "abuse, misuse"
    },
    {
      "front": "内心",
      "back": "on the inside, one's real intention"
    },
    {
      "front": "心理",
      "back": "mentality, psychology"
    },
    {
      "front": "用心",
      "back": "care, caution"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱心",
      "back": "enthusiasm, zeal"
    },
    {
      "front": "心",
      "back": "heart, mind"
    },
    {
      "front": "思いがけない",
      "back": "unexpected"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い",
      "back": "thoughts, feelings"
    },
    {
      "front": "思いやり",
      "back": "thoughtfulness, kindness"
    },
    {
      "front": "忘年会",
      "back": "year-end party"
    },
    {
      "front": "解決",
      "back": "solution, settlement"
    },
    {
      "front": "決心",
      "back": "determination, resolution"
    },
    {
      "front": "決まり",
      "back": "rule"
    },
    {
      "front": "知人",
      "back": "acquaintance (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "知り合う",
      "back": "get acquainted with, get to know (someone)"
    },
    {
      "front": "知事",
      "back": "governor"
    },
    {
      "front": "通知",
      "back": "notification"
    },
    {
      "front": "知らせ",
      "back": "notice, news"
    },
    {
      "front": "知らず知らず",
      "back": "unknowingly, unconsciously"
    },
    {
      "front": "知れる",
      "back": "become known, be found out"
    },
    {
      "front": "有能",
      "back": "competent, capable"
    },
    {
      "front": "知能",
      "back": "intelligence, mental capacity"
    },
    {
      "front": "才能",
      "back": "talent, ability"
    },
    {
      "front": "能",
      "back": "ability, capability"
    },
    {
      "front": "能",
      "back": "the Noh play"
    },
    {
      "front": "可",
      "back": "permitted, OK"
    },
    {
      "front": "不十分",
      "back": "insufficient"
    },
    {
      "front": "不足",
      "back": "lack, shortage"
    },
    {
      "front": "不安",
      "back": "uneasy, worried"
    },
    {
      "front": "不合格",
      "back": "failing an exam, failure"
    },
    {
      "front": "不満",
      "back": "dissatisfaction, discontent"
    },
    {
      "front": "不通",
      "back": "interruption of service"
    },
    {
      "front": "不可能",
      "back": "impossible"
    },
    {
      "front": "小便",
      "back": "urine, pee"
    },
    {
      "front": "便り",
      "back": "letter, correspondence"
    },
    {
      "front": "便箋",
      "back": "letter paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "住まい",
      "back": "dwelling, residence"
    },
    {
      "front": "住宅地",
      "back": "residential district"
    },
    {
      "front": "長所",
      "back": "strong point, strength"
    },
    {
      "front": "短所",
      "back": "weak point"
    },
    {
      "front": "便所",
      "back": "lavatory, bathroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "所々",
      "back": "here and there, in places"
    },
    {
      "front": "氏",
      "back": "Mr."
    },
    {
      "front": "名人",
      "back": "master, expert"
    },
    {
      "front": "人名",
      "back": "person's name"
    },
    {
      "front": "地名",
      "back": "name of a place"
    },
    {
      "front": "国名",
      "back": "country name"
    },
    {
      "front": "名所",
      "back": "famous place"
    },
    {
      "front": "あだ名",
      "back": "nickname"
    },
    {
      "front": "名",
      "back": "name, reputation"
    },
    {
      "front": "各地",
      "back": "every place, various parts"
    },
    {
      "front": "各国",
      "back": "each country"
    },
    {
      "front": "市外",
      "back": "outside the city"
    },
    {
      "front": "市内",
      "back": "in the city"
    },
    {
      "front": "市場",
      "back": "market (industrial, financial, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "市場",
      "back": "marketplace (selling groceries)"
    },
    {
      "front": "市長",
      "back": "mayor"
    },
    {
      "front": "市",
      "back": "city (municipality)"
    },
    {
      "front": "下町",
      "back": "(old) downtown"
    },
    {
      "front": "町外れ",
      "back": "outskirts of town"
    },
    {
      "front": "町なか",
      "back": "in the town"
    },
    {
      "front": "区分",
      "back": "division, segment"
    },
    {
      "front": "都内",
      "back": "in the metropolitan area of Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "front": "都会",
      "back": "urban city"
    },
    {
      "front": "都心",
      "back": "heart of a city, urban area"
    },
    {
      "front": "都",
      "back": "metropolis of Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "front": "都",
      "back": "capital, city"
    },
    {
      "front": "様子",
      "back": "condition, the state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "様々",
      "back": "various, diverse"
    },
    {
      "front": "奥様",
      "back": "married woman, someone's wife"
    },
    {
      "front": "人物",
      "back": "character, person"
    },
    {
      "front": "見物人",
      "back": "spectator, onlooker"
    },
    {
      "front": "入れ物",
      "back": "container, holder"
    },
    {
      "front": "食物",
      "back": "food"
    },
    {
      "front": "書物",
      "back": "book"
    },
    {
      "front": "物覚え",
      "back": "memory, learning things"
    },
    {
      "front": "物事",
      "back": "things"
    },
    {
      "front": "物理",
      "back": "physics"
    },
    {
      "front": "作物",
      "back": "crop"
    },
    {
      "front": "物価",
      "back": "prices"
    },
    {
      "front": "物知り",
      "back": "knowledgeable (wise) person"
    },
    {
      "front": "名物",
      "back": "specialty, famous product"
    },
    {
      "front": "なま物",
      "back": "uncooked food"
    },
    {
      "front": "偽物",
      "back": "imitation, fake"
    },
    {
      "front": "体重",
      "back": "body weight"
    },
    {
      "front": "重たい",
      "back": "heavy"
    },
    {
      "front": "重ねる",
      "back": "put (something) on top of another, pile up"
    },
    {
      "front": "重なる",
      "back": "come one after another, overlap"
    },
    {
      "front": "重み",
      "back": "weight, importance"
    },
    {
      "front": "厳重",
      "back": "strictness, severity"
    },
    {
      "front": "慎重",
      "back": "discreet, prudent"
    },
    {
      "front": "大量",
      "back": "large quantity, large amount"
    },
    {
      "front": "少量",
      "back": "small quantity, small amount"
    },
    {
      "front": "多量",
      "back": "large quantity, large amount"
    },
    {
      "front": "重量",
      "back": "weight"
    },
    {
      "front": "量",
      "back": "quantity, amount"
    },
    {
      "front": "量る",
      "back": "measure (weight or volume)"
    },
    {
      "front": "インフレーション",
      "back": "inflation"
    },
    {
      "front": "郵送",
      "back": "mailing"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り上げる",
      "back": "take, confiscate"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り入れる",
      "back": "take in, adopt"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り出す",
      "back": "take out, pull out"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り消す",
      "back": "cancel"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り消し",
      "back": "cancellation, revocation"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り決め",
      "back": "decision, agreement"
    },
    {
      "front": "取れる",
      "back": "be harvested"
    },
    {
      "front": "おごる",
      "back": "treat"
    },
    {
      "front": "遠足",
      "back": "field trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "待ち合わせる",
      "back": "meet by appointment"
    },
    {
      "front": "長持ち",
      "back": "endurance, lasting long"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ち物",
      "back": "one's belongings"
    },
    {
      "front": "受け持つ",
      "back": "be in charge of, teach"
    },
    {
      "front": "維持",
      "back": "maintenance, upkeep"
    },
    {
      "front": "打ち上げる",
      "back": "blast off, set off"
    },
    {
      "front": "打ち明ける",
      "back": "confess, tell something on one's mind"
    },
    {
      "front": "打ち消す",
      "back": "negate, deny"
    },
    {
      "front": "投書",
      "back": "letter to the editor"
    },
    {
      "front": "投票",
      "back": "vote, ballot"
    },
    {
      "front": "役人",
      "back": "government official"
    },
    {
      "front": "役目",
      "back": "duty, role"
    },
    {
      "front": "市役所",
      "back": "municipal office, city hall"
    },
    {
      "front": "区役所",
      "back": "ward office"
    },
    {
      "front": "役所",
      "back": "public office"
    },
    {
      "front": "重役",
      "back": "executive"
    },
    {
      "front": "役",
      "back": "role, part"
    },
    {
      "front": "一生",
      "back": "lifetime"
    },
    {
      "front": "生年月日",
      "back": "date of birth"
    },
    {
      "front": "生き方",
      "back": "way of life"
    },
    {
      "front": "人生",
      "back": "one's life (to lead)"
    },
    {
      "front": "生み出す",
      "back": "generate, produce"
    },
    {
      "front": "生け花",
      "back": "flower arrangement"
    },
    {
      "front": "長生き",
      "back": "long life, longevity"
    },
    {
      "front": "無生物",
      "back": "inanimate object"
    },
    {
      "front": "生物",
      "back": "living creature, organism"
    },
    {
      "front": "生き物",
      "back": "living creature"
    },
    {
      "front": "生",
      "back": "raw, fresh"
    },
    {
      "front": "生",
      "back": "life (of a person/an animal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "生じる",
      "back": "happen, occur"
    },
    {
      "front": "生まれ",
      "back": "birth, origin"
    },
    {
      "front": "生える",
      "back": "grow, spring up"
    },
    {
      "front": "生ずる",
      "back": "arise, bring about"
    },
    {
      "front": "生き生きと",
      "back": "lively, vigorously"
    },
    {
      "front": "生まれつき",
      "back": "by nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "誕生",
      "back": "birth"
    },
    {
      "front": "芝生",
      "back": "lawn, turf"
    },
    {
      "front": "生涯",
      "back": "life, lifetime"
    },
    {
      "front": "うつむく",
      "back": "look down, lower one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "front": "ネットワーク",
      "back": "network"
    },
    {
      "front": "わずか",
      "back": "meager, marginal"
    },
    {
      "front": "男性",
      "back": "male, man"
    },
    {
      "front": "性格",
      "back": "character, personality"
    },
    {
      "front": "性能",
      "back": "performance, capacity"
    },
    {
      "front": "性",
      "back": "sex, gender"
    },
    {
      "front": "ついに",
      "back": "at last, finally"
    },
    {
      "front": "産地",
      "back": "production center, producing area"
    },
    {
      "front": "生産",
      "back": "production"
    },
    {
      "front": "活字",
      "back": "printed type"
    },
    {
      "front": "活用",
      "back": "utilization, conjugation"
    },
    {
      "front": "活躍",
      "back": "(successful) performance, action"
    },
    {
      "front": "学年",
      "back": "school year, grade"
    },
    {
      "front": "学力",
      "back": "academic ability"
    },
    {
      "front": "見学",
      "back": "field trip"
    },
    {
      "front": "語学",
      "back": "language study"
    },
    {
      "front": "文学",
      "back": "literature"
    },
    {
      "front": "学会",
      "back": "academic association, academic conference"
    },
    {
      "front": "工学部",
      "back": "department of engineering"
    },
    {
      "front": "学長",
      "back": "school president, principal"
    },
    {
      "front": "学部",
      "back": "faculty, department"
    },
    {
      "front": "学費",
      "back": "tuition"
    },
    {
      "front": "学ぶ",
      "back": "learn, study"
    },
    {
      "front": "奨学金",
      "back": "scholarship"
    },
    {
      "front": "哲学",
      "back": "philosophy"
    },
    {
      "front": "バイト",
      "back": "part-time job"
    },
    {
      "front": "アドバイス",
      "back": "advice"
    },
    {
      "front": "せっかく",
      "back": "with much trouble"
    },
    {
      "front": "休校",
      "back": "temporary school closure"
    },
    {
      "front": "校長",
      "back": "principal, schoolmaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "校庭",
      "back": "school field"
    },
    {
      "front": "校舎",
      "back": "school building"
    },
    {
      "front": "教わる",
      "back": "be taught, learn"
    },
    {
      "front": "キリスト教",
      "back": "Christianity"
    },
    {
      "front": "イスラム教",
      "back": "Islam, Muslim religion"
    },
    {
      "front": "宗教",
      "back": "religion"
    },
    {
      "front": "つい",
      "back": "inadvertently, carelessly"
    },
    {
      "front": "体制",
      "back": "system, structure"
    },
    {
      "front": "制度",
      "back": "system"
    },
    {
      "front": "制御",
      "back": "control, command"
    },
    {
      "front": "御無沙汰",
      "back": "be out of touch"
    },
    {
      "front": "たまたま",
      "back": "by chance, accidentally"
    },
    {
      "front": "強力",
      "back": "powerful"
    },
    {
      "front": "力強い",
      "back": "powerful, vigorous"
    },
    {
      "front": "強気",
      "back": "assertiveness, being strong-willed"
    },
    {
      "front": "最強",
      "back": "strongest"
    },
    {
      "front": "ファッション",
      "back": "fashion"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱気",
      "back": "wimpy, losing one's confidence"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱み",
      "back": "weakness, disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "front": "ショッピング",
      "back": "shopping"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き出す",
      "back": "draw out, bring out"
    },
    {
      "front": "字引",
      "back": "dictionary, encyclopedia"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き止める",
      "back": "dissuade someone from leaving, hold back"
    },
    {
      "front": "長引く",
      "back": "be prolonged, drag on"
    },
    {
      "front": "引用",
      "back": "quotation, citation"
    },
    {
      "front": "取引",
      "back": "transaction, deal"
    },
    {
      "front": "強引",
      "back": "coercive, persistent"
    },
    {
      "front": "引きずる",
      "back": "drag along, dwell on"
    },
    {
      "front": "あり",
      "back": "ant"
    },
    {
      "front": "かえる",
      "back": "frog"
    },
    {
      "front": "見習う",
      "back": "learn, follow someone's example"
    },
    {
      "front": "学習",
      "back": "study, learning"
    },
    {
      "front": "おじさん",
      "back": "Mister, middle-aged man"
    },
    {
      "front": "入試",
      "back": "entrance examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "試合",
      "back": "match, game"
    },
    {
      "front": "試す",
      "back": "try, test"
    },
    {
      "front": "試し",
      "back": "try-on, (by) way of experiment"
    },
    {
      "front": "ペース",
      "back": "pace"
    },
    {
      "front": "受験",
      "back": "take an examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪質",
      "back": "malignant, vicious"
    },
    {
      "front": "物質",
      "back": "matter, substance"
    },
    {
      "front": "性質",
      "back": "nature, property"
    },
    {
      "front": "質",
      "back": "quality"
    },
    {
      "front": "かえって",
      "back": "rather, instead"
    },
    {
      "front": "問屋",
      "back": "wholesale store, wholesaler"
    },
    {
      "front": "学問",
      "back": "learning, scholarship"
    },
    {
      "front": "問い",
      "back": "question, inquiry"
    },
    {
      "front": "訪問",
      "back": "visit"
    },
    {
      "front": "アイドル",
      "back": "idol"
    },
    {
      "front": "話題",
      "back": "topic of conversation, being talked about"
    },
    {
      "front": "題名",
      "back": "title"
    },
    {
      "front": "題",
      "back": "title, topic"
    },
    {
      "front": "単語",
      "back": "word"
    },
    {
      "front": "単に",
      "back": "simply, just"
    },
    {
      "front": "キッチン",
      "back": "kitchen"
    },
    {
      "front": "満点",
      "back": "perfect score"
    },
    {
      "front": "地点",
      "back": "spot, point"
    },
    {
      "front": "重点",
      "back": "important point, emphasis"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱点",
      "back": "weak point, weakness"
    },
    {
      "front": "点",
      "back": "point (of concern), dot"
    },
    {
      "front": "キス",
      "back": "kiss"
    },
    {
      "front": "日数",
      "back": "number of days"
    },
    {
      "front": "小数",
      "back": "decimal"
    },
    {
      "front": "多数",
      "back": "large number, a lot of"
    },
    {
      "front": "人数",
      "back": "number of people"
    },
    {
      "front": "手数",
      "back": "trouble, bother"
    },
    {
      "front": "無数",
      "back": "countless, innumerable"
    },
    {
      "front": "単数",
      "back": "singular"
    },
    {
      "front": "複数",
      "back": "some, several"
    },
    {
      "front": "点数",
      "back": "point, score"
    },
    {
      "front": "枚数",
      "back": "number of flat things"
    },
    {
      "front": "偶数",
      "back": "even number"
    },
    {
      "front": "カタログ",
      "back": "catalogue"
    },
    {
      "front": "マナー",
      "back": "manners"
    },
    {
      "front": "前回",
      "back": "last time"
    },
    {
      "front": "回り道",
      "back": "detour"
    },
    {
      "front": "回数",
      "back": "frequency, number of times"
    },
    {
      "front": "カラオケ",
      "back": "karaoke"
    },
    {
      "front": "勝手",
      "back": "selfish, self-centered"
    },
    {
      "front": "勝ち",
      "back": "win, victory"
    },
    {
      "front": "勝負",
      "back": "match, game"
    },
    {
      "front": "負け",
      "back": "defeat, loss"
    },
    {
      "front": "おばさん",
      "back": "middle-aged woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "担ぐ",
      "back": "shoulder, carry"
    },
    {
      "front": "局",
      "back": "bureau, station"
    },
    {
      "front": "番地",
      "back": "land number"
    },
    {
      "front": "当日",
      "back": "the day (of the event etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "日当たり",
      "back": "exposure to the sun"
    },
    {
      "front": "当分",
      "back": "for some time, for the time being"
    },
    {
      "front": "当初",
      "back": "initial, beginning"
    },
    {
      "front": "見当",
      "back": "estimate, guess"
    },
    {
      "front": "当局",
      "back": "authorities"
    },
    {
      "front": "当番",
      "back": "being on duty, person in charge"
    },
    {
      "front": "当てる",
      "back": "guess, hit the jackpot"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビーチ",
      "back": "beach"
    },
    {
      "front": "文法",
      "back": "grammar"
    },
    {
      "front": "法学部",
      "back": "faculty of law"
    },
    {
      "front": "法",
      "back": "law, rule"
    },
    {
      "front": "憲法",
      "back": "constitution, constitutional law"
    },
    {
      "front": "せいぜい",
      "back": "at most, at best"
    },
    {
      "front": "不規則",
      "back": "irregular"
    },
    {
      "front": "法則",
      "back": "law, rule"
    },
    {
      "front": "エアコン",
      "back": "air-conditioning, air conditioner"
    },
    {
      "front": "経済",
      "back": "economy, economics"
    },
    {
      "front": "済む",
      "back": "be settled, complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "済ませる",
      "back": "get done with (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "株",
      "back": "stock, share"
    },
    {
      "front": "式",
      "back": "ceremony"
    },
    {
      "front": "葬式",
      "back": "funeral"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゆったり",
      "back": "comfortable, easy fit"
    },
    {
      "front": "休業",
      "back": "suspension of a business operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "工業",
      "back": "industry (of production)"
    },
    {
      "front": "業界",
      "back": "industry, business world"
    },
    {
      "front": "作業",
      "back": "work, operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "商業",
      "back": "commerce, trade"
    },
    {
      "front": "産業",
      "back": "industry"
    },
    {
      "front": "営業",
      "back": "business, sales"
    },
    {
      "front": "漁業",
      "back": "fishery"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハードウェア",
      "back": "hardware"
    },
    {
      "front": "金利",
      "back": "interest, interest rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "利口",
      "back": "clever, smart"
    },
    {
      "front": "有利",
      "back": "advantage, profitable"
    },
    {
      "front": "不利",
      "back": "disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "front": "利く",
      "back": "work, function"
    },
    {
      "front": "リクエスト",
      "back": "request"
    },
    {
      "front": "キャンセル",
      "back": "cancellation"
    },
    {
      "front": "利益",
      "back": "profit, benefit"
    },
    {
      "front": "年収",
      "back": "annual income"
    },
    {
      "front": "収入",
      "back": "income"
    },
    {
      "front": "買収",
      "back": "acquisition, bribing"
    },
    {
      "front": "収穫",
      "back": "harvest, harvesting"
    },
    {
      "front": "技術",
      "back": "skill, technology"
    },
    {
      "front": "芸術",
      "back": "art, arts and crafts"
    },
    {
      "front": "競技",
      "back": "sports game, competitive sport"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボリューム",
      "back": "volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "製作",
      "back": "manufacture, production"
    },
    {
      "front": "作製",
      "back": "manufacture, production"
    },
    {
      "front": "製品",
      "back": "product"
    },
    {
      "front": "フルーツ",
      "back": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "front": "木造",
      "back": "being made of wood, wooden (things)"
    },
    {
      "front": "製造",
      "back": "production, manufacturing"
    },
    {
      "front": "天然",
      "back": "nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "必ずしも",
      "back": "not always, not necessarily"
    },
    {
      "front": "不要",
      "back": "unnecessary, unneeded"
    },
    {
      "front": "不必要",
      "back": "unnecessary, unneeded"
    },
    {
      "front": "要点",
      "back": "main point, gist"
    },
    {
      "front": "要するに",
      "back": "in a word, in short"
    },
    {
      "front": "需要",
      "back": "demand"
    },
    {
      "front": "要旨",
      "back": "overview, summary"
    },
    {
      "front": "むく",
      "back": "peel (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラッシュ",
      "back": "rush, rush hour"
    },
    {
      "front": "求人",
      "back": "recruiting"
    },
    {
      "front": "要求",
      "back": "need, demand"
    },
    {
      "front": "求める",
      "back": "seek, yearn for"
    },
    {
      "front": "額",
      "back": "forehead"
    },
    {
      "front": "額",
      "back": "picture frame"
    },
    {
      "front": "体温計",
      "back": "(clinical) thermometer"
    },
    {
      "front": "会計",
      "back": "accounting, payment (for goods and services)"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒暖計",
      "back": "thermometer"
    },
    {
      "front": "計",
      "back": "total"
    },
    {
      "front": "計る",
      "back": "compute, measure (number or time)"
    },
    {
      "front": "キャベツ",
      "back": "cabbage"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き算",
      "back": "subtraction"
    },
    {
      "front": "クッキー",
      "back": "cookie"
    },
    {
      "front": "一時",
      "back": "temporarily"
    },
    {
      "front": "日差し",
      "back": "rays of the sun, sunlight"
    },
    {
      "front": "差し上げる",
      "back": "give (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "物差し",
      "back": "ruler"
    },
    {
      "front": "差",
      "back": "difference"
    },
    {
      "front": "差す",
      "back": "open (an umbrella)"
    },
    {
      "front": "おにぎり",
      "back": "rice ball"
    },
    {
      "front": "時間割り",
      "back": "time schedule, timetable"
    },
    {
      "front": "割合",
      "back": "rate, proportion"
    },
    {
      "front": "役割",
      "back": "role, part"
    },
    {
      "front": "学割",
      "back": "student discount"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り引き",
      "back": "discount"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り引く",
      "back": "give a discount, deduct"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り当てる",
      "back": "assign, allot"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り",
      "back": "rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "割に",
      "back": "comparatively, rather"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り箸",
      "back": "disposable chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひょっとしたら",
      "back": "perhaps"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐるぐる",
      "back": "round and round"
    },
    {
      "front": "残暑",
      "back": "lingering summer heat"
    },
    {
      "front": "残業",
      "back": "overtime work"
    },
    {
      "front": "残り",
      "back": "rest, leftover"
    },
    {
      "front": "残らず",
      "back": "with nothing left behind, without exception"
    },
    {
      "front": "蒸し暑い",
      "back": "hot and humid"
    },
    {
      "front": "どく",
      "back": "move out of the way"
    },
    {
      "front": "年配",
      "back": "advanced age, elderliness"
    },
    {
      "front": "支出",
      "back": "expense, spending"
    },
    {
      "front": "支社",
      "back": "branch office"
    },
    {
      "front": "支度",
      "back": "preparation, getting ready"
    },
    {
      "front": "支店",
      "back": "branch (office)"
    },
    {
      "front": "支配",
      "back": "control, rule"
    },
    {
      "front": "支える",
      "back": "support, sustain"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウエスト",
      "back": "waist"
    },
    {
      "front": "支払い",
      "back": "payment"
    },
    {
      "front": "支払う",
      "back": "pay"
    },
    {
      "front": "払い",
      "back": "payment, bill (to pay)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゴールデンウィーク",
      "back": "golden week"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い返す",
      "back": "talk back"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り返す",
      "back": "take back, regain"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き返す",
      "back": "go back, retrace one's steps"
    },
    {
      "front": "返却",
      "back": "return"
    },
    {
      "front": "シューズ",
      "back": "shoes"
    },
    {
      "front": "借金",
      "back": "borrowing money, debt"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸し出し",
      "back": "lending service, checking out"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸し",
      "back": "loan"
    },
    {
      "front": "申し上げる",
      "back": "tell, say (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "申請",
      "back": "application, petition"
    },
    {
      "front": "申す",
      "back": "say, tell (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "サングラス",
      "back": "sunglasses"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い込む",
      "back": "assume, believe"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ち込む",
      "back": "bring in, carry on"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ込む",
      "back": "draw back, pull in"
    },
    {
      "front": "払い込む",
      "back": "pay in"
    },
    {
      "front": "にらむ",
      "back": "glare, stare"
    },
    {
      "front": "つかまる",
      "back": "hold on to (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "短期大学",
      "back": "junior college"
    },
    {
      "front": "初期",
      "back": "initial period"
    },
    {
      "front": "前期",
      "back": "previous term, last semester"
    },
    {
      "front": "後期",
      "back": "latter term, second half"
    },
    {
      "front": "長期",
      "back": "long period"
    },
    {
      "front": "短期",
      "back": "short-term"
    },
    {
      "front": "新学期",
      "back": "new term, new semester"
    },
    {
      "front": "学期",
      "back": "school term, semester"
    },
    {
      "front": "かぼちゃ",
      "back": "pumpkin"
    },
    {
      "front": "限度",
      "back": "limit, boundary"
    },
    {
      "front": "限界",
      "back": "boundary, limit"
    },
    {
      "front": "有限",
      "back": "limited, finite"
    },
    {
      "front": "無限",
      "back": "infinite, endless"
    },
    {
      "front": "無制限",
      "back": "unlimited"
    },
    {
      "front": "制限",
      "back": "restriction, limit"
    },
    {
      "front": "期限",
      "back": "time limit, deadline"
    },
    {
      "front": "限り",
      "back": "limit"
    },
    {
      "front": "バーゲン",
      "back": "bargain sale"
    },
    {
      "front": "大急ぎ",
      "back": "in a great hurry"
    },
    {
      "front": "急用",
      "back": "urgent business"
    },
    {
      "front": "トースト",
      "back": "toast"
    },
    {
      "front": "品切れ",
      "back": "sold out"
    },
    {
      "front": "値切る",
      "back": "ask for a discount, haggle for bargains"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い切り",
      "back": "to one's heart's content, with all one's might"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い切って",
      "back": "daringly, taking the plunge"
    },
    {
      "front": "区切る",
      "back": "divide, partition"
    },
    {
      "front": "切れ",
      "back": "sharpness"
    },
    {
      "front": "爪切り",
      "back": "nail clipper"
    },
    {
      "front": "ホット",
      "back": "hot"
    },
    {
      "front": "前売り券",
      "back": "advance ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "回数券",
      "back": "book of (discounted) tickets"
    },
    {
      "front": "券",
      "back": "voucher, ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "わさび",
      "back": "Japanese horseradish"
    },
    {
      "front": "代金",
      "back": "charge, fee (in exchange for goods, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "年代",
      "back": "generation, era"
    },
    {
      "front": "近代",
      "back": "modern times"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジョギング",
      "back": "jogging"
    },
    {
      "front": "中指",
      "back": "middle finger, middle toe"
    },
    {
      "front": "小指",
      "back": "little finger, little toe"
    },
    {
      "front": "人差し指",
      "back": "index finger, forefinger"
    },
    {
      "front": "目指す",
      "back": "aim for"
    },
    {
      "front": "指す",
      "back": "point to, aim at"
    },
    {
      "front": "セルフサービス",
      "back": "self-service"
    },
    {
      "front": "一定",
      "back": "fixed, certain"
    },
    {
      "front": "定休日",
      "back": "regular holiday"
    },
    {
      "front": "安定",
      "back": "stability, composure"
    },
    {
      "front": "不安定",
      "back": "unstable"
    },
    {
      "front": "定員",
      "back": "capacity, fixed number (of people)"
    },
    {
      "front": "定価",
      "back": "regular price"
    },
    {
      "front": "定期",
      "back": "regular, periodic (thing)"
    },
    {
      "front": "指定",
      "back": "designation, appointment"
    },
    {
      "front": "肯定",
      "back": "affirmation"
    },
    {
      "front": "くしゃくしゃ",
      "back": "messy, crumpled"
    },
    {
      "front": "じめじめ",
      "back": "damp"
    },
    {
      "front": "予言",
      "back": "prediction, forecast"
    },
    {
      "front": "予報",
      "back": "forecast, prediction"
    },
    {
      "front": "予習",
      "back": "preparation, previewing (a lesson)"
    },
    {
      "front": "予算",
      "back": "budget"
    },
    {
      "front": "じろじろ",
      "back": "staringly"
    },
    {
      "front": "花束",
      "back": "flower bouquet"
    },
    {
      "front": "束",
      "back": "bundle, bunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "消化",
      "back": "digestion"
    },
    {
      "front": "化学",
      "back": "chemistry"
    },
    {
      "front": "強化",
      "back": "strengthening"
    },
    {
      "front": "つるつる",
      "back": "smooth, slippery"
    },
    {
      "front": "更新",
      "back": "renewal"
    },
    {
      "front": "変更",
      "back": "alteration, change"
    },
    {
      "front": "更に",
      "back": "furthermore, still more"
    },
    {
      "front": "増大",
      "back": "increase, enlargement"
    },
    {
      "front": "急増",
      "back": "sharp increase"
    },
    {
      "front": "増す",
      "back": "increase"
    },
    {
      "front": "こしょう",
      "back": "pepper"
    },
    {
      "front": "増減",
      "back": "increase and decrease, rise and fall"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り出す",
      "back": "lean forward, embark on"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗客",
      "back": "passenger"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗車券",
      "back": "train ticket, bus ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗車",
      "back": "boarding, getting on board"
    },
    {
      "front": "びしょびしょ",
      "back": "soaked"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨降り",
      "back": "rainfall, rainy weather"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り降り",
      "back": "getting on and off"
    },
    {
      "front": "着ける",
      "back": "pull up, park (a vehicle)"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚着",
      "back": "heavy clothing"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎゅうぎゅう",
      "back": "packed, crammed"
    },
    {
      "front": "税金",
      "back": "tax"
    },
    {
      "front": "税",
      "back": "tax"
    },
    {
      "front": "県",
      "back": "prefecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち上がる",
      "back": "stand up, take action"
    },
    {
      "front": "私立",
      "back": "private (institution)"
    },
    {
      "front": "夕立",
      "back": "evening shower"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち止まる",
      "back": "stop, halt"
    },
    {
      "front": "国立",
      "back": "national"
    },
    {
      "front": "県立",
      "back": "prefectural"
    },
    {
      "front": "市立",
      "back": "municipal, city-run"
    },
    {
      "front": "都立",
      "back": "Tokyo metropolitan"
    },
    {
      "front": "立て込む",
      "back": "be full of, be crowded with"
    },
    {
      "front": "バツ",
      "back": "cross, x-mark (on errors, mistakes etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "とんかつ",
      "back": "pork cutlet"
    },
    {
      "front": "出席",
      "back": "attendance, presence"
    },
    {
      "front": "客席",
      "back": "seat, passenger seat"
    },
    {
      "front": "座席",
      "back": "seat"
    },
    {
      "front": "ねぎ",
      "back": "Welsh onion, green onion"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠点",
      "back": "fault, flaw"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠ける",
      "back": "be chipped, be missing"
    },
    {
      "front": "目次",
      "back": "table of contents"
    },
    {
      "front": "次男",
      "back": "second son"
    },
    {
      "front": "次女",
      "back": "second daughter"
    },
    {
      "front": "次回",
      "back": "next time"
    },
    {
      "front": "次ぐ",
      "back": "rank next, come next"
    },
    {
      "front": "次々に",
      "back": "one after another, in succession"
    },
    {
      "front": "きゅうり",
      "back": "cucumber"
    },
    {
      "front": "不運",
      "back": "misfortune, bad luck"
    },
    {
      "front": "運",
      "back": "fortune, luck"
    },
    {
      "front": "まぐろ",
      "back": "tuna"
    },
    {
      "front": "回転",
      "back": "spin, rotation"
    },
    {
      "front": "転がる",
      "back": "roll over"
    },
    {
      "front": "転がす",
      "back": "roll (something) over"
    },
    {
      "front": "パイナップル",
      "back": "pineapple"
    },
    {
      "front": "移転",
      "back": "transfer, relocation"
    },
    {
      "front": "行動",
      "back": "action, conduct"
    },
    {
      "front": "運動会",
      "back": "sports festival, athletic meet"
    },
    {
      "front": "運動場",
      "back": "playground, playing field"
    },
    {
      "front": "動作",
      "back": "movement, action"
    },
    {
      "front": "移動",
      "back": "movement, shift"
    },
    {
      "front": "マヨネーズ",
      "back": "mayonnaise"
    },
    {
      "front": "早朝",
      "back": "early morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "早まる",
      "back": "make a hasty decision, act rashly"
    },
    {
      "front": "上達",
      "back": "progress, proficiency"
    },
    {
      "front": "時速",
      "back": "speed per hour"
    },
    {
      "front": "全速力",
      "back": "full speed, full steam"
    },
    {
      "front": "速達",
      "back": "special delivery, express mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "速達便",
      "back": "special delivery, express mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "高速道路",
      "back": "freeway, expressway"
    },
    {
      "front": "高速",
      "back": "high speed, express"
    },
    {
      "front": "速度",
      "back": "speed, velocity"
    },
    {
      "front": "急速",
      "back": "rapid, swift"
    },
    {
      "front": "とりあえず",
      "back": "for now, for the time being"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎりぎり",
      "back": "just in time, barely"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り遅れる",
      "back": "miss (a train, bus, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "年始",
      "back": "beginning of the year"
    },
    {
      "front": "始まり",
      "back": "beginning, start, cause"
    },
    {
      "front": "はっと",
      "back": "taken aback, startled"
    },
    {
      "front": "最終",
      "back": "last, final"
    },
    {
      "front": "終電",
      "back": "last train"
    },
    {
      "front": "終点",
      "back": "last stop, terminal"
    },
    {
      "front": "始終",
      "back": "from beginning to end, constantly"
    },
    {
      "front": "終える",
      "back": "finish (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "現場",
      "back": "scene, job site"
    },
    {
      "front": "現住所",
      "back": "present address"
    },
    {
      "front": "現代",
      "back": "present age, modern times"
    },
    {
      "front": "現れる",
      "back": "appear, emerge"
    },
    {
      "front": "現す",
      "back": "show, reveal"
    },
    {
      "front": "現れ",
      "back": "manifestation, indication"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばらばら",
      "back": "separately, discretely"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶるぶる",
      "back": "shivering, trembling"
    },
    {
      "front": "在学",
      "back": "being in school"
    },
    {
      "front": "実行",
      "back": "practice, execution"
    },
    {
      "front": "実力",
      "back": "(real) ability, capability"
    },
    {
      "front": "実用",
      "back": "practical use, utility"
    },
    {
      "front": "実物",
      "back": "real thing, actual object"
    },
    {
      "front": "実習",
      "back": "practice, training"
    },
    {
      "front": "実施",
      "back": "implementation, enforcement"
    },
    {
      "front": "現実",
      "back": "reality"
    },
    {
      "front": "実現",
      "back": "realization, actualization"
    },
    {
      "front": "実は",
      "back": "actually"
    },
    {
      "front": "実に",
      "back": "truly, surely"
    },
    {
      "front": "実る",
      "back": "bear fruit, be fulfilled"
    },
    {
      "front": "実",
      "back": "fruit, nut"
    },
    {
      "front": "すらすら",
      "back": "smoothly, easily"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずるい",
      "back": "cunning, sneaky"
    },
    {
      "front": "通り過ぎる",
      "back": "go past, pass"
    },
    {
      "front": "通過",
      "back": "passing, passage"
    },
    {
      "front": "過ごす",
      "back": "spend (time)"
    },
    {
      "front": "超過",
      "back": "excess"
    },
    {
      "front": "すやすや",
      "back": "(sleep) peacefully, soundly"
    },
    {
      "front": "去る",
      "back": "go away, leave"
    },
    {
      "front": "発行",
      "back": "publication, issue"
    },
    {
      "front": "発達",
      "back": "development, growth"
    },
    {
      "front": "発明",
      "back": "invention"
    },
    {
      "front": "発電",
      "back": "generation of electricity"
    },
    {
      "front": "発電所",
      "back": "power plant"
    },
    {
      "front": "発売",
      "back": "release (of a product), putting on the market"
    },
    {
      "front": "発熱",
      "back": "heat generation, getting a fever"
    },
    {
      "front": "発つ",
      "back": "start, leave"
    },
    {
      "front": "がたがた",
      "back": "with a rattling noise, unstable"
    },
    {
      "front": "ざらざら",
      "back": "rough, gritty"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い表す",
      "back": "express in words"
    },
    {
      "front": "表情",
      "back": "facial expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "表す",
      "back": "express (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "白紙",
      "back": "blank sheet of paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "表紙",
      "back": "cover (of a book, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "紙くず",
      "back": "wastepaper"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぬるぬる",
      "back": "slimy"
    },
    {
      "front": "五十音",
      "back": "Japanese syllabary"
    },
    {
      "front": "足音",
      "back": "footstep (sound)"
    },
    {
      "front": "音読み",
      "back": "Chinese-derived kanji reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "物音",
      "back": "noise, sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑音",
      "back": "noise"
    },
    {
      "front": "発音",
      "back": "pronunciation"
    },
    {
      "front": "きょろきょろ",
      "back": "look around"
    },
    {
      "front": "行楽",
      "back": "excursion, outing"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽",
      "back": "comfortable, easy"
    },
    {
      "front": "娯楽",
      "back": "amusement, pastime"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐずぐず",
      "back": "slowly, idly"
    },
    {
      "front": "目薬",
      "back": "eye drops"
    },
    {
      "front": "薬品",
      "back": "medicine, drug"
    },
    {
      "front": "薬指",
      "back": "ring finger"
    },
    {
      "front": "食欲",
      "back": "appetite"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲求",
      "back": "want, desire"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲",
      "back": "desire, greed"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぽかぽか",
      "back": "pleasantly warm"
    },
    {
      "front": "映る",
      "back": "be reflected, appear"
    },
    {
      "front": "映す",
      "back": "reflect (something), project (an image)"
    },
    {
      "front": "画家",
      "back": "artist, painter"
    },
    {
      "front": "水面",
      "back": "surface of the water"
    },
    {
      "front": "方面",
      "back": "direction"
    },
    {
      "front": "半面",
      "back": "one side"
    },
    {
      "front": "場面",
      "back": "scene, situation"
    },
    {
      "front": "地面",
      "back": "surface, ground"
    },
    {
      "front": "表面",
      "back": "surface"
    },
    {
      "front": "画面",
      "back": "screen"
    },
    {
      "front": "面",
      "back": "surface, side"
    },
    {
      "front": "かっと",
      "back": "in a temper, in a rage"
    },
    {
      "front": "どきっと",
      "back": "surprised, shocked"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ先",
      "back": "first thing, first"
    },
    {
      "front": "真夜中",
      "back": "midnight, middle of the night"
    },
    {
      "front": "真っ最中",
      "back": "midst, to be in the middle of"
    },
    {
      "front": "真夏",
      "back": "midsummer"
    },
    {
      "front": "真心",
      "back": "sincerity, true heart"
    },
    {
      "front": "真実",
      "back": "truth, reality"
    },
    {
      "front": "真剣",
      "back": "serious, attentive"
    },
    {
      "front": "くたくた",
      "back": "exhausted"
    },
    {
      "front": "水色",
      "back": "light blue"
    },
    {
      "front": "金色",
      "back": "golden color"
    },
    {
      "front": "無色",
      "back": "colorless"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばら色",
      "back": "rose color, rosy"
    },
    {
      "front": "すべすべ",
      "back": "smooth, silky"
    },
    {
      "front": "長方形",
      "back": "rectangle"
    },
    {
      "front": "人形",
      "back": "doll"
    },
    {
      "front": "地形",
      "back": "geographical features, landscape"
    },
    {
      "front": "形式",
      "back": "form, format"
    },
    {
      "front": "にやにや",
      "back": "grin to oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "小型",
      "back": "small size"
    },
    {
      "front": "型",
      "back": "type, model"
    },
    {
      "front": "一種",
      "back": "sort of, almost"
    },
    {
      "front": "一種",
      "back": "a type of, a kind of"
    },
    {
      "front": "人種",
      "back": "race"
    },
    {
      "front": "種目",
      "back": "item, event"
    },
    {
      "front": "種",
      "back": "seed"
    },
    {
      "front": "イカ",
      "back": "squid"
    },
    {
      "front": "分類",
      "back": "classification"
    },
    {
      "front": "人類",
      "back": "humankind"
    },
    {
      "front": "直前",
      "back": "just before, immediately prior"
    },
    {
      "front": "直後",
      "back": "immediately after"
    },
    {
      "front": "見直す",
      "back": "change one's view, review"
    },
    {
      "front": "書き直す",
      "back": "rewrite"
    },
    {
      "front": "直通",
      "back": "direct link"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち直る",
      "back": "get over, recover"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり直す",
      "back": "do over again"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり直し",
      "back": "doing over, redoing"
    },
    {
      "front": "直ちに",
      "back": "at once, immediately"
    },
    {
      "front": "垂直",
      "back": "vertical, perpendicular"
    },
    {
      "front": "うきうき",
      "back": "excitedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "げらげら",
      "back": "(laugh) out loud"
    },
    {
      "front": "間接",
      "back": "indirect"
    },
    {
      "front": "接近",
      "back": "approach, to draw near"
    },
    {
      "front": "接する",
      "back": "come in contact, adjoin"
    },
    {
      "front": "白線",
      "back": "white (warning) line"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱線",
      "back": "derailment"
    },
    {
      "front": "直線",
      "back": "straight line"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごめん",
      "back": "sorry"
    },
    {
      "front": "三角形",
      "back": "triangle"
    },
    {
      "front": "真四角",
      "back": "square"
    },
    {
      "front": "方角",
      "back": "direction"
    },
    {
      "front": "角度",
      "back": "angle"
    },
    {
      "front": "直角",
      "back": "right angle"
    },
    {
      "front": "作曲",
      "back": "composition"
    },
    {
      "front": "曲線",
      "back": "curve, curved line"
    },
    {
      "front": "共通語",
      "back": "common language"
    },
    {
      "front": "共通",
      "back": "commonality"
    },
    {
      "front": "共に",
      "back": "together"
    },
    {
      "front": "でこぼこ",
      "back": "unevenness, bumpiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "同一",
      "back": "same, identical"
    },
    {
      "front": "同時",
      "back": "simultaneous, at the same time"
    },
    {
      "front": "合同",
      "back": "joint"
    },
    {
      "front": "同様",
      "back": "similar, the same as"
    },
    {
      "front": "同性",
      "back": "of the same sex"
    },
    {
      "front": "共同",
      "back": "joint, cooperation"
    },
    {
      "front": "べたべた",
      "back": "stick together, sticky"
    },
    {
      "front": "人違い",
      "back": "mistaken identity"
    },
    {
      "front": "見違える",
      "back": "change beyond recognition, look radically different"
    },
    {
      "front": "違いない",
      "back": "without doubt, for sure"
    },
    {
      "front": "真似",
      "back": "imitation, mimicry"
    },
    {
      "front": "似る",
      "back": "resemble, be alike"
    },
    {
      "front": "似せる",
      "back": "imitate, model after"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴたりと",
      "back": "suddenly"
    },
    {
      "front": "以来",
      "back": "since then"
    },
    {
      "front": "以前",
      "back": "before, ago"
    },
    {
      "front": "以後",
      "back": "from now on, hereafter"
    },
    {
      "front": "以降",
      "back": "thereafter, later than"
    },
    {
      "front": "くすぐる",
      "back": "tickle"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅費",
      "back": "travel expense"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅",
      "back": "journey, travel"
    },
    {
      "front": "和食",
      "back": "Japanese-style food"
    },
    {
      "front": "和語",
      "back": "native Japanese word"
    },
    {
      "front": "和英",
      "back": "Japanese-English"
    },
    {
      "front": "英和",
      "back": "English-Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "漢和",
      "back": "Chinese and Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "和式",
      "back": "Japanese style"
    },
    {
      "front": "和らぐ",
      "back": "soften, ease up"
    },
    {
      "front": "昭和",
      "back": "the Showa era"
    },
    {
      "front": "かんかん",
      "back": "furiously angry, in a rage"
    },
    {
      "front": "これまで",
      "back": "until now, until here"
    },
    {
      "front": "西洋人",
      "back": "Westerner"
    },
    {
      "front": "海洋",
      "back": "ocean, sea"
    },
    {
      "front": "東洋",
      "back": "the East"
    },
    {
      "front": "西洋",
      "back": "the West"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋間",
      "back": "Western-style room"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋食",
      "back": "Western food"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋式",
      "back": "Western style"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋画",
      "back": "foreign film"
    },
    {
      "front": "からす",
      "back": "crow, raven"
    },
    {
      "front": "和服",
      "back": "Japanese clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "かみそり",
      "back": "razor"
    },
    {
      "front": "室内",
      "back": "indoors"
    },
    {
      "front": "図書室",
      "back": "library"
    },
    {
      "front": "待合室",
      "back": "waiting room"
    },
    {
      "front": "和室",
      "back": "Japanese style room"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋室",
      "back": "Western-style room"
    },
    {
      "front": "父母",
      "back": "father and mother, parents"
    },
    {
      "front": "父兄",
      "back": "parents, legal guardians"
    },
    {
      "front": "がくんと",
      "back": "sharply, significantly"
    },
    {
      "front": "親子",
      "back": "parent and child"
    },
    {
      "front": "親友",
      "back": "best friend"
    },
    {
      "front": "親指",
      "back": "thumb"
    },
    {
      "front": "親類",
      "back": "relatives"
    },
    {
      "front": "親しみ",
      "back": "intimacy, familiarity"
    },
    {
      "front": "親戚",
      "back": "relative"
    },
    {
      "front": "くるくる",
      "back": "round and round, spin"
    },
    {
      "front": "万一",
      "back": "if by any chance, just in case"
    },
    {
      "front": "万歳",
      "back": "hurray"
    },
    {
      "front": "歳末",
      "back": "year end"
    },
    {
      "front": "姉妹",
      "back": "sisters"
    },
    {
      "front": "次第",
      "back": "as soon as"
    },
    {
      "front": "次第に",
      "back": "gradually"
    },
    {
      "front": "じゃんじゃん",
      "back": "many times, repeatedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "休息",
      "back": "rest, break"
    },
    {
      "front": "息",
      "back": "breath"
    },
    {
      "front": "ため息",
      "back": "sigh"
    },
    {
      "front": "若々しい",
      "back": "youthful, young-looking"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩行者",
      "back": "pedestrian"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩行者天国",
      "back": "vehicle-free promenade"
    },
    {
      "front": "前者",
      "back": "the former"
    },
    {
      "front": "後者",
      "back": "the latter"
    },
    {
      "front": "文学者",
      "back": "literary person, literati"
    },
    {
      "front": "作者",
      "back": "writer, creator of an artwork"
    },
    {
      "front": "消費者",
      "back": "consumer"
    },
    {
      "front": "学者",
      "back": "scholar"
    },
    {
      "front": "者",
      "back": "person"
    },
    {
      "front": "よける",
      "back": "avoid, dodge"
    },
    {
      "front": "結局",
      "back": "after all, finally"
    },
    {
      "front": "結ぶ",
      "back": "tie, join"
    },
    {
      "front": "がやがや",
      "back": "noisily, loudly"
    },
    {
      "front": "婚約",
      "back": "engagement"
    },
    {
      "front": "契約",
      "back": "contract, agreement"
    },
    {
      "front": "ワープロ",
      "back": "word processor"
    },
    {
      "front": "日課",
      "back": "daily routine"
    },
    {
      "front": "課長",
      "back": "section chief"
    },
    {
      "front": "バック",
      "back": "back, reverse"
    },
    {
      "front": "効力",
      "back": "effect, validity"
    },
    {
      "front": "有効",
      "back": "effective, valid"
    },
    {
      "front": "効く",
      "back": "take effect, work"
    },
    {
      "front": "自国",
      "back": "one's own country"
    },
    {
      "front": "不自然",
      "back": "unnatural, artificial"
    },
    {
      "front": "各自",
      "back": "each one, every individual"
    },
    {
      "front": "自習",
      "back": "self-study"
    },
    {
      "front": "自然に",
      "back": "naturally"
    },
    {
      "front": "自ら",
      "back": "(for) oneself, personally"
    },
    {
      "front": "自慢",
      "back": "showing off, boast"
    },
    {
      "front": "ただ",
      "back": "simply, merely"
    },
    {
      "front": "かかる",
      "back": "catch (a cold, etc.), come down with"
    },
    {
      "front": "不自由",
      "back": "inconvenience, discomfort"
    },
    {
      "front": "経由",
      "back": "via, through"
    },
    {
      "front": "通信",
      "back": "correspondence, communication"
    },
    {
      "front": "信用",
      "back": "trust, credit"
    },
    {
      "front": "信仰",
      "back": "faith, religious belief"
    },
    {
      "front": "それぞれ",
      "back": "each, respectively"
    },
    {
      "front": "信頼",
      "back": "reliance, trust"
    },
    {
      "front": "依頼",
      "back": "request"
    },
    {
      "front": "頼る",
      "back": "rely on, depend on"
    },
    {
      "front": "頼もしい",
      "back": "reliable, dependable"
    },
    {
      "front": "水族館",
      "back": "aquarium"
    },
    {
      "front": "民間",
      "back": "private, civilian"
    },
    {
      "front": "国民",
      "back": "citizen"
    },
    {
      "front": "住民",
      "back": "resident"
    },
    {
      "front": "チーム",
      "back": "team"
    },
    {
      "front": "家主",
      "back": "landlord"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ち主",
      "back": "owner"
    },
    {
      "front": "主役",
      "back": "leading role"
    },
    {
      "front": "主要",
      "back": "major, principal"
    },
    {
      "front": "主",
      "back": "main, chief"
    },
    {
      "front": "テーマ",
      "back": "theme, subject matter"
    },
    {
      "front": "レベル",
      "back": "level"
    },
    {
      "front": "共産主義",
      "back": "Communism"
    },
    {
      "front": "主義",
      "back": "principle, -ism"
    },
    {
      "front": "議会",
      "back": "assembly, council"
    },
    {
      "front": "議員",
      "back": "legislator, assembly member"
    },
    {
      "front": "議長",
      "back": "chairperson"
    },
    {
      "front": "センター",
      "back": "center (for an activity, etc.), hub"
    },
    {
      "front": "論文",
      "back": "thesis, paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "世論",
      "back": "public opinion"
    },
    {
      "front": "結論",
      "back": "conclusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "議論",
      "back": "discussion, debate"
    },
    {
      "front": "論",
      "back": "argument, theory"
    },
    {
      "front": "論じる",
      "back": "argue, discuss"
    },
    {
      "front": "イメージ",
      "back": "image"
    },
    {
      "front": "トップ",
      "back": "top, the best"
    },
    {
      "front": "反則",
      "back": "rule violation, foul"
    },
    {
      "front": "反映",
      "back": "reflection"
    },
    {
      "front": "違反",
      "back": "violation, breach"
    },
    {
      "front": "反論",
      "back": "objection, counterargument"
    },
    {
      "front": "プロ",
      "back": "professional"
    },
    {
      "front": "対",
      "back": "pair"
    },
    {
      "front": "メンバー",
      "back": "member"
    },
    {
      "front": "一応",
      "back": "tentatively, just in case"
    },
    {
      "front": "応用",
      "back": "application, usage"
    },
    {
      "front": "応じる",
      "back": "answer, comply with"
    },
    {
      "front": "モデル",
      "back": "model"
    },
    {
      "front": "解答",
      "back": "solution, answer"
    },
    {
      "front": "問答",
      "back": "questions and answers, dialogue"
    },
    {
      "front": "回答",
      "back": "reply, answer"
    },
    {
      "front": "特定",
      "back": "specific, identification"
    },
    {
      "front": "特色",
      "back": "characteristic, uniqueness"
    },
    {
      "front": "タイプ",
      "back": "type"
    },
    {
      "front": "送別会",
      "back": "farewell party"
    },
    {
      "front": "区別",
      "back": "distinction, discrimination"
    },
    {
      "front": "送別",
      "back": "farewell, send-off"
    },
    {
      "front": "性別",
      "back": "sex, gender"
    },
    {
      "front": "差別",
      "back": "discrimination"
    },
    {
      "front": "別れ",
      "back": "separation, parting"
    },
    {
      "front": "専門家",
      "back": "specialist, expert"
    },
    {
      "front": "専門",
      "back": "specialty, profession"
    },
    {
      "front": "エネルギー",
      "back": "energy"
    },
    {
      "front": "一般に",
      "back": "generally, in general"
    },
    {
      "front": "全般",
      "back": "general, all-round"
    },
    {
      "front": "本格的",
      "back": "authentic, serious"
    },
    {
      "front": "目的地",
      "back": "destination"
    },
    {
      "front": "男性的",
      "back": "masculine, manly"
    },
    {
      "front": "女性的",
      "back": "feminine, womanly"
    },
    {
      "front": "文化的",
      "back": "cultural"
    },
    {
      "front": "合理的",
      "back": "rational, logical"
    },
    {
      "front": "全面的",
      "back": "full-scale, complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "論理的",
      "back": "logical, rational"
    },
    {
      "front": "実用的",
      "back": "practical"
    },
    {
      "front": "経済的",
      "back": "economical, economic"
    },
    {
      "front": "形式的",
      "back": "formal"
    },
    {
      "front": "自主的",
      "back": "voluntary, independent"
    },
    {
      "front": "ああ",
      "back": "like that, that much"
    },
    {
      "front": "並木",
      "back": "row (line) of trees"
    },
    {
      "front": "クラス",
      "back": "class, category"
    },
    {
      "front": "平日",
      "back": "weekday"
    },
    {
      "front": "水平",
      "back": "horizontal, level"
    },
    {
      "front": "水平線",
      "back": "horizon"
    },
    {
      "front": "平気",
      "back": "nonchalant, calm"
    },
    {
      "front": "地平線",
      "back": "horizon"
    },
    {
      "front": "平野",
      "back": "plain land"
    },
    {
      "front": "不平",
      "back": "discontent, complaint"
    },
    {
      "front": "平面",
      "back": "flat surface"
    },
    {
      "front": "平ら",
      "back": "flat, level"
    },
    {
      "front": "平均",
      "back": "average"
    },
    {
      "front": "平凡",
      "back": "common, ordinary"
    },
    {
      "front": "おっしゃる",
      "back": "say, tell (honorific)"
    },
    {
      "front": "どうも",
      "back": "for some reason, somehow"
    },
    {
      "front": "上等",
      "back": "first-class, premium"
    },
    {
      "front": "高等",
      "back": "advanced, high-grade"
    },
    {
      "front": "高等学校",
      "back": "high school"
    },
    {
      "front": "不平等",
      "back": "unequal, unfair"
    },
    {
      "front": "平等",
      "back": "equal, fair"
    },
    {
      "front": "等しい",
      "back": "equal, same"
    },
    {
      "front": "シリーズ",
      "back": "series"
    },
    {
      "front": "病人",
      "back": "sick person"
    },
    {
      "front": "急病",
      "back": "sudden illness"
    },
    {
      "front": "病室",
      "back": "hospital room"
    },
    {
      "front": "人文科学",
      "back": "humanities"
    },
    {
      "front": "外科",
      "back": "surgery"
    },
    {
      "front": "内科",
      "back": "internal medicine"
    },
    {
      "front": "科目",
      "back": "school subject"
    },
    {
      "front": "社会科学",
      "back": "social science"
    },
    {
      "front": "学科",
      "back": "school subject, academic department"
    },
    {
      "front": "自然科学",
      "back": "natural science"
    },
    {
      "front": "科学者",
      "back": "scientist"
    },
    {
      "front": "虫歯",
      "back": "cavity"
    },
    {
      "front": "いらっしゃる",
      "back": "come, go (honorific)"
    },
    {
      "front": "セット",
      "back": "set"
    },
    {
      "front": "死体",
      "back": "corpse"
    },
    {
      "front": "必死",
      "back": "desperate"
    },
    {
      "front": "必死に",
      "back": "desperately"
    },
    {
      "front": "死者",
      "back": "dead person"
    },
    {
      "front": "病死",
      "back": "death from sickness"
    },
    {
      "front": "きちんと",
      "back": "properly, neatly"
    },
    {
      "front": "死亡",
      "back": "death"
    },
    {
      "front": "亡くす",
      "back": "lose (in death)"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち入り禁止",
      "back": "no trespassing"
    },
    {
      "front": "禁止",
      "back": "prohibition, forbiddance"
    },
    {
      "front": "煙",
      "back": "smoke"
    },
    {
      "front": "喫煙",
      "back": "smoking"
    },
    {
      "front": "レポート",
      "back": "report, paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "日本酒",
      "back": "Japanese rice wine"
    },
    {
      "front": "酒屋",
      "back": "liquor store"
    },
    {
      "front": "禁酒",
      "back": "abstention from alcohol"
    },
    {
      "front": "酔う",
      "back": "get drunk"
    },
    {
      "front": "険しい",
      "back": "steep, rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "冒険",
      "back": "adventure, venture"
    },
    {
      "front": "スタート",
      "back": "start, begin"
    },
    {
      "front": "保証人",
      "back": "guarantor"
    },
    {
      "front": "証明",
      "back": "proof, evidence"
    },
    {
      "front": "証券",
      "back": "securities"
    },
    {
      "front": "保証",
      "back": "guarantee, warranty"
    },
    {
      "front": "おる",
      "back": "be present, stay (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ご存知",
      "back": "know (honorific)"
    },
    {
      "front": "生存",
      "back": "existence, to be alive"
    },
    {
      "front": "存在",
      "back": "existence"
    },
    {
      "front": "保存",
      "back": "preservation, conservation"
    },
    {
      "front": "存じる",
      "back": "think, know (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "注ぐ",
      "back": "pour"
    },
    {
      "front": "注",
      "back": "annotation, explanatory note"
    },
    {
      "front": "まるで",
      "back": "just like"
    },
    {
      "front": "意外",
      "back": "unexpected, surprising"
    },
    {
      "front": "生意気",
      "back": "impudent, cocky"
    },
    {
      "front": "意地悪",
      "back": "mean, ill-natured"
    },
    {
      "front": "不注意",
      "back": "careless"
    },
    {
      "front": "意義",
      "back": "meaning, significance"
    },
    {
      "front": "スタイル",
      "back": "style, figure"
    },
    {
      "front": "コード",
      "back": "cord"
    },
    {
      "front": "明確",
      "back": "clear and specific"
    },
    {
      "front": "不確か",
      "back": "uncertain, unreliable"
    },
    {
      "front": "確実",
      "back": "certain, sure"
    },
    {
      "front": "バランス",
      "back": "balance"
    },
    {
      "front": "認可",
      "back": "approval, authorization"
    },
    {
      "front": "認める",
      "back": "recognize, permit"
    },
    {
      "front": "能率",
      "back": "efficiency"
    },
    {
      "front": "確率",
      "back": "probability, chance"
    },
    {
      "front": "率",
      "back": "ratio, rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "ようやく",
      "back": "at last, at long last"
    },
    {
      "front": "時機",
      "back": "opportunity, chance"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅客機",
      "back": "passenger plane"
    },
    {
      "front": "機会",
      "back": "opportunity, chance"
    },
    {
      "front": "機長",
      "back": "(plane) captain"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジェット機",
      "back": "jet airplane"
    },
    {
      "front": "消火器",
      "back": "fire extinguisher"
    },
    {
      "front": "受話器",
      "back": "telephone receiver"
    },
    {
      "front": "器用",
      "back": "skillful, being good with one's hands"
    },
    {
      "front": "不器用",
      "back": "clumsy, unskillful"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽器",
      "back": "musical instrument"
    },
    {
      "front": "器械",
      "back": "instrument, equipment"
    },
    {
      "front": "材木",
      "back": "timber, wood"
    },
    {
      "front": "パターン",
      "back": "pattern"
    },
    {
      "front": "家具",
      "back": "furniture"
    },
    {
      "front": "道具",
      "back": "tool"
    },
    {
      "front": "器具",
      "back": "equipment, instrument"
    },
    {
      "front": "基地",
      "back": "base, military base"
    },
    {
      "front": "基づく",
      "back": "be based on"
    },
    {
      "front": "基礎",
      "back": "base, foundation"
    },
    {
      "front": "よう",
      "back": "look like, seem"
    },
    {
      "front": "水準",
      "back": "level, standard"
    },
    {
      "front": "基準",
      "back": "standard, criterion"
    },
    {
      "front": "予備",
      "back": "reserve, extra"
    },
    {
      "front": "設計",
      "back": "design, plan"
    },
    {
      "front": "設備",
      "back": "equipment, facilities"
    },
    {
      "front": "ロボット",
      "back": "robot"
    },
    {
      "front": "社説",
      "back": "editorial"
    },
    {
      "front": "解説",
      "back": "explanation, commentary"
    },
    {
      "front": "説",
      "back": "theory, opinion"
    },
    {
      "front": "インク",
      "back": "ink"
    },
    {
      "front": "不公平",
      "back": "unfair, unjust"
    },
    {
      "front": "公式",
      "back": "formal, official"
    },
    {
      "front": "公共",
      "back": "public, community"
    },
    {
      "front": "公平",
      "back": "fairness, equality"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピンポン",
      "back": "table tennis"
    },
    {
      "front": "体育",
      "back": "physical training, physical education"
    },
    {
      "front": "遊園地",
      "back": "amusement park"
    },
    {
      "front": "学園",
      "back": "educational institution, school"
    },
    {
      "front": "保育園",
      "back": "day-care center, nursery school"
    },
    {
      "front": "やや",
      "back": "slightly, a little"
    },
    {
      "front": "祭日",
      "back": "national holiday"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひな祭り",
      "back": "the Doll Festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "交際",
      "back": "association, dating"
    },
    {
      "front": "国際的",
      "back": "international"
    },
    {
      "front": "国際化",
      "back": "internationalization"
    },
    {
      "front": "際",
      "back": "opportunity, time"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛行",
      "back": "flight"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛行場",
      "back": "airport, airdrome"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛び上がる",
      "back": "fly up, jump up"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛び下りる",
      "back": "jump off, jump down"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛び出す",
      "back": "fly out, dash out"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛び込む",
      "back": "dive into, jump into"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛ばす",
      "back": "fly (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ますます",
      "back": "increasingly, more and more"
    },
    {
      "front": "プラス",
      "back": "plus, advantage"
    },
    {
      "front": "航空",
      "back": "aviation"
    },
    {
      "front": "航空券",
      "back": "airline ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "航空機",
      "back": "aircraft, airplane"
    },
    {
      "front": "船長",
      "back": "captain"
    },
    {
      "front": "風船",
      "back": "balloon"
    },
    {
      "front": "船便",
      "back": "surface mail, shipping service"
    },
    {
      "front": "シーズン",
      "back": "season"
    },
    {
      "front": "半島",
      "back": "peninsula"
    },
    {
      "front": "島",
      "back": "island (Chinese origin)"
    },
    {
      "front": "完全",
      "back": "perfect, complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "不完全",
      "back": "imperfect, incomplete"
    },
    {
      "front": "未成年",
      "back": "minor, underage"
    },
    {
      "front": "成人",
      "back": "adult, to be of age"
    },
    {
      "front": "成長",
      "back": "growth"
    },
    {
      "front": "作成",
      "back": "to produce, to make"
    },
    {
      "front": "成立",
      "back": "formation, closing (of a deal etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "賛成",
      "back": "approval, agreement"
    },
    {
      "front": "たとえ",
      "back": "even if, granting that"
    },
    {
      "front": "失業",
      "back": "unemployment, loss of job"
    },
    {
      "front": "失う",
      "back": "lose, miss"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふと",
      "back": "suddenly, unintentionally"
    },
    {
      "front": "勝敗",
      "back": "victory or defeat"
    },
    {
      "front": "敗れる",
      "back": "be defeated, lose (a game)"
    },
    {
      "front": "原子力",
      "back": "atomic energy, nuclear power"
    },
    {
      "front": "野原",
      "back": "open field"
    },
    {
      "front": "原料",
      "back": "raw material"
    },
    {
      "front": "原理",
      "back": "mechanism, theory"
    },
    {
      "front": "原",
      "back": "plain, field"
    },
    {
      "front": "ステージ",
      "back": "stage"
    },
    {
      "front": "資本主義",
      "back": "capitalism"
    },
    {
      "front": "資料",
      "back": "materials, data"
    },
    {
      "front": "願い",
      "back": "wish, hope"
    },
    {
      "front": "大正",
      "back": "Taisho era"
    },
    {
      "front": "正方形",
      "back": "square"
    },
    {
      "front": "正門",
      "back": "main gate, main entrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "不正",
      "back": "fraud, injustice"
    },
    {
      "front": "正式",
      "back": "formal, official"
    },
    {
      "front": "正座",
      "back": "sitting on one's heels"
    },
    {
      "front": "正面",
      "back": "front, face"
    },
    {
      "front": "正",
      "back": "original (copy)"
    },
    {
      "front": "プラン",
      "back": "plan"
    },
    {
      "front": "マッチ",
      "back": "match, matchbox"
    },
    {
      "front": "日常",
      "back": "everyday life, daily life"
    },
    {
      "front": "異常",
      "back": "unusual, abnormal"
    },
    {
      "front": "常に",
      "back": "always, at all times (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "カバー",
      "back": "cover, covering"
    },
    {
      "front": "無意識",
      "back": "unconsciously, unintentionally"
    },
    {
      "front": "知識",
      "back": "knowledge"
    },
    {
      "front": "意識",
      "back": "consciousness, awareness"
    },
    {
      "front": "常識",
      "back": "common sense, common knowledge"
    },
    {
      "front": "しばしば",
      "back": "often, frequently"
    },
    {
      "front": "非常口",
      "back": "emergency exit"
    },
    {
      "front": "非常",
      "back": "emergency"
    },
    {
      "front": "非常識",
      "back": "lack of common sense"
    },
    {
      "front": "困難",
      "back": "difficulty, hardship"
    },
    {
      "front": "どんなに",
      "back": "how much"
    },
    {
      "front": "体調",
      "back": "health condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "調子",
      "back": "tone, condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "調味料",
      "back": "seasoning"
    },
    {
      "front": "強調",
      "back": "emphasis, stress"
    },
    {
      "front": "リズム",
      "back": "rhythm"
    },
    {
      "front": "整理",
      "back": "putting something in order, sorting out"
    },
    {
      "front": "整備",
      "back": "maintenance"
    },
    {
      "front": "調整",
      "back": "regulation, adjustment"
    },
    {
      "front": "整う",
      "back": "be arranged, be ready"
    },
    {
      "front": "カーブ",
      "back": "curve"
    },
    {
      "front": "節約",
      "back": "saving, thrift"
    },
    {
      "front": "調節",
      "back": "adjustment"
    },
    {
      "front": "調査",
      "back": "investigation, examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "検査",
      "back": "inspection, examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダム",
      "back": "dam"
    },
    {
      "front": "提出",
      "back": "submission"
    },
    {
      "front": "案外",
      "back": "unexpectedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "答案",
      "back": "exam paper, answer sheet"
    },
    {
      "front": "案",
      "back": "plan, idea"
    },
    {
      "front": "まさか",
      "back": "never (in a million years)"
    },
    {
      "front": "掲示",
      "back": "notice, post"
    },
    {
      "front": "目標",
      "back": "target, goal"
    },
    {
      "front": "標準",
      "back": "standard, norm"
    },
    {
      "front": "連れ",
      "back": "companion"
    },
    {
      "front": "連れる",
      "back": "take along, bring along"
    },
    {
      "front": "オリンピック",
      "back": "the Olympics"
    },
    {
      "front": "長続き",
      "back": "lasting for a long time"
    },
    {
      "front": "連続",
      "back": "continuation, series"
    },
    {
      "front": "続々",
      "back": "in succession, one after another"
    },
    {
      "front": "さす",
      "back": "pour"
    },
    {
      "front": "相当",
      "back": "suitability, equivalence"
    },
    {
      "front": "相づち",
      "back": "supportive reaction"
    },
    {
      "front": "相撲",
      "back": "Japanese-style wrestling"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピン",
      "back": "hairpin, pin"
    },
    {
      "front": "記入",
      "back": "entry, fill in"
    },
    {
      "front": "暗記",
      "back": "memorization"
    },
    {
      "front": "記事",
      "back": "article, story"
    },
    {
      "front": "記号",
      "back": "symbol, mark"
    },
    {
      "front": "記者",
      "back": "journalist, reporter"
    },
    {
      "front": "記憶",
      "back": "memory, remembrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "そろう",
      "back": "be (all) together, become complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "録音テープ",
      "back": "recording tape"
    },
    {
      "front": "録画",
      "back": "videotaping, recording"
    },
    {
      "front": "登山",
      "back": "mountain climbing"
    },
    {
      "front": "山登り",
      "back": "mountain climbing"
    },
    {
      "front": "登場",
      "back": "appearance (on stage, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "無関心",
      "back": "indifferent, not interested"
    },
    {
      "front": "関心",
      "back": "concern, interest"
    },
    {
      "front": "税関",
      "back": "customs office"
    },
    {
      "front": "機関",
      "back": "agency, facility"
    },
    {
      "front": "関節",
      "back": "joint"
    },
    {
      "front": "関連",
      "back": "relation, relevance"
    },
    {
      "front": "関わる",
      "back": "be involved, be concerned"
    },
    {
      "front": "まとまる",
      "back": "come together, agree on"
    },
    {
      "front": "無関係",
      "back": "irrelevant, unrelated"
    },
    {
      "front": "係",
      "back": "person in charge"
    },
    {
      "front": "コーチ",
      "back": "coach"
    },
    {
      "front": "現状",
      "back": "current condition (situation)"
    },
    {
      "front": "症状",
      "back": "symptom"
    },
    {
      "front": "事態",
      "back": "situation, state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "態度",
      "back": "attitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジャーナリスト",
      "back": "journalist"
    },
    {
      "front": "政治家",
      "back": "politician"
    },
    {
      "front": "明治",
      "back": "Meiji era"
    },
    {
      "front": "府立",
      "back": "prefectural"
    },
    {
      "front": "府",
      "back": "prefecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "せめて",
      "back": "at least"
    },
    {
      "front": "政党",
      "back": "political party"
    },
    {
      "front": "党",
      "back": "political party"
    },
    {
      "front": "対策",
      "back": "measure, countermeasure"
    },
    {
      "front": "もともと",
      "back": "originally, by nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "入選",
      "back": "being selected for a contest, etc., being nominated"
    },
    {
      "front": "選択",
      "back": "selection, choice"
    },
    {
      "front": "挙げる",
      "back": "cite, give (an example)"
    },
    {
      "front": "天候",
      "back": "weather, climate"
    },
    {
      "front": "気候",
      "back": "climate"
    },
    {
      "front": "スライド",
      "back": "slide"
    },
    {
      "front": "候補",
      "back": "candidate"
    },
    {
      "front": "補う",
      "back": "supplement, replenish"
    },
    {
      "front": "手首",
      "back": "wrist"
    },
    {
      "front": "足首",
      "back": "ankle"
    },
    {
      "front": "首相",
      "back": "prime minister"
    },
    {
      "front": "サークル",
      "back": "circle, club"
    },
    {
      "front": "先頭",
      "back": "forefront, head"
    },
    {
      "front": "頭痛",
      "back": "headache"
    },
    {
      "front": "頭",
      "back": "head (of a group), chief"
    },
    {
      "front": "クラシック",
      "back": "classical music, the classics"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝顔",
      "back": "morning glory"
    },
    {
      "front": "顔色",
      "back": "complexion (face), countenance"
    },
    {
      "front": "改造",
      "back": "reconstruction, reorganization"
    },
    {
      "front": "改正",
      "back": "revision, amendment"
    },
    {
      "front": "改めて",
      "back": "once again, anew"
    },
    {
      "front": "改める",
      "back": "reform, change for the better"
    },
    {
      "front": "生命",
      "back": "life"
    },
    {
      "front": "命",
      "back": "life"
    },
    {
      "front": "命じる",
      "back": "order, give orders"
    },
    {
      "front": "寿命",
      "back": "life span"
    },
    {
      "front": "プリント",
      "back": "print"
    },
    {
      "front": "領収書",
      "back": "receipt"
    },
    {
      "front": "領事館",
      "back": "consulate"
    },
    {
      "front": "つぐ",
      "back": "pour, pour into"
    },
    {
      "front": "組合",
      "back": "union, guild"
    },
    {
      "front": "組",
      "back": "school class"
    },
    {
      "front": "組む",
      "back": "pair up, partner with"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボーナス",
      "back": "bonus"
    },
    {
      "front": "組織",
      "back": "organization, structure"
    },
    {
      "front": "前進",
      "back": "advance, proceed"
    },
    {
      "front": "進歩",
      "back": "progress, advancement"
    },
    {
      "front": "進学",
      "back": "enter school"
    },
    {
      "front": "ポスター",
      "back": "poster"
    },
    {
      "front": "推薦",
      "back": "recommendation, nomination"
    },
    {
      "front": "レンズ",
      "back": "lens"
    },
    {
      "front": "無責任",
      "back": "irresponsible"
    },
    {
      "front": "担任",
      "back": "teacher in charge"
    },
    {
      "front": "任せる",
      "back": "entrust to, leave it to"
    },
    {
      "front": "委員会",
      "back": "committee"
    },
    {
      "front": "委員",
      "back": "committee member, delegate"
    },
    {
      "front": "マイク",
      "back": "microphone"
    },
    {
      "front": "出勤",
      "back": "going to work, attendance at work"
    },
    {
      "front": "勤め",
      "back": "duty, work"
    },
    {
      "front": "公務員",
      "back": "public officer, civil servant"
    },
    {
      "front": "事務員",
      "back": "clerical staff"
    },
    {
      "front": "事務",
      "back": "office duty, clerical work"
    },
    {
      "front": "義務",
      "back": "duty, obligation"
    },
    {
      "front": "務める",
      "back": "perform a duty, play a role"
    },
    {
      "front": "務め",
      "back": "duty, task"
    },
    {
      "front": "従う",
      "back": "follow, obey"
    },
    {
      "front": "どうか",
      "back": "please"
    },
    {
      "front": "雇う",
      "back": "employ, hire"
    },
    {
      "front": "実績",
      "back": "results achieved, performance"
    },
    {
      "front": "わく",
      "back": "well up"
    },
    {
      "front": "集中",
      "back": "concentration, convergence"
    },
    {
      "front": "集合",
      "back": "gathering, assembly"
    },
    {
      "front": "募集",
      "back": "recruitment, collection"
    },
    {
      "front": "集まり",
      "back": "gathering, assembly"
    },
    {
      "front": "採点",
      "back": "marking, grading"
    },
    {
      "front": "採る",
      "back": "gather, pick"
    },
    {
      "front": "時給",
      "back": "hourly wage"
    },
    {
      "front": "月給",
      "back": "monthly salary"
    },
    {
      "front": "供給",
      "back": "supply, provision"
    },
    {
      "front": "そろえる",
      "back": "make (something) uniform, put (something) in order"
    },
    {
      "front": "就任",
      "back": "inauguration, assumption (of office)"
    },
    {
      "front": "就く",
      "back": "set about a task, assume (a position)"
    },
    {
      "front": "就職",
      "back": "finding a job, getting a job"
    },
    {
      "front": "早退",
      "back": "leaving earlier than usual"
    },
    {
      "front": "退院",
      "back": "discharge from hospital"
    },
    {
      "front": "つながり",
      "back": "connection, relationship"
    },
    {
      "front": "退屈",
      "back": "boring, tedious"
    },
    {
      "front": "条件",
      "back": "condition, term"
    },
    {
      "front": "参考書",
      "back": "reference book"
    },
    {
      "front": "参考",
      "back": "reference, consultation"
    },
    {
      "front": "参る",
      "back": "go, come (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "お参り",
      "back": "visiting a shrine or temple"
    },
    {
      "front": "考慮",
      "back": "consideration, deliberation"
    },
    {
      "front": "はねる",
      "back": "run over, hit"
    },
    {
      "front": "増加",
      "back": "increase, rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "加える",
      "back": "add (things of the same or different kinds)"
    },
    {
      "front": "加わる",
      "back": "join in"
    },
    {
      "front": "追加",
      "back": "addition, supplement"
    },
    {
      "front": "追う",
      "back": "chase, pursue"
    },
    {
      "front": "スピーカー",
      "back": "speaker"
    },
    {
      "front": "見比べる",
      "back": "look and compare"
    },
    {
      "front": "比較的",
      "back": "comparatively, relatively"
    },
    {
      "front": "比較",
      "back": "comparison"
    },
    {
      "front": "いくら",
      "back": "no matter how much"
    },
    {
      "front": "批判",
      "back": "criticism"
    },
    {
      "front": "評価",
      "back": "evaluation, recognition"
    },
    {
      "front": "批評",
      "back": "criticism, comment"
    },
    {
      "front": "評判",
      "back": "reputation"
    },
    {
      "front": "感覚",
      "back": "sense, feel"
    },
    {
      "front": "感情",
      "back": "feeling, emotion"
    },
    {
      "front": "感心",
      "back": "admiration"
    },
    {
      "front": "感動",
      "back": "to be impressed, to be touched"
    },
    {
      "front": "実感",
      "back": "true sense, realization"
    },
    {
      "front": "感じ",
      "back": "feeling, impression"
    },
    {
      "front": "テンポ",
      "back": "tempo, pace"
    },
    {
      "front": "オーケストラ",
      "back": "orchestra"
    },
    {
      "front": "空想",
      "back": "fantasy, daydreams"
    },
    {
      "front": "理想",
      "back": "ideal"
    },
    {
      "front": "思想",
      "back": "thought, conception"
    },
    {
      "front": "感想",
      "back": "thought, impression"
    },
    {
      "front": "アンテナ",
      "back": "antenna"
    },
    {
      "front": "想像",
      "back": "imagination"
    },
    {
      "front": "現象",
      "back": "phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "front": "対象",
      "back": "target, object"
    },
    {
      "front": "象",
      "back": "elephant"
    },
    {
      "front": "抽象的",
      "back": "abstract"
    },
    {
      "front": "スタンド",
      "back": "table lamp, desk lamp"
    },
    {
      "front": "障子",
      "back": "paper sliding-door"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い換える",
      "back": "paraphrase, express in different words"
    },
    {
      "front": "交換",
      "back": "exchange, bartering"
    },
    {
      "front": "変換",
      "back": "change, conversion"
    },
    {
      "front": "ブレーキ",
      "back": "brake"
    },
    {
      "front": "交替",
      "back": "shift, taking turns"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り替える",
      "back": "change, replace"
    },
    {
      "front": "着替え",
      "back": "change of clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "立て替える",
      "back": "pay for others (for the time being)"
    },
    {
      "front": "火災",
      "back": "fire, fire disaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "災難",
      "back": "calamity, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "front": "ナンバー",
      "back": "number"
    },
    {
      "front": "水害",
      "back": "flood damage"
    },
    {
      "front": "有害",
      "back": "harmful, hazardous"
    },
    {
      "front": "無害",
      "back": "harmless"
    },
    {
      "front": "公害",
      "back": "(environmental) pollution"
    },
    {
      "front": "障害",
      "back": "obstacle, disorder"
    },
    {
      "front": "害",
      "back": "harm, damage"
    },
    {
      "front": "ストップ",
      "back": "stop"
    },
    {
      "front": "被害",
      "back": "damage, harm"
    },
    {
      "front": "被せる",
      "back": "cover (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "破る",
      "back": "defeat"
    },
    {
      "front": "トンネル",
      "back": "tunnel"
    },
    {
      "front": "救う",
      "back": "save, relieve"
    },
    {
      "front": "助手",
      "back": "assistant"
    },
    {
      "front": "救助",
      "back": "rescue, relief"
    },
    {
      "front": "助かる",
      "back": "be helped, be rescued"
    },
    {
      "front": "まく",
      "back": "sow (seeds)"
    },
    {
      "front": "支援",
      "back": "support, backing"
    },
    {
      "front": "応援",
      "back": "support, cheering"
    },
    {
      "front": "援助",
      "back": "aid, assistance"
    },
    {
      "front": "派出所",
      "back": "police box, police station"
    },
    {
      "front": "派手",
      "back": "flashy, loud"
    },
    {
      "front": "派閥",
      "back": "clique, faction"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハンドル",
      "back": "steering wheel"
    },
    {
      "front": "小遣い",
      "back": "pocket money, allowance"
    },
    {
      "front": "広告",
      "back": "advertisement"
    },
    {
      "front": "警告",
      "back": "warning, admonition"
    },
    {
      "front": "管理",
      "back": "management, administration"
    },
    {
      "front": "クリーム",
      "back": "cream"
    },
    {
      "front": "犯人",
      "back": "criminal, offender"
    },
    {
      "front": "犯罪",
      "back": "offense, crime"
    },
    {
      "front": "罪",
      "back": "crime, sin"
    },
    {
      "front": "強盗",
      "back": "robbery, burglar"
    },
    {
      "front": "盗難",
      "back": "theft"
    },
    {
      "front": "自殺",
      "back": "suicide"
    },
    {
      "front": "奪う",
      "back": "rob, take by force"
    },
    {
      "front": "逮捕",
      "back": "arrest, capture"
    },
    {
      "front": "捕まえる",
      "back": "catch (someone/something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "捕まる",
      "back": "be caught, be arrested"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベテラン",
      "back": "experienced person, veteran"
    },
    {
      "front": "逃げ道",
      "back": "escape route"
    },
    {
      "front": "逃がす",
      "back": "let (someone/something) to escape"
    },
    {
      "front": "大戦",
      "back": "world war"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦前",
      "back": "prewar period"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦後",
      "back": "postwar period"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦場",
      "back": "battlefield"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦死",
      "back": "death in war"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦う",
      "back": "wage war, fight"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦い",
      "back": "war, battle"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンクリート",
      "back": "concrete"
    },
    {
      "front": "スピーチ",
      "back": "speech"
    },
    {
      "front": "争う",
      "back": "compete, fight"
    },
    {
      "front": "人混み",
      "back": "crowd"
    },
    {
      "front": "混雑",
      "back": "congestion, to be crowded"
    },
    {
      "front": "混ぜる",
      "back": "mix (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "混じる",
      "back": "be blended, get mixed (distinguishable)"
    },
    {
      "front": "混ざる",
      "back": "be mixed, be stirred"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベンチ",
      "back": "bench"
    },
    {
      "front": "混乱",
      "back": "chaos, confusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "統一",
      "back": "unity, standardization"
    },
    {
      "front": "統計",
      "back": "statistics, figures"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビタミン",
      "back": "vitamin"
    },
    {
      "front": "総理",
      "back": "prime minister"
    },
    {
      "front": "総数",
      "back": "total (number)"
    },
    {
      "front": "捜す",
      "back": "look for, search for"
    },
    {
      "front": "たまる",
      "back": "accumulate, store up"
    },
    {
      "front": "索引",
      "back": "index"
    },
    {
      "front": "検索",
      "back": "search"
    },
    {
      "front": "湖",
      "back": "lake"
    },
    {
      "front": "注意深い",
      "back": "careful"
    },
    {
      "front": "深さ",
      "back": "depth, profundity"
    },
    {
      "front": "深まる",
      "back": "deepen, become deeper"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶつける",
      "back": "hit, strike"
    },
    {
      "front": "段落",
      "back": "paragraph"
    },
    {
      "front": "落とし物",
      "back": "lost property"
    },
    {
      "front": "落ち着く",
      "back": "calm down, settle in"
    },
    {
      "front": "落第",
      "back": "failing an exam"
    },
    {
      "front": "マラソン",
      "back": "marathon"
    },
    {
      "front": "波",
      "back": "wave, fluctuations"
    },
    {
      "front": "一流",
      "back": "top-ranked, world-class"
    },
    {
      "front": "二流",
      "back": "second-rate, second-class"
    },
    {
      "front": "三流",
      "back": "third-rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "流行",
      "back": "fashion, trend"
    },
    {
      "front": "中流",
      "back": "mid-stream, middle reaches"
    },
    {
      "front": "上流",
      "back": "upstream"
    },
    {
      "front": "下流",
      "back": "downstream"
    },
    {
      "front": "交流",
      "back": "interaction, contact"
    },
    {
      "front": "流れ",
      "back": "flow, stream"
    },
    {
      "front": "流す",
      "back": "run (water etc.), shed"
    },
    {
      "front": "パイプ",
      "back": "pipe"
    },
    {
      "front": "よそ",
      "back": "somewhere else, not one's own"
    },
    {
      "front": "崩れる",
      "back": "crumble, collapse"
    },
    {
      "front": "崩す",
      "back": "put (something) into disorder, destroy"
    },
    {
      "front": "パイロット",
      "back": "pilot"
    },
    {
      "front": "手洗い",
      "back": "washing hands"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗い物",
      "back": "dishes to be washed"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗面",
      "back": "washing one's face, having a wash"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗面器",
      "back": "washbowl"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗剤",
      "back": "detergent"
    },
    {
      "front": "絵本",
      "back": "picture book"
    },
    {
      "front": "石油",
      "back": "petroleum oil"
    },
    {
      "front": "モダン",
      "back": "modern"
    },
    {
      "front": "浮く",
      "back": "float"
    },
    {
      "front": "浮かべる",
      "back": "float (something), set (something) afloat"
    },
    {
      "front": "ユーモア",
      "back": "humor"
    },
    {
      "front": "永遠",
      "back": "eternity"
    },
    {
      "front": "永久",
      "back": "permanence, eternity"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷え込む",
      "back": "get cold"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷ます",
      "back": "let (something) cool"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷凍",
      "back": "freeze, frozen"
    },
    {
      "front": "シャッター",
      "back": "shutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "金庫",
      "back": "strong box, safe"
    },
    {
      "front": "車庫",
      "back": "garage"
    },
    {
      "front": "倉庫",
      "back": "warehouse, storehouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "心臓",
      "back": "heart"
    },
    {
      "front": "まれ",
      "back": "rareness"
    },
    {
      "front": "快晴",
      "back": "clear and fine weather"
    },
    {
      "front": "最適",
      "back": "optimum, best"
    },
    {
      "front": "適度",
      "back": "moderate, proper"
    },
    {
      "front": "適用",
      "back": "application"
    },
    {
      "front": "適当",
      "back": "suitable, appropriate"
    },
    {
      "front": "適切",
      "back": "appropriate, adequate"
    },
    {
      "front": "適する",
      "back": "suit, be suitable"
    },
    {
      "front": "スマート",
      "back": "sophisticated, skillful"
    },
    {
      "front": "湿気",
      "back": "humidity, dampness"
    },
    {
      "front": "湿度",
      "back": "humidity"
    },
    {
      "front": "湿る",
      "back": "get damp, get wet"
    },
    {
      "front": "湿っぽい",
      "back": "damp, gloomy"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンクール",
      "back": "contest, competition (mainly in arts)"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚染",
      "back": "pollution, contamination"
    },
    {
      "front": "景気",
      "back": "economic conditions"
    },
    {
      "front": "風景",
      "back": "scenery, landscape"
    },
    {
      "front": "めでたい",
      "back": "happy, fortunate"
    },
    {
      "front": "影",
      "back": "shadow, shade"
    },
    {
      "front": "撮影",
      "back": "photographing, shoot"
    },
    {
      "front": "響く",
      "back": "reverberate, vibrate"
    },
    {
      "front": "国境",
      "back": "national border"
    },
    {
      "front": "境界",
      "back": "boundary, border"
    },
    {
      "front": "環境",
      "back": "environment, surroundings"
    },
    {
      "front": "境",
      "back": "boundary, border"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダイヤモンド",
      "back": "diamond"
    },
    {
      "front": "客観的",
      "back": "objective"
    },
    {
      "front": "観客",
      "back": "audience, spectator"
    },
    {
      "front": "主観的",
      "back": "subjective"
    },
    {
      "front": "観察",
      "back": "observation"
    },
    {
      "front": "モーター",
      "back": "motor, engine"
    },
    {
      "front": "日光",
      "back": "sunshine, sunlight"
    },
    {
      "front": "観光",
      "back": "sightseeing"
    },
    {
      "front": "光",
      "back": "light"
    },
    {
      "front": "測定",
      "back": "measure"
    },
    {
      "front": "観測",
      "back": "observation"
    },
    {
      "front": "測る",
      "back": "measure (length, depth, distance or dimensions)"
    },
    {
      "front": "メーター",
      "back": "meter"
    },
    {
      "front": "宇宙",
      "back": "universe, space"
    },
    {
      "front": "衛生的",
      "back": "sanitary, hygienic"
    },
    {
      "front": "衛星",
      "back": "satellite"
    },
    {
      "front": "電球",
      "back": "light bulb"
    },
    {
      "front": "プロ野球",
      "back": "professional baseball"
    },
    {
      "front": "球",
      "back": "globe, ball"
    },
    {
      "front": "リットル",
      "back": "liter"
    },
    {
      "front": "振り返る",
      "back": "turn one's head, look back on"
    },
    {
      "front": "神道",
      "back": "Shinto"
    },
    {
      "front": "神様",
      "back": "god"
    },
    {
      "front": "神経",
      "back": "nerves"
    },
    {
      "front": "神",
      "back": "god"
    },
    {
      "front": "ボーイ",
      "back": "waiter, porter"
    },
    {
      "front": "精算",
      "back": "settlement of accounts, adjustment"
    },
    {
      "front": "精神",
      "back": "mind, mentality"
    },
    {
      "front": "ヨット",
      "back": "sailboat, yacht"
    },
    {
      "front": "貴重品",
      "back": "valuables"
    },
    {
      "front": "貴重",
      "back": "precious, valuable"
    },
    {
      "front": "貴い",
      "back": "precious, valuable"
    },
    {
      "front": "足跡",
      "back": "footprint, footmark"
    },
    {
      "front": "跡",
      "back": "trace, imprint"
    },
    {
      "front": "好奇心",
      "back": "curiosity"
    },
    {
      "front": "奇跡",
      "back": "miracle"
    },
    {
      "front": "リボン",
      "back": "ribbon"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄り道",
      "back": "stopping by, going out of the way"
    },
    {
      "front": "近寄る",
      "back": "go near, approach"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄り集まる",
      "back": "gather, get together"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄せる",
      "back": "draw (something) near"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄りかかる",
      "back": "lean against something"
    },
    {
      "front": "チョーク",
      "back": "chalk"
    },
    {
      "front": "歴史的",
      "back": "historical"
    },
    {
      "front": "王様",
      "back": "king"
    },
    {
      "front": "王",
      "back": "king"
    },
    {
      "front": "ノック",
      "back": "knock"
    },
    {
      "front": "建て前",
      "back": "one's public stance"
    },
    {
      "front": "建築",
      "back": "construction (of a building or structure)"
    },
    {
      "front": "構造",
      "back": "construction, structure"
    },
    {
      "front": "結構",
      "back": "all right, no thank you"
    },
    {
      "front": "構成",
      "back": "composition, organization"
    },
    {
      "front": "構う",
      "back": "care, bother"
    },
    {
      "front": "ものすごい",
      "back": "tremendous"
    },
    {
      "front": "地位",
      "back": "position, status"
    },
    {
      "front": "単位",
      "back": "unit, credit"
    },
    {
      "front": "位",
      "back": "rank, dignity"
    },
    {
      "front": "アクセント",
      "back": "accent, stress"
    },
    {
      "front": "離れる",
      "back": "get away from (someone/something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "離す",
      "back": "set (something) apart, let go (of)"
    },
    {
      "front": "オルガン",
      "back": "organ (music)"
    },
    {
      "front": "停電",
      "back": "blackout, power failure"
    },
    {
      "front": "停止",
      "back": "stop, suspension"
    },
    {
      "front": "一周",
      "back": "going round, circle"
    },
    {
      "front": "周り",
      "back": "vicinity, surroundings"
    },
    {
      "front": "周囲",
      "back": "circumference, surroundings"
    },
    {
      "front": "囲む",
      "back": "surround, encircle"
    },
    {
      "front": "雰囲気",
      "back": "atmosphere, mood"
    },
    {
      "front": "囲碁",
      "back": "go (game)"
    },
    {
      "front": "もうける",
      "back": "make a profit"
    },
    {
      "front": "横切る",
      "back": "cut across"
    },
    {
      "front": "横顔",
      "back": "side profile"
    },
    {
      "front": "断水",
      "back": "water stoppage"
    },
    {
      "front": "断定",
      "back": "decision, conclusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "油断",
      "back": "inattention, carelessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "横断",
      "back": "crossing, traversing"
    },
    {
      "front": "むける",
      "back": "come off, peel"
    },
    {
      "front": "継続",
      "back": "continuation, succession"
    },
    {
      "front": "ヘリコプター",
      "back": "helicopter"
    },
    {
      "front": "幅広い",
      "back": "wide, profound"
    },
    {
      "front": "幅",
      "back": "width, breadth"
    },
    {
      "front": "州",
      "back": "state, province"
    },
    {
      "front": "大陸",
      "back": "continent"
    },
    {
      "front": "陸上",
      "back": "land, shore"
    },
    {
      "front": "離陸",
      "back": "takeoff"
    },
    {
      "front": "陸",
      "back": "land, shore"
    },
    {
      "front": "陸",
      "back": "land, shore"
    },
    {
      "front": "南極",
      "back": "the South Pole"
    },
    {
      "front": "北極",
      "back": "North Pole"
    },
    {
      "front": "消極的",
      "back": "negative, passive"
    },
    {
      "front": "はめる",
      "back": "put (something) into a hole, frame etc."
    },
    {
      "front": "先端",
      "back": "end, tip"
    },
    {
      "front": "最先端",
      "back": "cutting edge, forefront"
    },
    {
      "front": "端",
      "back": "end, edge"
    },
    {
      "front": "百貨店",
      "back": "department store"
    },
    {
      "front": "貨物",
      "back": "freight, cargo"
    },
    {
      "front": "ほえる",
      "back": "bark, roar"
    },
    {
      "front": "輸入",
      "back": "import"
    },
    {
      "front": "輸出",
      "back": "export"
    },
    {
      "front": "輸送",
      "back": "transport, ship"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンセント",
      "back": "outlet"
    },
    {
      "front": "回復",
      "back": "recovery, recuperation"
    },
    {
      "front": "体操",
      "back": "gymnastics, physical exercise"
    },
    {
      "front": "操作",
      "back": "operation, manipulation"
    },
    {
      "front": "縦書き",
      "back": "vertical writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "縦",
      "back": "lengthways, vertical"
    },
    {
      "front": "ロッカー",
      "back": "locker"
    },
    {
      "front": "滞在",
      "back": "stay"
    },
    {
      "front": "渋滞",
      "back": "traffic jam, backup"
    },
    {
      "front": "地帯",
      "back": "zone, area"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱帯",
      "back": "tropics"
    },
    {
      "front": "温帯",
      "back": "temperate zone"
    },
    {
      "front": "帯",
      "back": "belt, sash"
    },
    {
      "front": "書留",
      "back": "registered mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "見守る",
      "back": "watch, keep watch over"
    },
    {
      "front": "留守番",
      "back": "looking after the house while others are out"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひねる",
      "back": "twist, turn"
    },
    {
      "front": "宛先",
      "back": "postal address"
    },
    {
      "front": "宛名",
      "back": "name of recipient, addressee"
    },
    {
      "front": "後戻り",
      "back": "turning back, retreat"
    },
    {
      "front": "払い戻す",
      "back": "pay back, reimburse"
    },
    {
      "front": "戻す",
      "back": "put (something) back"
    },
    {
      "front": "バケツ",
      "back": "bucket"
    },
    {
      "front": "資源",
      "back": "resources"
    },
    {
      "front": "起き上がる",
      "back": "get up"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝転ぶ",
      "back": "lie down"
    },
    {
      "front": "早寝",
      "back": "going to bed early"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝過ごす",
      "back": "oversleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝室",
      "back": "bedroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝かす",
      "back": "put (someone) to bed"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひきょう",
      "back": "playing dirty, mean"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷静",
      "back": "cool, calm"
    },
    {
      "front": "静まる",
      "back": "become quiet, calm down"
    },
    {
      "front": "ことわざ",
      "back": "proverb, (common) saying"
    },
    {
      "front": "両手",
      "back": "both hands"
    },
    {
      "front": "両面",
      "back": "both faces, both sides"
    },
    {
      "front": "両者",
      "back": "both parties, both sides"
    },
    {
      "front": "片方",
      "back": "one side, the other one"
    },
    {
      "front": "片手",
      "back": "one hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "なでる",
      "back": "stroke, pat"
    },
    {
      "front": "両側",
      "back": "both sides"
    },
    {
      "front": "片側",
      "back": "one side"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏口",
      "back": "back door"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏門",
      "back": "back gate"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏切る",
      "back": "betray"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏表",
      "back": "inside-out, front and back"
    },
    {
      "front": "ためる",
      "back": "collect and store (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "項目",
      "back": "item, topic"
    },
    {
      "front": "要項",
      "back": "important points"
    },
    {
      "front": "目印",
      "back": "landmark, sign (to spot)"
    },
    {
      "front": "印象",
      "back": "impression"
    },
    {
      "front": "印",
      "back": "mark, symbol"
    },
    {
      "front": "印刷",
      "back": "printing"
    },
    {
      "front": "矢印",
      "back": "arrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "くむ",
      "back": "collect, scoop up"
    },
    {
      "front": "月刊",
      "back": "published monthly"
    },
    {
      "front": "週刊",
      "back": "published weekly"
    },
    {
      "front": "出版",
      "back": "publishing, publication"
    },
    {
      "front": "出版社",
      "back": "publishing company, publisher"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちぎる",
      "back": "tear, tear off"
    },
    {
      "front": "細長い",
      "back": "long and thin, long and narrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "載る",
      "back": "appear in print, be published"
    },
    {
      "front": "面積",
      "back": "area, square measure"
    },
    {
      "front": "積極的",
      "back": "active, aggressive"
    },
    {
      "front": "積む",
      "back": "pile up, load"
    },
    {
      "front": "いけない",
      "back": "wrong, must not"
    },
    {
      "front": "通訳",
      "back": "interpreting, interpreter"
    },
    {
      "front": "申し訳",
      "back": "excuse, apology"
    },
    {
      "front": "申し訳ない",
      "back": "sorry, inexcusable"
    },
    {
      "front": "翻訳",
      "back": "translation"
    },
    {
      "front": "誤り",
      "back": "error, mistake"
    },
    {
      "front": "ささやく",
      "back": "whisper"
    },
    {
      "front": "日付け",
      "back": "date"
    },
    {
      "front": "付け足す",
      "back": "add on, append"
    },
    {
      "front": "後片付け",
      "back": "cleaning up"
    },
    {
      "front": "付き合い",
      "back": "social obligation"
    },
    {
      "front": "付近",
      "back": "neighborhood, vicinity"
    },
    {
      "front": "近付ける",
      "back": "bring (something) close"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い付く",
      "back": "think of, hit upon"
    },
    {
      "front": "追い付く",
      "back": "catch up with"
    },
    {
      "front": "傷付ける",
      "back": "hurt (someone), damage (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "噛み付く",
      "back": "bite"
    },
    {
      "front": "どっと",
      "back": "burst (out laughing etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ペンキ",
      "back": "paint"
    },
    {
      "front": "金属",
      "back": "metal"
    },
    {
      "front": "属する",
      "back": "belong, be a member (of)"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰省",
      "back": "homecoming, going (back) to one's hometown"
    },
    {
      "front": "大蔵省",
      "back": "Ministry of Finance"
    },
    {
      "front": "外務省",
      "back": "Ministry of Foreign Affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "反省",
      "back": "reflection of one's past conduct, repentance"
    },
    {
      "front": "省く",
      "back": "omit"
    },
    {
      "front": "プラットホーム",
      "back": "platform"
    },
    {
      "front": "省略",
      "back": "omission, abbreviation"
    },
    {
      "front": "略す",
      "back": "abbreviate, omit"
    },
    {
      "front": "略",
      "back": "abbreviation"
    },
    {
      "front": "信念",
      "back": "belief, conviction"
    },
    {
      "front": "記念",
      "back": "commemoration, memory"
    },
    {
      "front": "くず",
      "back": "waste, scrap"
    },
    {
      "front": "含む",
      "back": "contain, include"
    },
    {
      "front": "含める",
      "back": "include"
    },
    {
      "front": "道順",
      "back": "route, directions"
    },
    {
      "front": "順調",
      "back": "favorable condition, smooth progress"
    },
    {
      "front": "順位",
      "back": "order, rank"
    },
    {
      "front": "順",
      "back": "order, sequence"
    },
    {
      "front": "順々に",
      "back": "by turns, one at a time"
    },
    {
      "front": "あちらこちら",
      "back": "all over, everywhere"
    },
    {
      "front": "順序",
      "back": "order"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆",
      "back": "reverse, opposite"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆らう",
      "back": "go against, rebel"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆さ",
      "back": "reverse, inversion"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆さま",
      "back": "upside-down, reverse"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひとりでに",
      "back": "automatically, by oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "行列",
      "back": "queue, line"
    },
    {
      "front": "列車",
      "back": "train"
    },
    {
      "front": "列島",
      "back": "archipelago"
    },
    {
      "front": "列",
      "back": "row, line"
    },
    {
      "front": "やっつける",
      "back": "beat up"
    },
    {
      "front": "例年",
      "back": "typical year, average year"
    },
    {
      "front": "例外",
      "back": "exception"
    },
    {
      "front": "用例",
      "back": "example"
    },
    {
      "front": "例題",
      "back": "example problem"
    },
    {
      "front": "実例",
      "back": "example, instance"
    },
    {
      "front": "例える",
      "back": "compare, liken"
    },
    {
      "front": "余分",
      "back": "excess, extra"
    },
    {
      "front": "余計",
      "back": "unnecessary, extra"
    },
    {
      "front": "余り",
      "back": "remainder, leftover"
    },
    {
      "front": "余裕",
      "back": "room, leeway (time, money etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "とっさに",
      "back": "at once, promptly"
    },
    {
      "front": "中途",
      "back": "halfway"
    },
    {
      "front": "用途",
      "back": "usage, purpose of use"
    },
    {
      "front": "削除",
      "back": "deletion, elimination"
    },
    {
      "front": "削る",
      "back": "scrape, cut back"
    },
    {
      "front": "既製",
      "back": "ready-made, ready-to-wear"
    },
    {
      "front": "既に",
      "back": "already"
    },
    {
      "front": "時刻",
      "back": "time"
    },
    {
      "front": "深刻",
      "back": "serious, grave"
    },
    {
      "front": "刻む",
      "back": "cut, chop"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふるさと",
      "back": "hometown, birthplace"
    },
    {
      "front": "締め切る",
      "back": "close, fix a deadline"
    },
    {
      "front": "締まる",
      "back": "become tight, be firm"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふわふわ",
      "back": "soft and fluffy"
    },
    {
      "front": "休養",
      "back": "rest, recreation"
    },
    {
      "front": "教養",
      "back": "culture, education"
    },
    {
      "front": "栄養",
      "back": "nutrition, nourishment"
    },
    {
      "front": "よる",
      "back": "be caused by, be due to"
    },
    {
      "front": "豊富",
      "back": "abundant, plentiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "目茶苦茶",
      "back": "in a mess, chaotic"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦情",
      "back": "complaint on actual damage, loss, etc. (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦心",
      "back": "pains, efforts"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦痛",
      "back": "pain, stress"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦しむ",
      "back": "suffer"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦しみ",
      "back": "suffering, pain"
    },
    {
      "front": "さびる",
      "back": "rust, get rusty"
    },
    {
      "front": "働き",
      "back": "work, function"
    },
    {
      "front": "疲れ",
      "back": "fatigue, exhaustion"
    },
    {
      "front": "労働",
      "back": "labor, work"
    },
    {
      "front": "労働者",
      "back": "laborer, worker"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦労",
      "back": "difficulty, hardship"
    },
    {
      "front": "しわ",
      "back": "wrinkle, ruck"
    },
    {
      "front": "貧しい",
      "back": "poor, impoverished"
    },
    {
      "front": "貧乏人",
      "back": "poor person"
    },
    {
      "front": "甘やかす",
      "back": "be indulgent to, spoil"
    },
    {
      "front": "辛い",
      "back": "hard, tough"
    },
    {
      "front": "辛い",
      "back": "harsh, severe"
    },
    {
      "front": "不幸せ",
      "back": "unhappy, unfortunate"
    },
    {
      "front": "幸運",
      "back": "good fortune, good luck"
    },
    {
      "front": "幸い",
      "back": "fortunately, thankfully"
    },
    {
      "front": "幸福",
      "back": "happy, fortunate"
    },
    {
      "front": "砂",
      "back": "sand"
    },
    {
      "front": "砂漠",
      "back": "desert"
    },
    {
      "front": "範囲",
      "back": "range, scope"
    },
    {
      "front": "模様",
      "back": "pattern, design"
    },
    {
      "front": "村",
      "back": "village"
    },
    {
      "front": "農家",
      "back": "farm"
    },
    {
      "front": "農村",
      "back": "farming village, agricultural community"
    },
    {
      "front": "農業",
      "back": "agriculture"
    },
    {
      "front": "農民",
      "back": "peasant, farmer"
    },
    {
      "front": "よこす",
      "back": "send, hand over"
    },
    {
      "front": "薄暗い",
      "back": "gloomy, dim"
    },
    {
      "front": "薄着",
      "back": "light clothing"
    },
    {
      "front": "薄める",
      "back": "dilute (something), water down"
    },
    {
      "front": "気圧",
      "back": "atmospheric pressure"
    },
    {
      "front": "低気圧",
      "back": "low pressure, atmospheric depression"
    },
    {
      "front": "高気圧",
      "back": "high atmospheric pressure"
    },
    {
      "front": "縮小",
      "back": "reduction, cutdown"
    },
    {
      "front": "縮める",
      "back": "reduce (time, size etc.), shorten"
    },
    {
      "front": "縮む",
      "back": "shrink, contract"
    },
    {
      "front": "縮み",
      "back": "shrinkage"
    },
    {
      "front": "やたらに",
      "back": "frequently, persistently"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き伸ばす",
      "back": "stretch out, enlarge"
    },
    {
      "front": "追伸",
      "back": "P.S."
    },
    {
      "front": "伸ばす",
      "back": "stretch (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "デモ",
      "back": "demonstration"
    },
    {
      "front": "倍",
      "back": "double, times"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り越し",
      "back": "riding past one's stop"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り越える",
      "back": "overcome, get over"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り越す",
      "back": "miss one's station"
    },
    {
      "front": "追い越す",
      "back": "outrun, overtake"
    },
    {
      "front": "越す",
      "back": "go across, pass"
    },
    {
      "front": "めいめい",
      "back": "each, individually"
    },
    {
      "front": "追い抜く",
      "back": "pass, overtake"
    },
    {
      "front": "抜く",
      "back": "pull (something) out"
    },
    {
      "front": "抜ける",
      "back": "come out, leave"
    },
    {
      "front": "栓抜き",
      "back": "bottle opener"
    },
    {
      "front": "昇る",
      "back": "rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちぎれる",
      "back": "be torn off, come off"
    },
    {
      "front": "膨らむ",
      "back": "swell, inflate"
    },
    {
      "front": "改札",
      "back": "ticket gate"
    },
    {
      "front": "札",
      "back": "bill, paper money"
    },
    {
      "front": "札",
      "back": "sign, tag"
    },
    {
      "front": "ほこり",
      "back": "dust"
    },
    {
      "front": "感謝",
      "back": "gratitude, thanks"
    },
    {
      "front": "射す",
      "back": "shine on"
    },
    {
      "front": "日程",
      "back": "schedule"
    },
    {
      "front": "行程",
      "back": "distance, journey"
    },
    {
      "front": "程度",
      "back": "degree, extent"
    },
    {
      "front": "過程",
      "back": "process, course"
    },
    {
      "front": "課程",
      "back": "course, curriculum"
    },
    {
      "front": "程",
      "back": "extent, limit"
    },
    {
      "front": "女優",
      "back": "actress"
    },
    {
      "front": "優勝",
      "back": "championship"
    },
    {
      "front": "優れる",
      "back": "be superior to, be excellent"
    },
    {
      "front": "優秀",
      "back": "excellent, exceptional"
    },
    {
      "front": "とがる",
      "back": "be sharp"
    },
    {
      "front": "透明",
      "back": "transparent, clear"
    },
    {
      "front": "透き通る",
      "back": "become transparent, become clear"
    },
    {
      "front": "半導体",
      "back": "semiconductor"
    },
    {
      "front": "指導",
      "back": "guide, instruction"
    },
    {
      "front": "のんき",
      "back": "easy-going, laid-back"
    },
    {
      "front": "失望",
      "back": "disappointment, loss of hope"
    },
    {
      "front": "希望",
      "back": "hope, wish"
    },
    {
      "front": "望む",
      "back": "want, hope"
    },
    {
      "front": "望み",
      "back": "desire, hope"
    },
    {
      "front": "はしご",
      "back": "ladder"
    },
    {
      "front": "意志",
      "back": "will, volition"
    },
    {
      "front": "努める",
      "back": "endeavor, make efforts"
    },
    {
      "front": "独り言",
      "back": "to talk to oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "独立",
      "back": "independence, self-reliance"
    },
    {
      "front": "独特",
      "back": "unique, distinct"
    },
    {
      "front": "もうかる",
      "back": "make a profit, be profitable"
    },
    {
      "front": "中身",
      "back": "content, interior"
    },
    {
      "front": "身長",
      "back": "stature, height"
    },
    {
      "front": "全身",
      "back": "the whole body"
    },
    {
      "front": "心身",
      "back": "mind and body"
    },
    {
      "front": "受け身",
      "back": "being passive"
    },
    {
      "front": "身の回り",
      "back": "everyday affair, one's association"
    },
    {
      "front": "自身",
      "back": "self"
    },
    {
      "front": "身",
      "back": "body, oneself, one's status"
    },
    {
      "front": "占める",
      "back": "occupy, hold"
    },
    {
      "front": "ろうそく",
      "back": "candle"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲人",
      "back": "go-between, matchmaker"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲間",
      "back": "comrade, peer"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲良く",
      "back": "harmoniously, getting along"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲直り",
      "back": "reconciliation, making up"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲",
      "back": "relationship"
    },
    {
      "front": "照らす",
      "back": "illuminate, shine on"
    },
    {
      "front": "照る",
      "back": "shine, blaze"
    },
    {
      "front": "にわかに",
      "back": "rapidly, at once"
    },
    {
      "front": "夫人",
      "back": "wife, Mrs."
    },
    {
      "front": "工夫",
      "back": "contrivance, use of one's ingenuity"
    },
    {
      "front": "夫妻",
      "back": "husband and wife, Mr. and Mrs."
    },
    {
      "front": "婦人",
      "back": "woman, lady"
    },
    {
      "front": "主婦",
      "back": "housewife"
    },
    {
      "front": "エチケット",
      "back": "etiquette"
    },
    {
      "front": "相互",
      "back": "mutual, reciprocal"
    },
    {
      "front": "お互い",
      "back": "each other"
    },
    {
      "front": "互い",
      "back": "each other"
    },
    {
      "front": "皆",
      "back": "all, everybody"
    },
    {
      "front": "たく",
      "back": "make a fire (stove etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "我が家",
      "back": "one's home"
    },
    {
      "front": "我が国",
      "back": "our country"
    },
    {
      "front": "我々",
      "back": "we"
    },
    {
      "front": "年齢",
      "back": "age"
    },
    {
      "front": "高齢",
      "back": "advanced age, old age"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛情",
      "back": "love, affection"
    },
    {
      "front": "せい",
      "back": "cause, blame"
    },
    {
      "front": "恋人",
      "back": "boyfriend or girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "front": "初恋",
      "back": "first love"
    },
    {
      "front": "失恋",
      "back": "broken heart"
    },
    {
      "front": "恋",
      "back": "love, romance"
    },
    {
      "front": "ロック",
      "back": "rock (music)"
    },
    {
      "front": "延長",
      "back": "extension, prolongation"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き延ばす",
      "back": "extend, prolong"
    },
    {
      "front": "延期",
      "back": "postponement, deferment"
    },
    {
      "front": "延びる",
      "back": "extend, be postponed"
    },
    {
      "front": "祝う",
      "back": "celebrate, congratulate"
    },
    {
      "front": "祝い",
      "back": "celebration, congratulation"
    },
    {
      "front": "単純",
      "back": "simple, uncomplicated"
    },
    {
      "front": "純粋",
      "back": "pure, unmixed"
    },
    {
      "front": "笑顔",
      "back": "smiling face, smile"
    },
    {
      "front": "笑い",
      "back": "laughter, laugh"
    },
    {
      "front": "ほほ笑む",
      "back": "smile"
    },
    {
      "front": "大喜び",
      "back": "great joy"
    },
    {
      "front": "喜び",
      "back": "joy, delight"
    },
    {
      "front": "喜ばす",
      "back": "please, make (someone) happy"
    },
    {
      "front": "キリスト",
      "back": "Christ"
    },
    {
      "front": "保護者",
      "back": "guardian, parent"
    },
    {
      "front": "弁護士",
      "back": "lawyer, attorney"
    },
    {
      "front": "看病",
      "back": "looking after a sick person"
    },
    {
      "front": "看護婦",
      "back": "female nurse"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハード",
      "back": "hard"
    },
    {
      "front": "否定",
      "back": "denial, negation"
    },
    {
      "front": "述べる",
      "back": "state, remark"
    },
    {
      "front": "裁判所",
      "back": "courthouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "裁判",
      "back": "trial, judgment"
    },
    {
      "front": "総裁",
      "back": "president, director-general"
    },
    {
      "front": "つなぐ",
      "back": "connect (someone, something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "訴える",
      "back": "sue"
    },
    {
      "front": "迷子",
      "back": "lost child, lost person"
    },
    {
      "front": "迷信",
      "back": "superstition"
    },
    {
      "front": "区域",
      "back": "zone, district"
    },
    {
      "front": "まし",
      "back": "better, preferable"
    },
    {
      "front": "疑問",
      "back": "question, doubt"
    },
    {
      "front": "疑う",
      "back": "doubt, suspect"
    },
    {
      "front": "疑い",
      "back": "doubt, suspicion"
    },
    {
      "front": "疑わしい",
      "back": "doubtful, suspicious"
    },
    {
      "front": "謎",
      "back": "puzzle, mystery"
    },
    {
      "front": "なぜか",
      "back": "for some reason"
    },
    {
      "front": "著者",
      "back": "author, writer"
    },
    {
      "front": "著す",
      "back": "write (a book)"
    },
    {
      "front": "人権",
      "back": "human rights"
    },
    {
      "front": "権利",
      "back": "right, privilege"
    },
    {
      "front": "のぞく",
      "back": "peep, look in"
    },
    {
      "front": "賞品",
      "back": "prize, award"
    },
    {
      "front": "観賞",
      "back": "ornamental"
    },
    {
      "front": "賞",
      "back": "prize, award"
    },
    {
      "front": "ノーベル賞",
      "back": "Nobel Prize"
    },
    {
      "front": "おかげ",
      "back": "with the help of, thanks to"
    },
    {
      "front": "財産",
      "back": "fortune, asset"
    },
    {
      "front": "修正",
      "back": "correction, revision"
    },
    {
      "front": "終了",
      "back": "end, termination"
    },
    {
      "front": "完了",
      "back": "completion"
    },
    {
      "front": "プライド",
      "back": "pride"
    },
    {
      "front": "承知",
      "back": "consent, acknowledgment"
    },
    {
      "front": "承認",
      "back": "approval, recognition"
    },
    {
      "front": "納める",
      "back": "pay (tax, fee etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "不得意",
      "back": "not good at, weak"
    },
    {
      "front": "取得",
      "back": "acquisition"
    },
    {
      "front": "納得",
      "back": "to fully understand and accept"
    },
    {
      "front": "得",
      "back": "advantage, gain"
    },
    {
      "front": "得する",
      "back": "profitable, beneficial"
    },
    {
      "front": "得る",
      "back": "obtain, gain"
    },
    {
      "front": "つまむ",
      "back": "snack on"
    },
    {
      "front": "めくる",
      "back": "turn over"
    },
    {
      "front": "損害",
      "back": "damage, harm"
    },
    {
      "front": "損する",
      "back": "lose, suffer loss"
    },
    {
      "front": "損",
      "back": "loss, damage"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼き肉",
      "back": "grilled meat, barbecued meat"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼きそば",
      "back": "pan-fried noodles"
    },
    {
      "front": "グラウンド",
      "back": "field"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾燥",
      "back": "drying up, desiccation"
    },
    {
      "front": "幹",
      "back": "tree trunk"
    },
    {
      "front": "水素",
      "back": "hydrogen"
    },
    {
      "front": "素直",
      "back": "honest, straightforward"
    },
    {
      "front": "酸素",
      "back": "oxygen"
    },
    {
      "front": "ファックス",
      "back": "fax"
    },
    {
      "front": "岩",
      "back": "rock"
    },
    {
      "front": "解散",
      "back": "breakup, dissolution"
    },
    {
      "front": "散らかす",
      "back": "make a mess"
    },
    {
      "front": "散らかる",
      "back": "be in a mess, lie scattered"
    },
    {
      "front": "散る",
      "back": "scatter, fall"
    },
    {
      "front": "散らばる",
      "back": "be scattered"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぱっと",
      "back": "suddenly, quickly"
    },
    {
      "front": "植木",
      "back": "garden plant"
    },
    {
      "front": "田植え",
      "back": "rice planting"
    },
    {
      "front": "植物",
      "back": "plant, vegetation"
    },
    {
      "front": "植物園",
      "back": "botanical garden"
    },
    {
      "front": "植える",
      "back": "plant"
    },
    {
      "front": "パンダ",
      "back": "panda"
    },
    {
      "front": "大根",
      "back": "oriental radish"
    },
    {
      "front": "根",
      "back": "root"
    },
    {
      "front": "羽根",
      "back": "feather"
    },
    {
      "front": "にこやか",
      "back": "smiling, beaming (face)"
    },
    {
      "front": "看板",
      "back": "signboard, billboard"
    },
    {
      "front": "まな板",
      "back": "chopping board"
    },
    {
      "front": "板",
      "back": "board, plank"
    },
    {
      "front": "草木",
      "back": "plants and trees"
    },
    {
      "front": "草花",
      "back": "plants and flowers"
    },
    {
      "front": "ほうれん草",
      "back": "spinach"
    },
    {
      "front": "せっかち",
      "back": "impatient, hasty"
    },
    {
      "front": "木の葉",
      "back": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
      "front": "言葉遣い",
      "back": "wording, language"
    },
    {
      "front": "話し言葉",
      "back": "spoken language"
    },
    {
      "front": "書き言葉",
      "back": "written language"
    },
    {
      "front": "葉っぱ",
      "back": "leaf"
    },
    {
      "front": "いじめ",
      "back": "bullying"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼び出す",
      "back": "call, page"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼びかける",
      "back": "call, urge"
    },
    {
      "front": "吸収",
      "back": "absorption, merger"
    },
    {
      "front": "吸い込む",
      "back": "inhale, suck in"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼吸",
      "back": "breathing, respiration"
    },
    {
      "front": "いやらしい",
      "back": "lewd, nasty"
    },
    {
      "front": "普及",
      "back": "spread, diffusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "扱う",
      "back": "handle, deal with"
    },
    {
      "front": "中級",
      "back": "middle-class, intermediate"
    },
    {
      "front": "上級",
      "back": "higher grade, advanced class"
    },
    {
      "front": "高級",
      "back": "high-ranking, high-class"
    },
    {
      "front": "初級",
      "back": "beginner class, elementary level"
    },
    {
      "front": "同級生",
      "back": "classmate"
    },
    {
      "front": "級",
      "back": "grade, class"
    },
    {
      "front": "いやいや",
      "back": "reluctantly, grudgingly"
    },
    {
      "front": "腹",
      "back": "belly"
    },
    {
      "front": "腹いっぱい",
      "back": "full stomach"
    },
    {
      "front": "つくづく",
      "back": "truly, deeply"
    },
    {
      "front": "液体",
      "back": "liquid, fluid"
    },
    {
      "front": "血液",
      "back": "blood (formal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "溶ける",
      "back": "dissolve, melt"
    },
    {
      "front": "溶かす",
      "back": "melt (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "貿易",
      "back": "(export and import) trade"
    },
    {
      "front": "容器",
      "back": "container"
    },
    {
      "front": "容易",
      "back": "easy, simple"
    },
    {
      "front": "むしろ",
      "back": "rather"
    },
    {
      "front": "骨折",
      "back": "breaking a bone"
    },
    {
      "front": "保健",
      "back": "preservation of health"
    },
    {
      "front": "診察",
      "back": "medical examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "診断",
      "back": "diagnosis"
    },
    {
      "front": "診る",
      "back": "examine (doctor)"
    },
    {
      "front": "医学",
      "back": "medical science, medicine"
    },
    {
      "front": "医療",
      "back": "medical service, healthcare"
    },
    {
      "front": "気の毒",
      "back": "pitiful, poor"
    },
    {
      "front": "有毒",
      "back": "poisonous, toxic"
    },
    {
      "front": "消毒",
      "back": "disinfection, sterilization"
    },
    {
      "front": "毒",
      "back": "poison, harm"
    },
    {
      "front": "もたらす",
      "back": "bring about, lead to"
    },
    {
      "front": "清書",
      "back": "clean copy, final copy"
    },
    {
      "front": "不潔",
      "back": "dirty, filthy"
    },
    {
      "front": "清潔",
      "back": "cleanliness, neatness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミス",
      "back": "mistake"
    },
    {
      "front": "監督",
      "back": "supervisor, film director"
    },
    {
      "front": "描く",
      "back": "depict, draw"
    },
    {
      "front": "再開",
      "back": "reopening, resumption"
    },
    {
      "front": "編集",
      "back": "editing"
    },
    {
      "front": "編む",
      "back": "knit"
    },
    {
      "front": "開放",
      "back": "open (to the public)"
    },
    {
      "front": "解放",
      "back": "release, setting free"
    },
    {
      "front": "放る",
      "back": "fling, throw"
    },
    {
      "front": "放す",
      "back": "release, free"
    },
    {
      "front": "無視",
      "back": "ignoring, disregarding"
    },
    {
      "front": "重視",
      "back": "importance, value"
    },
    {
      "front": "衣食住",
      "back": "clothing and food and housing"
    },
    {
      "front": "衣服",
      "back": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "front": "服装",
      "back": "attire, way of dressing"
    },
    {
      "front": "装置",
      "back": "equipment, device"
    },
    {
      "front": "振り仮名",
      "back": "reading aid in kana characters"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮名遣い",
      "back": "kana orthography, use of kana"
    },
    {
      "front": "送り仮名",
      "back": "kana suffix"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮定",
      "back": "assumption, supposition"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮に",
      "back": "supposing that, even if"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮",
      "back": "temporary state"
    },
    {
      "front": "銅",
      "back": "copper"
    },
    {
      "front": "演説",
      "back": "speech, address"
    },
    {
      "front": "演奏",
      "back": "musical performance"
    },
    {
      "front": "劇場",
      "back": "theater"
    },
    {
      "front": "演劇",
      "back": "drama, play"
    },
    {
      "front": "劇",
      "back": "drama, play"
    },
    {
      "front": "悲劇",
      "back": "tragedy"
    },
    {
      "front": "悲しみ",
      "back": "grief, sadness"
    },
    {
      "front": "団体",
      "back": "group, organization"
    },
    {
      "front": "団地",
      "back": "housing estate, housing complex"
    },
    {
      "front": "集団",
      "back": "group, mass"
    },
    {
      "front": "固まる",
      "back": "harden, solidify"
    },
    {
      "front": "博士",
      "back": "expert, master"
    },
    {
      "front": "博士",
      "back": "Ph.D."
    },
    {
      "front": "展開",
      "back": "development, storyline (plot)"
    },
    {
      "front": "発展",
      "back": "development, expansion"
    },
    {
      "front": "展覧会",
      "back": "exhibition"
    },
    {
      "front": "おしまい",
      "back": "end"
    },
    {
      "front": "催し",
      "back": "event"
    },
    {
      "front": "催促",
      "back": "reminding, urging"
    },
    {
      "front": "辞任",
      "back": "resignation"
    },
    {
      "front": "古典",
      "back": "classics"
    },
    {
      "front": "典型",
      "back": "model, typical"
    },
    {
      "front": "典型的",
      "back": "typical"
    },
    {
      "front": "辞典",
      "back": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "front": "リード",
      "back": "the lead, taking a lead"
    },
    {
      "front": "特殊",
      "back": "special, unique"
    },
    {
      "front": "特徴",
      "back": "distinctive feature, characteristic"
    },
    {
      "front": "微妙",
      "back": "subtle, delicate"
    },
    {
      "front": "免税",
      "back": "tax exemption"
    },
    {
      "front": "許可",
      "back": "permission, approval"
    },
    {
      "front": "免許",
      "back": "license, qualification"
    },
    {
      "front": "訓読み",
      "back": "Japanese reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "訓練",
      "back": "training, drill"
    },
    {
      "front": "訓",
      "back": "Japanese reading of kanji"
    },
    {
      "front": "オーバー",
      "back": "exaggerated, overly done"
    },
    {
      "front": "名詞",
      "back": "noun"
    },
    {
      "front": "代名詞",
      "back": "pronoun"
    },
    {
      "front": "動詞",
      "back": "verb"
    },
    {
      "front": "形容詞",
      "back": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "front": "副詞",
      "back": "adverb"
    },
    {
      "front": "つながる",
      "back": "be connected, be linked"
    },
    {
      "front": "司会",
      "back": "master of ceremonies, host"
    },
    {
      "front": "休講",
      "back": "cancellation of a lecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "講義",
      "back": "lecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "講演",
      "back": "lecture"
    },
    {
      "front": "講堂",
      "back": "lecture hall, auditorium"
    },
    {
      "front": "よほど",
      "back": "very, by far"
    },
    {
      "front": "師走",
      "back": "December"
    },
    {
      "front": "技師",
      "back": "engineer, technician"
    },
    {
      "front": "医師",
      "back": "doctor, physician"
    },
    {
      "front": "講師",
      "back": "lecturer, instructor"
    },
    {
      "front": "手伝い",
      "back": "help, assistance"
    },
    {
      "front": "お手伝い",
      "back": "help, assistance"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝統",
      "back": "tradition"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝染",
      "back": "contagion, infection"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝わる",
      "back": "be transmitted, come from"
    },
    {
      "front": "宣伝",
      "back": "publicity, advertisement"
    },
    {
      "front": "小鳥",
      "back": "small bird"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼き鳥",
      "back": "skewered chicken"
    },
    {
      "front": "鳴らす",
      "back": "make a sound with (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "泣き顔",
      "back": "crying face"
    },
    {
      "front": "大声",
      "back": "loud voice"
    },
    {
      "front": "話し声",
      "back": "talking voice"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌声",
      "back": "singing voice"
    },
    {
      "front": "泣き声",
      "back": "tearful voice, sound of crying"
    },
    {
      "front": "笑い声",
      "back": "laughter"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒音",
      "back": "noise"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒ぎ",
      "back": "clamor, commotion"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒がしい",
      "back": "noisy"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒々しい",
      "back": "noisy, rowdy"
    },
    {
      "front": "テープ",
      "back": "tape"
    },
    {
      "front": "飼う",
      "back": "keep (an animal)"
    },
    {
      "front": "名刺",
      "back": "business card, calling card"
    },
    {
      "front": "刺さる",
      "back": "stick, get stuck"
    },
    {
      "front": "急激",
      "back": "rapid, abrupt"
    },
    {
      "front": "感激",
      "back": "deep emotion, to be touched"
    },
    {
      "front": "刺激",
      "back": "stimulus"
    },
    {
      "front": "興味",
      "back": "interest"
    },
    {
      "front": "驚かす",
      "back": "surprise"
    },
    {
      "front": "至る所",
      "back": "everywhere, all over"
    },
    {
      "front": "至急",
      "back": "urgent"
    },
    {
      "front": "至る",
      "back": "come to, reach"
    },
    {
      "front": "一致",
      "back": "agreement, match"
    },
    {
      "front": "致す",
      "back": "do (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "到着",
      "back": "arrival"
    },
    {
      "front": "斜め",
      "back": "diagonal, slant"
    },
    {
      "front": "傾向",
      "back": "tendency, disposition"
    },
    {
      "front": "傾く",
      "back": "decline, go down"
    },
    {
      "front": "坂",
      "back": "slope, hill"
    },
    {
      "front": "狭まる",
      "back": "get narrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "狭める",
      "back": "narrow (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビデオテープ",
      "back": "videotape"
    },
    {
      "front": "硬さ",
      "back": "hardness"
    },
    {
      "front": "柔道",
      "back": "judo"
    },
    {
      "front": "張り切る",
      "back": "go all out, make efforts"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲張り",
      "back": "greedy"
    },
    {
      "front": "主張",
      "back": "claim, assertion"
    },
    {
      "front": "拡張",
      "back": "expansion, extension"
    },
    {
      "front": "張る",
      "back": "strain, be stretched"
    },
    {
      "front": "突然",
      "back": "suddenly"
    },
    {
      "front": "突っ込む",
      "back": "thrust in, run into"
    },
    {
      "front": "煙突",
      "back": "chimney, smokestack"
    },
    {
      "front": "追突",
      "back": "collision"
    },
    {
      "front": "衝突",
      "back": "collision, conflict"
    },
    {
      "front": "突く",
      "back": "thrust, poke"
    },
    {
      "front": "触れる",
      "back": "touch, come in contact with"
    },
    {
      "front": "避ける",
      "back": "avoid, evade"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍",
      "back": "army, troops"
    },
    {
      "front": "ろくに",
      "back": "hardly, barely"
    },
    {
      "front": "自衛隊",
      "back": "Self Defense Forces"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍隊",
      "back": "army, military"
    },
    {
      "front": "兵隊",
      "back": "soldier, troops"
    },
    {
      "front": "ズボン",
      "back": "trousers, pants"
    },
    {
      "front": "武器",
      "back": "weapon, arms"
    },
    {
      "front": "武士",
      "back": "warrior"
    },
    {
      "front": "弾",
      "back": "bullet"
    },
    {
      "front": "真ん丸",
      "back": "perfect circle, perfectly round"
    },
    {
      "front": "カセットテープ",
      "back": "cassette tape"
    },
    {
      "front": "専攻",
      "back": "major"
    },
    {
      "front": "攻める",
      "back": "make an attack, assault"
    },
    {
      "front": "攻撃",
      "back": "attack, assault"
    },
    {
      "front": "撃つ",
      "back": "fire, shoot"
    },
    {
      "front": "爆発",
      "back": "explosion, eruption"
    },
    {
      "front": "乱暴",
      "back": "violence"
    },
    {
      "front": "暴落",
      "back": "plunge, crash"
    },
    {
      "front": "暴れる",
      "back": "act violently, rage about"
    },
    {
      "front": "気絶",
      "back": "fainting"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶えず",
      "back": "constantly, unremittingly"
    },
    {
      "front": "消防車",
      "back": "fire engine"
    },
    {
      "front": "防止",
      "back": "prevention, determent"
    },
    {
      "front": "消防",
      "back": "fire fighting, fire prevention"
    },
    {
      "front": "予防",
      "back": "prevention, protection"
    },
    {
      "front": "防ぐ",
      "back": "prevent"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひび",
      "back": "crack"
    },
    {
      "front": "好き嫌い",
      "back": "likes and dislikes, taste"
    },
    {
      "front": "不機嫌",
      "back": "in a bad mood"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫌がる",
      "back": "dislike, hate"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫌う",
      "back": "dislike, hate"
    },
    {
      "front": "徹夜",
      "back": "staying up all night"
    },
    {
      "front": "徹底的",
      "back": "thorough"
    },
    {
      "front": "底",
      "back": "bottom, depth"
    },
    {
      "front": "抵抗",
      "back": "resistance"
    },
    {
      "front": "敵",
      "back": "enemy, foe"
    },
    {
      "front": "威張る",
      "back": "put on airs, be arrogant"
    },
    {
      "front": "勢い",
      "back": "vigor, momentum"
    },
    {
      "front": "こたつ",
      "back": "table with an electric heater and a coverlet"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐れる",
      "back": "fear, worry"
    },
    {
      "front": "怖がる",
      "back": "be afraid of, fear"
    },
    {
      "front": "体系",
      "back": "system, organization"
    },
    {
      "front": "文系",
      "back": "liberal arts, humanities"
    },
    {
      "front": "理系",
      "back": "science"
    },
    {
      "front": "系統",
      "back": "system, lineage"
    },
    {
      "front": "系列",
      "back": "affiliation"
    },
    {
      "front": "絹",
      "back": "silk"
    },
    {
      "front": "ストーブ",
      "back": "stove"
    },
    {
      "front": "木綿",
      "back": "cotton"
    },
    {
      "front": "綿",
      "back": "cotton"
    },
    {
      "front": "刀",
      "back": "sword, blade"
    },
    {
      "front": "棒",
      "back": "stick"
    },
    {
      "front": "スチュワーデス",
      "back": "flight attendant"
    },
    {
      "front": "柄",
      "back": "pattern, print"
    },
    {
      "front": "柄",
      "back": "handle, grip"
    },
    {
      "front": "枝",
      "back": "branch, twig"
    },
    {
      "front": "木枯らし",
      "back": "cold wintry wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "枯れる",
      "back": "wither, die"
    },
    {
      "front": "テープレコーダー",
      "back": "tape recorder"
    },
    {
      "front": "詩人",
      "back": "poet"
    },
    {
      "front": "詩",
      "back": "poetry, poem"
    },
    {
      "front": "詰まる",
      "back": "get clogged, become blocked"
    },
    {
      "front": "詰める",
      "back": "stuff (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "譲る",
      "back": "give, hand over"
    },
    {
      "front": "誠に",
      "back": "truly, very"
    },
    {
      "front": "盛り上げる",
      "back": "bring excitement"
    },
    {
      "front": "盛ん",
      "back": "prosperous, thriving"
    },
    {
      "front": "盛る",
      "back": "heap up, fill"
    },
    {
      "front": "謙遜",
      "back": "modesty, humbleness"
    },
    {
      "front": "兼ねる",
      "back": "serve two functions, combine"
    },
    {
      "front": "方針",
      "back": "policy, principle"
    },
    {
      "front": "針",
      "back": "needle, (clock) hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "釣り合う",
      "back": "balance out, match"
    },
    {
      "front": "釣り合い",
      "back": "balance, proportion"
    },
    {
      "front": "鋭い",
      "back": "sharp, acute"
    },
    {
      "front": "鈍い",
      "back": "dull, slow"
    },
    {
      "front": "鎖",
      "back": "chain"
    },
    {
      "front": "鑑賞",
      "back": "viewing, enjoyment (of art)"
    },
    {
      "front": "鐘",
      "back": "bell, gong"
    },
    {
      "front": "谷",
      "back": "valley"
    },
    {
      "front": "海水浴",
      "back": "sea bathing"
    },
    {
      "front": "岸",
      "back": "shore, bank"
    },
    {
      "front": "辺り",
      "back": "vicinity, around"
    },
    {
      "front": "砂浜",
      "back": "sand beach"
    },
    {
      "front": "沖",
      "back": "offshore"
    },
    {
      "front": "湾",
      "back": "bay, gulf"
    },
    {
      "front": "泉",
      "back": "spring, fountain"
    },
    {
      "front": "潜る",
      "back": "dive, go under the water"
    },
    {
      "front": "泥",
      "back": "mud"
    },
    {
      "front": "濁る",
      "back": "become turbid, get cloudy"
    },
    {
      "front": "澄む",
      "back": "become clear"
    },
    {
      "front": "湯気",
      "back": "steam, vapor"
    },
    {
      "front": "湯飲み",
      "back": "teacup"
    },
    {
      "front": "よる",
      "back": "be based on, depend on"
    },
    {
      "front": "濡らす",
      "back": "get (something) wet"
    },
    {
      "front": "溝",
      "back": "ditch, groove"
    },
    {
      "front": "叫ぶ",
      "back": "shout, cry out"
    },
    {
      "front": "もっとも",
      "back": "quite right"
    },
    {
      "front": "吐く",
      "back": "holler, vomit"
    },
    {
      "front": "恩",
      "back": "debt of gratitude, kindness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひく",
      "back": "run over"
    },
    {
      "front": "恵まれる",
      "back": "be blessed, be fortunate enough"
    },
    {
      "front": "街角",
      "back": "street corner"
    },
    {
      "front": "半径",
      "back": "radius"
    },
    {
      "front": "直径",
      "back": "diameter"
    },
    {
      "front": "丼",
      "back": "bowl"
    },
    {
      "front": "豆",
      "back": "bean, peas"
    },
    {
      "front": "グリーン",
      "back": "green"
    },
    {
      "front": "粒",
      "back": "grain, drop"
    },
    {
      "front": "粉",
      "back": "powder, flour"
    },
    {
      "front": "大麦",
      "back": "barley"
    },
    {
      "front": "小麦",
      "back": "wheat"
    },
    {
      "front": "小麦粉",
      "back": "flour"
    },
    {
      "front": "麦",
      "back": "wheat"
    },
    {
      "front": "かつて",
      "back": "once, at one time in the past"
    },
    {
      "front": "電灯",
      "back": "electric light"
    },
    {
      "front": "灯油",
      "back": "kerosene, lamp oil"
    },
    {
      "front": "蛍光灯",
      "back": "fluorescent light"
    },
    {
      "front": "炎",
      "back": "flame, blaze"
    },
    {
      "front": "西暦",
      "back": "Christian Era, A.D."
    },
    {
      "front": "エイズ",
      "back": "AIDS"
    },
    {
      "front": "皮肉",
      "back": "sarcasm, irony"
    },
    {
      "front": "皮",
      "back": "peel, skin"
    },
    {
      "front": "皮膚",
      "back": "skin"
    },
    {
      "front": "糸",
      "back": "thread, yarn"
    },
    {
      "front": "毛糸",
      "back": "woolen yarn, wool"
    },
    {
      "front": "毛皮",
      "back": "fur"
    },
    {
      "front": "眉毛",
      "back": "eyebrows"
    },
    {
      "front": "ラグビー",
      "back": "rugby"
    },
    {
      "front": "唇",
      "back": "lip"
    },
    {
      "front": "面倒臭い",
      "back": "troublesome, tiresome"
    },
    {
      "front": "臭う",
      "back": "stink (unpleasant)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ありがたい",
      "back": "thankful, grateful"
    },
    {
      "front": "匂う",
      "back": "smell (pleasant)"
    },
    {
      "front": "掘る",
      "back": "dig, unearth"
    },
    {
      "front": "塀",
      "back": "fence, wall"
    },
    {
      "front": "一層",
      "back": "(even) more"
    },
    {
      "front": "大層",
      "back": "very, greatly"
    },
    {
      "front": "高層",
      "back": "high altitude, high-rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "チキン",
      "back": "chicken"
    },
    {
      "front": "履歴書",
      "back": "resume, curriculum vitae"
    },
    {
      "front": "履物",
      "back": "footwear"
    },
    {
      "front": "覆う",
      "back": "cover up"
    },
    {
      "front": "戸棚",
      "back": "cupboard"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガラス戸",
      "back": "glass door"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジャーナリズム",
      "back": "journalism"
    },
    {
      "front": "翌日",
      "back": "the following day, the next day"
    },
    {
      "front": "翌年",
      "back": "the following year"
    },
    {
      "front": "翌朝",
      "back": "the following morning, the next morning"
    },
    {
      "front": "新鮮",
      "back": "fresh"
    },
    {
      "front": "アルファベット",
      "back": "alphabet"
    },
    {
      "front": "群れ",
      "back": "flock, herd"
    },
    {
      "front": "郡",
      "back": "county"
    },
    {
      "front": "脂",
      "back": "fat, grease"
    },
    {
      "front": "のり",
      "back": "seaweed"
    },
    {
      "front": "肌着",
      "back": "underwear"
    },
    {
      "front": "肌色",
      "back": "flesh color, skin color"
    },
    {
      "front": "胃腸",
      "back": "stomach and intestines"
    },
    {
      "front": "幕",
      "back": "curtain"
    },
    {
      "front": "お歳暮",
      "back": "year-end gift"
    },
    {
      "front": "暮らす",
      "back": "live, lead a life"
    },
    {
      "front": "暮らし",
      "back": "living, livelihood"
    },
    {
      "front": "暮れる",
      "back": "get dark"
    },
    {
      "front": "暮れ",
      "back": "dusk, the end (of a season or a year)"
    },
    {
      "front": "墓地",
      "back": "graveyard, cemetery"
    },
    {
      "front": "墓参り",
      "back": "visit to a grave"
    },
    {
      "front": "墓",
      "back": "grave, gravestone"
    },
    {
      "front": "芽",
      "back": "bud, sprout"
    },
    {
      "front": "荒れる",
      "back": "be wild, get rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "荒い",
      "back": "harsh, rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "セールスマン",
      "back": "sales representative, salesperson"
    },
    {
      "front": "礼",
      "back": "bow, thanks"
    },
    {
      "front": "行儀",
      "back": "manners, behavior"
    },
    {
      "front": "儀式",
      "back": "ceremony, ritual"
    },
    {
      "front": "礼儀",
      "back": "good manners, courtesy"
    },
    {
      "front": "憎む",
      "back": "hate, detest"
    },
    {
      "front": "憎い",
      "back": "hateful, abominable"
    },
    {
      "front": "憎らしい",
      "back": "hateful, obnoxious"
    },
    {
      "front": "仏教",
      "back": "Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "front": "仏",
      "back": "Buddha, Buddhist image"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごろごろ",
      "back": "rumble"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤ん坊",
      "back": "(human) baby"
    },
    {
      "front": "お坊さん",
      "back": "monk, priest"
    },
    {
      "front": "坊さん",
      "back": "Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "front": "国旗",
      "back": "national flag"
    },
    {
      "front": "旗",
      "back": "flag, banner"
    },
    {
      "front": "竹",
      "back": "bamboo"
    },
    {
      "front": "イントネーション",
      "back": "intonation"
    },
    {
      "front": "万年筆",
      "back": "fountain pen"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆記用具",
      "back": "pens and pencils, writing materials"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆記試験",
      "back": "written examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆者",
      "back": "writer, author"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆",
      "back": "writing brush"
    },
    {
      "front": "笛",
      "back": "whistle"
    },
    {
      "front": "あぐら",
      "back": "sitting cross-legged"
    },
    {
      "front": "筋道",
      "back": "method, logic"
    },
    {
      "front": "筋肉",
      "back": "muscle"
    },
    {
      "front": "筋",
      "back": "muscle, nerve"
    },
    {
      "front": "座布団",
      "back": "cushion"
    },
    {
      "front": "布",
      "back": "cloth"
    },
    {
      "front": "スモッグ",
      "back": "smog"
    },
    {
      "front": "包丁",
      "back": "kitchen knife"
    },
    {
      "front": "包み紙",
      "back": "wrapping paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "包帯",
      "back": "bandage"
    },
    {
      "front": "包み",
      "back": "package, parcel"
    },
    {
      "front": "抱く",
      "back": "embrace (firmly with affection), have a dream, ambition etc."
    },
    {
      "front": "抱く",
      "back": "hug, hold"
    },
    {
      "front": "たこ",
      "back": "octopus"
    },
    {
      "front": "慣用句",
      "back": "idiom, common expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "句",
      "back": "phrase"
    },
    {
      "front": "中旬",
      "back": "middle ten days of a month"
    },
    {
      "front": "上旬",
      "back": "the first ten days (of a month)"
    },
    {
      "front": "下旬",
      "back": "the last ten days (of a month)"
    },
    {
      "front": "飽きる",
      "back": "get tired of"
    },
    {
      "front": "のろい",
      "back": "slow, sluggish"
    },
    {
      "front": "飾り",
      "back": "ornament, decoration"
    },
    {
      "front": "餌",
      "back": "bait, feed"
    },
    {
      "front": "旧",
      "back": "old, former"
    },
    {
      "front": "育児",
      "back": "childcare, child-raising"
    },
    {
      "front": "児童",
      "back": "(school) children"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴょんぴょん",
      "back": "jump, hop"
    },
    {
      "front": "同姓",
      "back": "same surname"
    },
    {
      "front": "姓",
      "back": "family name, surname"
    },
    {
      "front": "花嫁",
      "back": "bride"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫁",
      "back": "bride, daughter-in-law"
    },
    {
      "front": "幼児",
      "back": "young child"
    },
    {
      "front": "幼い",
      "back": "little, childish"
    },
    {
      "front": "とうもろこし",
      "back": "corn"
    },
    {
      "front": "居眠り",
      "back": "doze, catnap"
    },
    {
      "front": "眠り",
      "back": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "睡眠",
      "back": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひらひら",
      "back": "lightly fluttering, floating"
    },
    {
      "front": "眺め",
      "back": "view, prospect"
    },
    {
      "front": "一瞬",
      "back": "instant, moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "瞬間",
      "back": "moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "がらがら",
      "back": "gargle"
    },
    {
      "front": "話し掛ける",
      "back": "speak to (someone)"
    },
    {
      "front": "通り掛かる",
      "back": "happen to pass by"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ掛かる",
      "back": "be caught, be trapped"
    },
    {
      "front": "追い掛ける",
      "back": "chase, run after"
    },
    {
      "front": "腰掛け",
      "back": "stool, seat"
    },
    {
      "front": "腰掛ける",
      "back": "sit down"
    },
    {
      "front": "かちかち",
      "back": "hard, solid"
    },
    {
      "front": "拝見",
      "back": "look at, see (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "拝む",
      "back": "bow in veneration, pray"
    },
    {
      "front": "控え室",
      "back": "waiting room"
    },
    {
      "front": "握りしめる",
      "back": "grip, clench (one's hands)"
    },
    {
      "front": "括弧",
      "back": "parentheses, brackets"
    },
    {
      "front": "輝く",
      "back": "shine, glitter"
    },
    {
      "front": "抑える",
      "back": "suppress, bring under control"
    },
    {
      "front": "出迎え",
      "back": "meeting, picking someone up"
    },
    {
      "front": "迎え",
      "back": "greeting, picking (someone) up"
    },
    {
      "front": "いっぺんに",
      "back": "all at once"
    },
    {
      "front": "巡る",
      "back": "make a round"
    },
    {
      "front": "隅",
      "back": "corner"
    },
    {
      "front": "城",
      "back": "castle"
    },
    {
      "front": "伺う",
      "back": "ask, hear (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウィークエンド",
      "back": "weekend"
    },
    {
      "front": "俳優",
      "back": "actor"
    },
    {
      "front": "俳句",
      "back": "Japanese seventeen-syllabled verse"
    },
    {
      "front": "悔しい",
      "back": "frustrating, regrettable"
    },
    {
      "front": "倣う",
      "back": "copy, follow an example"
    },
    {
      "front": "寮",
      "back": "dormitory"
    },
    {
      "front": "がさがさ",
      "back": "rustle"
    },
    {
      "front": "大臣",
      "back": "minister"
    },
    {
      "front": "総理大臣",
      "back": "prime minister"
    },
    {
      "front": "臨時",
      "back": "temporary, provisional"
    },
    {
      "front": "がぶがぶ",
      "back": "guzzling, gulping"
    },
    {
      "front": "闘う",
      "back": "fight, battle"
    },
    {
      "front": "惜しい",
      "back": "almost, close"
    },
    {
      "front": "噴火",
      "back": "eruption"
    },
    {
      "front": "噴水",
      "back": "jet, fountain"
    },
    {
      "front": "きれ",
      "back": "a cut of cloth"
    },
    {
      "front": "恨む",
      "back": "hold a grudge, feel resentment"
    },
    {
      "front": "恨み",
      "back": "grudge, hatred"
    },
    {
      "front": "不愉快",
      "back": "upset, disagreeable"
    },
    {
      "front": "愉快",
      "back": "pleasant, amusing"
    },
    {
      "front": "怪しむ",
      "back": "suspect, doubt"
    },
    {
      "front": "食卓",
      "back": "dining table"
    },
    {
      "front": "電卓",
      "back": "calculator"
    },
    {
      "front": "じゃぶじゃぶ",
      "back": "splashing, washing"
    },
    {
      "front": "勧める",
      "back": "suggest, recommend"
    },
    {
      "front": "焦点",
      "back": "focus, focal point"
    },
    {
      "front": "焦げる",
      "back": "be burned, be scorched"
    },
    {
      "front": "雄大",
      "back": "grand, magnificent"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちょうちょう",
      "back": "butterfly"
    },
    {
      "front": "幼稚園",
      "back": "kindergarten"
    },
    {
      "front": "幼稚",
      "back": "childish"
    },
    {
      "front": "稲",
      "back": "rice plant"
    },
    {
      "front": "原稿用紙",
      "back": "manuscript paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "投稿",
      "back": "posting, sending (an article etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "穏やか",
      "back": "calm, quiet"
    },
    {
      "front": "つばめ",
      "back": "swallow"
    },
    {
      "front": "隠す",
      "back": "hide, conceal"
    },
    {
      "front": "物陰",
      "back": "shade, place to hide"
    },
    {
      "front": "陰",
      "back": "shade"
    },
    {
      "front": "塊",
      "back": "mass, clump"
    },
    {
      "front": "醜い",
      "back": "ugly, bad-looking"
    },
    {
      "front": "はえ",
      "back": "fly"
    },
    {
      "front": "砕く",
      "back": "crush (something) into small pieces"
    },
    {
      "front": "砕ける",
      "back": "be crushed, break"
    },
    {
      "front": "貝",
      "back": "shellfish, shell"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪賢い",
      "back": "cunning, sly"
    },
    {
      "front": "賢い",
      "back": "wise, smart"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずる賢い",
      "back": "sly, cunning"
    },
    {
      "front": "はかり",
      "back": "scale"
    },
    {
      "front": "頂上",
      "back": "summit, top"
    },
    {
      "front": "頂く",
      "back": "receive, eat (humble)"
    },
    {
      "front": "頂戴",
      "back": "getting, receiving"
    },
    {
      "front": "矛盾",
      "back": "contradiction"
    },
    {
      "front": "刑事",
      "back": "detective"
    },
    {
      "front": "刑務所",
      "back": "prison"
    },
    {
      "front": "まねる",
      "back": "imitate, mimic"
    },
    {
      "front": "罰金",
      "back": "fine, penalty"
    },
    {
      "front": "罰する",
      "back": "punish, penalize"
    },
    {
      "front": "罰",
      "back": "punishment, penalty"
    },
    {
      "front": "老人",
      "back": "old person, elderly"
    },
    {
      "front": "海老",
      "back": "prawn"
    },
    {
      "front": "もうけ",
      "back": "profit"
    },
    {
      "front": "煮る",
      "back": "simmer, cook"
    },
    {
      "front": "煮える",
      "back": "become boiled, become simmered"
    },
    {
      "front": "黙る",
      "back": "become silent, shut one's mouth"
    },
    {
      "front": "獣",
      "back": "beast"
    },
    {
      "front": "よける",
      "back": "move out of the way"
    },
    {
      "front": "丘",
      "back": "hill"
    },
    {
      "front": "警官",
      "back": "police officer"
    },
    {
      "front": "県庁",
      "back": "prefectural office"
    },
    {
      "front": "都庁",
      "back": "Tokyo Metropolitan Government"
    },
    {
      "front": "府庁",
      "back": "prefectural office"
    },
    {
      "front": "官庁",
      "back": "government office"
    },
    {
      "front": "よす",
      "back": "quit, stop"
    },
    {
      "front": "摩擦",
      "back": "friction"
    },
    {
      "front": "擦る",
      "back": "rub, scrub"
    },
    {
      "front": "香水",
      "back": "perfume"
    },
    {
      "front": "香り",
      "back": "fragrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "きらりと",
      "back": "sparklingly, glittering"
    },
    {
      "front": "敬う",
      "back": "respect, honor"
    },
    {
      "front": "敷金",
      "back": "deposit, key money"
    },
    {
      "front": "座敷",
      "back": "Japanese-style room"
    },
    {
      "front": "勇気",
      "back": "courage"
    },
    {
      "front": "劣る",
      "back": "be inferior to, be worse than"
    },
    {
      "front": "勘定",
      "back": "check, count"
    },
    {
      "front": "勘",
      "back": "intuition, hunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごくんと",
      "back": "in one gulp"
    },
    {
      "front": "霧",
      "back": "fog, mist"
    },
    {
      "front": "霜",
      "back": "frost"
    },
    {
      "front": "盆地",
      "back": "basin"
    },
    {
      "front": "盆",
      "back": "tray"
    },
    {
      "front": "盆",
      "back": "the Bon festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴょんと",
      "back": "(jump or hop) lightly"
    },
    {
      "front": "公衆",
      "back": "public"
    },
    {
      "front": "群衆",
      "back": "masses (of people), crowd"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひらりと",
      "back": "in a fluttering motion"
    },
    {
      "front": "暑中見舞い",
      "back": "summer greeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "見舞い",
      "back": "personal visit to a sick person"
    },
    {
      "front": "見舞う",
      "back": "visit someone sick"
    },
    {
      "front": "舞台",
      "back": "stage, setting"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌舞伎",
      "back": "Japanese classical drama played by male actors"
    },
    {
      "front": "盆踊り",
      "back": "Bon dance festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "踊り",
      "back": "dance, dancing"
    },
    {
      "front": "もうじき",
      "back": "soon"
    },
    {
      "front": "跳ねる",
      "back": "bounce, hop"
    },
    {
      "front": "金銭",
      "back": "money"
    },
    {
      "front": "銭湯",
      "back": "public bath, bathhouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "埋める",
      "back": "fill (a place) with things or people, cover totally"
    },
    {
      "front": "埋める",
      "back": "bury, fill up (a hole, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "墨",
      "back": "black ink"
    },
    {
      "front": "狂う",
      "back": "become insane, get out of order"
    },
    {
      "front": "猿",
      "back": "monkey, ape"
    },
    {
      "front": "狙う",
      "back": "aim, be after"
    },
    {
      "front": "章",
      "back": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "front": "彫る",
      "back": "engrave, carve"
    },
    {
      "front": "祈る",
      "back": "pray, wish for"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピストル",
      "back": "pistol"
    },
    {
      "front": "裸",
      "back": "naked body, bareness"
    },
    {
      "front": "先祖",
      "back": "forefather, ancestor"
    },
    {
      "front": "祖先",
      "back": "ancestor"
    },
    {
      "front": "ママ",
      "back": "mom"
    },
    {
      "front": "酢",
      "back": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "front": "郊外",
      "back": "suburbs, outskirts"
    },
    {
      "front": "お年玉",
      "back": "New Year's gift money"
    },
    {
      "front": "玉ねぎ",
      "back": "onion"
    },
    {
      "front": "玉",
      "back": "bead, ball"
    },
    {
      "front": "パパ",
      "back": "dad"
    },
    {
      "front": "改善",
      "back": "improvement"
    },
    {
      "front": "綱",
      "back": "rope"
    },
    {
      "front": "縄",
      "back": "rope, cord"
    },
    {
      "front": "縛る",
      "back": "bind, tie"
    },
    {
      "front": "ペンチ",
      "back": "pliers, pincers"
    },
    {
      "front": "縫う",
      "back": "sew, stitch"
    },
    {
      "front": "絞る",
      "back": "wring out, squeeze"
    },
    {
      "front": "紺",
      "back": "dark blue, navy blue"
    },
    {
      "front": "口紅",
      "back": "lipstick"
    },
    {
      "front": "紅葉",
      "back": "autumn leaves, crimson foliage"
    },
    {
      "front": "虹",
      "back": "rainbow"
    },
    {
      "front": "はんこ",
      "back": "seal, stamp"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅雨入り",
      "back": "start of the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅雨明け",
      "back": "end of the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅",
      "back": "plum"
    },
    {
      "front": "欄",
      "back": "column, field"
    },
    {
      "front": "巣",
      "back": "nest, den"
    },
    {
      "front": "虚しい",
      "back": "vain, (feel) empty"
    },
    {
      "front": "嘘つき",
      "back": "liar"
    },
    {
      "front": "癖",
      "back": "habit"
    },
    {
      "front": "峠",
      "back": "mountain pass, ridge"
    },
    {
      "front": "嵐",
      "back": "storm"
    },
    {
      "front": "漬物",
      "back": "pickle, pickled vegetable"
    },
    {
      "front": "漬ける",
      "back": "pickle, marinade"
    },
    {
      "front": "マネー",
      "back": "money"
    },
    {
      "front": "潰す",
      "back": "crush (something)"
    },
    {
      "front": "潰れる",
      "back": "be squashed, be smashed"
    },
    {
      "front": "蛇",
      "back": "snake"
    },
    {
      "front": "芋",
      "back": "potato"
    },
    {
      "front": "菊",
      "back": "chrysanthemum"
    },
    {
      "front": "ガード",
      "back": "guardrail"
    },
    {
      "front": "挟む",
      "back": "pinch, get something caught (in)"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き上げる",
      "back": "withdraw, salvage"
    },
    {
      "front": "揚げる",
      "back": "fry"
    },
    {
      "front": "塔",
      "back": "tower"
    },
    {
      "front": "誓う",
      "back": "vow, swear"
    },
    {
      "front": "からから",
      "back": "(laugh) loudly"
    },
    {
      "front": "慰める",
      "back": "console, comfort"
    },
    {
      "front": "故郷",
      "back": "hometown, birthplace"
    },
    {
      "front": "朗らか",
      "back": "cheerful, bright"
    },
    {
      "front": "亀",
      "back": "turtle, tortoise"
    },
    {
      "front": "羨ましい",
      "back": "envious, jealous"
    },
    {
      "front": "鶴",
      "back": "crane (the bird, not the machine)"
    },
    {
      "front": "アルミニウム",
      "back": "aluminum"
    },
    {
      "front": "鳩",
      "back": "pigeon, dove"
    },
    {
      "front": "咳",
      "back": "cough"
    },
    {
      "front": "喉",
      "back": "throat"
    },
    {
      "front": "塞がる",
      "back": "be closed up, be blocked"
    },
    {
      "front": "塞ぐ",
      "back": "block (something) up, cover in"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちり",
      "back": "dust"
    },
    {
      "front": "掴む",
      "back": "grip, grab"
    },
    {
      "front": "憧れる",
      "back": "yearn after, long for"
    },
    {
      "front": "溺れる",
      "back": "drown"
    },
    {
      "front": "ディスコ",
      "back": "disco"
    },
    {
      "front": "蓋",
      "back": "lid, cover"
    },
    {
      "front": "柿",
      "back": "persimmon"
    },
    {
      "front": "パンティー",
      "back": "underwear"
    },
    {
      "front": "蜂",
      "back": "bee"
    },
    {
      "front": "お詫び",
      "back": "apologize, apology"
    },
    {
      "front": "詫びる",
      "back": "sincerely apologize"
    },
    {
      "front": "釘",
      "back": "nail, spike"
    },
    {
      "front": "頬",
      "back": "cheek (common reading)"
    },
    {
      "front": "頬",
      "back": "cheek (traditional reading)"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばあさん",
      "back": "grandmother, old lady"
    },
    {
      "front": "餅",
      "back": "rice cake"
    },
    {
      "front": "鰻",
      "back": "eel"
    },
    {
      "front": "麓",
      "back": "foot of the mountain"
    },
    {
      "front": "雀",
      "back": "sparrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぺらぺら",
      "back": "flimsy, thin"
    },
    {
      "front": "嗅ぐ",
      "back": "smell, sniff"
    },
    {
      "front": "揉む",
      "back": "rub, massage"
    },
    {
      "front": "舐める",
      "back": "lick"
    },
    {
      "front": "贅沢",
      "back": "luxury, extravagance"
    },
    {
      "front": "頷く",
      "back": "nod"
    },
    {
      "front": "択一",
      "back": "multiple choice"
    },
    {
      "front": "兆",
      "back": "trillion"
    },
    {
      "front": "一時",
      "back": "time; while"
    },
    {
      "front": "時には",
      "back": "occasionally"
    },
    {
      "front": "日に日に",
      "back": "day by day; every day"
    },
    {
      "front": "日誌",
      "back": "diary"
    },
    {
      "front": "歳月",
      "back": "time"
    },
    {
      "front": "針金",
      "back": "wire"
    },
    {
      "front": "五分",
      "back": "fifty percent; five percent"
    },
    {
      "front": "水分",
      "back": "moisture; water"
    },
    {
      "front": "水臭い",
      "back": "not frank; watery"
    },
    {
      "front": "分岐",
      "back": "divergence"
    },
    {
      "front": "分泌",
      "back": "secretion"
    },
    {
      "front": "何分",
      "back": "anyway; please"
    },
    {
      "front": "何でも",
      "back": "anything; whatever"
    },
    {
      "front": "何かと",
      "back": "in various ways"
    },
    {
      "front": "何ら",
      "back": "of any kind; whatever"
    },
    {
      "front": "ただ今",
      "back": "I'm home! soon; now"
    },
    {
      "front": "一行",
      "back": "group; party"
    },
    {
      "front": "よそ行き",
      "back": "best behavior; formal; going out"
    },
    {
      "front": "犯行",
      "back": "crime; criminal act"
    },
    {
      "front": "奥行",
      "back": "depth; length"
    },
    {
      "front": "大分",
      "back": "greatly; very"
    },
    {
      "front": "大まか",
      "back": "general; rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "広大",
      "back": "extensive; vast"
    },
    {
      "front": "莫大",
      "back": "immense; vast"
    },
    {
      "front": "少なからず",
      "back": "not a little"
    },
    {
      "front": "多大",
      "back": "great; serious"
    },
    {
      "front": "多湿",
      "back": "high humidity"
    },
    {
      "front": "史上",
      "back": "historically"
    },
    {
      "front": "下",
      "back": "lower part; lower stream"
    },
    {
      "front": "下がり",
      "back": "decline"
    },
    {
      "front": "下す",
      "back": "bestow; give a command"
    },
    {
      "front": "下駄",
      "back": "geta; wooden clogs"
    },
    {
      "front": "万人",
      "back": "all people"
    },
    {
      "front": "人だかり",
      "back": "crowd; throng"
    },
    {
      "front": "偉人",
      "back": "great man"
    },
    {
      "front": "水入らず",
      "back": "by themselves; with no one else"
    },
    {
      "front": "入金",
      "back": "receipt of money"
    },
    {
      "front": "挿入",
      "back": "insertion"
    },
    {
      "front": "出",
      "back": "coming from; flow; rising"
    },
    {
      "front": "お出で",
      "back": "coming; going"
    },
    {
      "front": "本番",
      "back": "real performance; take"
    },
    {
      "front": "媒体",
      "back": "medium"
    },
    {
      "front": "一目",
      "back": "a glimpse; a look"
    },
    {
      "front": "人目",
      "back": "attention; public notice"
    },
    {
      "front": "口先",
      "back": "lip service; lips"
    },
    {
      "front": "口出し",
      "back": "interference"
    },
    {
      "front": "口々に",
      "back": "variously"
    },
    {
      "front": "口ごもる",
      "back": "mumble"
    },
    {
      "front": "口癖",
      "back": "one's favorite phrase"
    },
    {
      "front": "蛇口",
      "back": "faucet"
    },
    {
      "front": "下手",
      "back": "humble position"
    },
    {
      "front": "一足",
      "back": "a step"
    },
    {
      "front": "土足",
      "back": "wearing shoes"
    },
    {
      "front": "足る",
      "back": "get by; suffice"
    },
    {
      "front": "氷山",
      "back": "iceberg"
    },
    {
      "front": "海藻",
      "back": "marine algae; seaweed"
    },
    {
      "front": "小火",
      "back": "small fire"
    },
    {
      "front": "供",
      "back": "attendant; retinue"
    },
    {
      "front": "供える",
      "back": "offer"
    },
    {
      "front": "好き好き",
      "back": "a matter of taste"
    },
    {
      "front": "友好",
      "back": "amity; friendship"
    },
    {
      "front": "大家",
      "back": "authority; great master"
    },
    {
      "front": "家系",
      "back": "family line; lineage"
    },
    {
      "front": "耳元",
      "back": "close to one's ears"
    },
    {
      "front": "次元",
      "back": "dimension"
    },
    {
      "front": "紀元",
      "back": "era"
    },
    {
      "front": "天下",
      "back": "the whole country; the world"
    },
    {
      "front": "一気に",
      "back": "in one breath"
    },
    {
      "front": "大気",
      "back": "the atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "front": "お気に入り",
      "back": "favorites"
    },
    {
      "front": "外気",
      "back": "open air"
    },
    {
      "front": "内気",
      "back": "bashful; shy"
    },
    {
      "front": "気まま",
      "back": "selfish; willful"
    },
    {
      "front": "英気",
      "back": "energy; vigor"
    },
    {
      "front": "時雨",
      "back": "late fall or early winter rain"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨漏り",
      "back": "leak; roof leak"
    },
    {
      "front": "霧雨",
      "back": "drizzle; misting rain"
    },
    {
      "front": "青ざめる",
      "back": "become pale"
    },
    {
      "front": "明くる日",
      "back": "the following day"
    },
    {
      "front": "明年",
      "back": "next year"
    },
    {
      "front": "明晩",
      "back": "tomorrow night"
    },
    {
      "front": "閏年",
      "back": "leap year"
    },
    {
      "front": "内向",
      "back": "introversion"
    },
    {
      "front": "開設",
      "back": "establishment"
    },
    {
      "front": "開幕",
      "back": "rising of the curtain"
    },
    {
      "front": "閉じこもる",
      "back": "shut oneself up"
    },
    {
      "front": "一円",
      "back": "throughout the region"
    },
    {
      "front": "円安",
      "back": "depreciation of the yen"
    },
    {
      "front": "目安",
      "back": "aim; standard"
    },
    {
      "front": "初雪",
      "back": "first snow of the season"
    },
    {
      "front": "一人前",
      "back": "one portion"
    },
    {
      "front": "目前",
      "back": "at hand; imminent"
    },
    {
      "front": "男前",
      "back": "handsome man"
    },
    {
      "front": "気前",
      "back": "generosity"
    },
    {
      "front": "前払い",
      "back": "advance payment; up front payment"
    },
    {
      "front": "明後日",
      "back": "day after tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "大半",
      "back": "majority; the greater part"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼下がり",
      "back": "early afternoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "前夜",
      "back": "eve; previous night"
    },
    {
      "front": "昼夜",
      "back": "day and night"
    },
    {
      "front": "土間",
      "back": "earth floor; pit"
    },
    {
      "front": "日食",
      "back": "solar eclipse"
    },
    {
      "front": "月食",
      "back": "lunar eclipse"
    },
    {
      "front": "食い下がる",
      "back": "hang on; persist"
    },
    {
      "front": "食み出す",
      "back": "project; protrude"
    },
    {
      "front": "食み出る",
      "back": "project; protrude"
    },
    {
      "front": "間食",
      "back": "food between meals"
    },
    {
      "front": "食",
      "back": "appetite; eating"
    },
    {
      "front": "菜食",
      "back": "vegetable diet"
    },
    {
      "front": "買い手",
      "back": "buyer; customer"
    },
    {
      "front": "買いかぶる",
      "back": "overrate"
    },
    {
      "front": "見分け",
      "back": "distinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "下見",
      "back": "preliminary inspection"
    },
    {
      "front": "見出す",
      "back": "discover; find out"
    },
    {
      "front": "外見",
      "back": "outward appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "見た目",
      "back": "outward appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "見晴らす",
      "back": "look out"
    },
    {
      "front": "見聞",
      "back": "experience"
    },
    {
      "front": "見る見る",
      "back": "in a moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "見なす",
      "back": "presume; regard as"
    },
    {
      "front": "見す見す",
      "back": "before one's very eyes"
    },
    {
      "front": "見窄らしい",
      "back": "poor-looking; shabby"
    },
    {
      "front": "見縊る",
      "back": "look down on"
    },
    {
      "front": "言いなり",
      "back": "doing as one is told"
    },
    {
      "front": "言わば",
      "back": "in short; so to speak"
    },
    {
      "front": "口語",
      "back": "colloquial language"
    },
    {
      "front": "文体",
      "back": "style"
    },
    {
      "front": "文科",
      "back": "literary department"
    },
    {
      "front": "文庫",
      "back": "collection of literary works; library"
    },
    {
      "front": "大文字",
      "back": "capital letter"
    },
    {
      "front": "小文字",
      "back": "lowercase letter"
    },
    {
      "front": "書き初め",
      "back": "New Year's calligraphy"
    },
    {
      "front": "前書き",
      "back": "foreword; preface"
    },
    {
      "front": "肩書き",
      "back": "degree; title"
    },
    {
      "front": "書斎",
      "back": "library; study"
    },
    {
      "front": "楷書",
      "back": "printed style of Chinese characters"
    },
    {
      "front": "覚醒剤",
      "back": "stimulant"
    },
    {
      "front": "会食",
      "back": "dinner together"
    },
    {
      "front": "間に合わせ",
      "back": "makeshift"
    },
    {
      "front": "会合",
      "back": "gathering; meeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "仕入れ",
      "back": "purchasing; stocking"
    },
    {
      "front": "万事",
      "back": "all things; everything"
    },
    {
      "front": "何事",
      "back": "what; whatever"
    },
    {
      "front": "幹事",
      "back": "manager; organizer"
    },
    {
      "front": "何故",
      "back": "how; why"
    },
    {
      "front": "故事",
      "back": "historical fact"
    },
    {
      "front": "来客",
      "back": "guest; visitor"
    },
    {
      "front": "外車",
      "back": "imported car"
    },
    {
      "front": "空車",
      "back": "empty car; vacant taxi"
    },
    {
      "front": "客車",
      "back": "passenger car"
    },
    {
      "front": "通達",
      "back": "communication"
    },
    {
      "front": "通夜",
      "back": "deathwatch; vigil"
    },
    {
      "front": "通話",
      "back": "telephone call"
    },
    {
      "front": "文字通り",
      "back": "literally"
    },
    {
      "front": "文通",
      "back": "correspondence"
    },
    {
      "front": "通ずる",
      "back": "lead"
    },
    {
      "front": "童話",
      "back": "fairy tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "中道",
      "back": "golden mean; middle road"
    },
    {
      "front": "人道",
      "back": "humanity; morality"
    },
    {
      "front": "剣道",
      "back": "fencing; swordsmanship"
    },
    {
      "front": "高低",
      "back": "high and low"
    },
    {
      "front": "路上",
      "back": "on the road"
    },
    {
      "front": "大地",
      "back": "earth; ground"
    },
    {
      "front": "高地",
      "back": "high ground; plateau"
    },
    {
      "front": "路地",
      "back": "alley; lane"
    },
    {
      "front": "口止め",
      "back": "hush up"
    },
    {
      "front": "食い止める",
      "back": "check; hold back"
    },
    {
      "front": "止めどなく",
      "back": "endlessly"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩合",
      "back": "commission; rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "度",
      "back": "degree; extent"
    },
    {
      "front": "緯度",
      "back": "latitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "近日",
      "back": "shortly; soon"
    },
    {
      "front": "体長",
      "back": "body length"
    },
    {
      "front": "長",
      "back": "chief; head"
    },
    {
      "front": "ＯＫ",
      "back": "agreement; consent"
    },
    {
      "front": "東部",
      "back": "eastern part; the East"
    },
    {
      "front": "西部",
      "back": "the West; western part"
    },
    {
      "front": "南部",
      "back": "South; south part"
    },
    {
      "front": "北部",
      "back": "north; northern part"
    },
    {
      "front": "力む",
      "back": "strain; swagger"
    },
    {
      "front": "国力",
      "back": "national power"
    },
    {
      "front": "国電",
      "back": "National Railway"
    },
    {
      "front": "電柱",
      "back": "telegraph pole"
    },
    {
      "front": "帝国",
      "back": "empire"
    },
    {
      "front": "近世",
      "back": "modern ages"
    },
    {
      "front": "この世",
      "back": "present life; this world"
    },
    {
      "front": "あの世",
      "back": "the other world"
    },
    {
      "front": "リスト",
      "back": "list"
    },
    {
      "front": "白人",
      "back": "Caucasian; white person"
    },
    {
      "front": "空白",
      "back": "blank; void"
    },
    {
      "front": "白書",
      "back": "white paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "白バイ",
      "back": "white police motorcycle"
    },
    {
      "front": "黒人",
      "back": "black person"
    },
    {
      "front": "黒子",
      "back": "birthmark; mole"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝飯",
      "back": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤飯",
      "back": "cooked rice and red beans"
    },
    {
      "front": "肉食",
      "back": "carnivore"
    },
    {
      "front": "挽肉",
      "back": "ground meat; mince"
    },
    {
      "front": "金魚",
      "back": "goldfish"
    },
    {
      "front": "魚",
      "back": "fish"
    },
    {
      "front": "野",
      "back": "field; open country"
    },
    {
      "front": "野蛮",
      "back": "barbarous; savage"
    },
    {
      "front": "分からず屋",
      "back": "obstinate person"
    },
    {
      "front": "小屋",
      "back": "cottage; playhouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "屋外",
      "back": "open air; outdoors"
    },
    {
      "front": "屋内",
      "back": "indoors"
    },
    {
      "front": "目茶目茶",
      "back": "ruin; wreck"
    },
    {
      "front": "茶道",
      "back": "tea ceremony"
    },
    {
      "front": "スタッフ",
      "back": "the staff"
    },
    {
      "front": "気味",
      "back": "a touch; feeling"
    },
    {
      "front": "甘味",
      "back": "sweetness"
    },
    {
      "front": "未明",
      "back": "early dawn"
    },
    {
      "front": "合理",
      "back": "rationality"
    },
    {
      "front": "理事",
      "back": "director; trustee"
    },
    {
      "front": "道理",
      "back": "justice; reason"
    },
    {
      "front": "倫理",
      "back": "ethics; morals"
    },
    {
      "front": "インテリア",
      "back": "inside; interior"
    },
    {
      "front": "解体",
      "back": "dismantling"
    },
    {
      "front": "雪解け",
      "back": "thawing of snow"
    },
    {
      "front": "解ける",
      "back": "come undone"
    },
    {
      "front": "解雇",
      "back": "discharge; dismissal"
    },
    {
      "front": "有り合わせ",
      "back": "available; in hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "何気無く",
      "back": "as if nothing had happened; casually"
    },
    {
      "front": "無人",
      "back": "deserted; uninhabited"
    },
    {
      "front": "無休",
      "back": "open all year round"
    },
    {
      "front": "無力",
      "back": "powerlessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "無地",
      "back": "plain"
    },
    {
      "front": "有無",
      "back": "existence; yes or no"
    },
    {
      "front": "無",
      "back": "naught; nothing"
    },
    {
      "front": "無し",
      "back": "naught; nothing"
    },
    {
      "front": "ＯＬ",
      "back": "female office worker"
    },
    {
      "front": "傑作",
      "back": "masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "front": "レンタル",
      "back": "hire; rental"
    },
    {
      "front": "用足し",
      "back": "business; errand"
    },
    {
      "front": "用語",
      "back": "diction; terminology"
    },
    {
      "front": "通用",
      "back": "common usage"
    },
    {
      "front": "副作用",
      "back": "reaction; side-effect"
    },
    {
      "front": "解消",
      "back": "cancellation"
    },
    {
      "front": "消耗",
      "back": "consumption; exhaustion"
    },
    {
      "front": "抹消",
      "back": "removal"
    },
    {
      "front": "小売り",
      "back": "retail"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り手",
      "back": "seller"
    },
    {
      "front": "店開き",
      "back": "opening of a business"
    },
    {
      "front": "飲食店",
      "back": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "front": "手品",
      "back": "magic; sleight of hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "品",
      "back": "elegance; refinement"
    },
    {
      "front": "品詞",
      "back": "part of speech"
    },
    {
      "front": "目玉商品",
      "back": "featured product; loss leader"
    },
    {
      "front": "格子",
      "back": "lattice; latticework"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱中",
      "back": "absorption; enthusiasm"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱気",
      "back": "fevered air; hot air"
    },
    {
      "front": "高熱",
      "back": "high fever"
    },
    {
      "front": "白熱",
      "back": "white heat"
    },
    {
      "front": "解熱",
      "back": "alleviation of fever"
    },
    {
      "front": "一風",
      "back": "eccentric"
    },
    {
      "front": "風上",
      "back": "upwind; windward"
    },
    {
      "front": "風下",
      "back": "downwind; leeward"
    },
    {
      "front": "風力",
      "back": "wind power"
    },
    {
      "front": "風向き",
      "back": "wind direction"
    },
    {
      "front": "無風",
      "back": "calm; windless"
    },
    {
      "front": "そよ風",
      "back": "gentle breeze"
    },
    {
      "front": "レジャー",
      "back": "leisure; recreation"
    },
    {
      "front": "無情",
      "back": "coldhearted; heartless"
    },
    {
      "front": "時報",
      "back": "time signal"
    },
    {
      "front": "報われる",
      "back": "be rewarded"
    },
    {
      "front": "報いる",
      "back": "recompense; requite"
    },
    {
      "front": "被告",
      "back": "defendant; the accused"
    },
    {
      "front": "ジャパン",
      "back": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "米価",
      "back": "price of rice"
    },
    {
      "front": "新米",
      "back": "new rice; novice"
    },
    {
      "front": "一昔",
      "back": "age; decade"
    },
    {
      "front": "昔話",
      "back": "legend; old tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "良",
      "back": "good"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪人",
      "back": "wicked person"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪気",
      "back": "malice"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪事",
      "back": "evil deed"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪寒",
      "back": "chill"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪しからず",
      "back": "I beg you to understand my position"
    },
    {
      "front": "きまり悪い",
      "back": "awkward; embarrassed"
    },
    {
      "front": "険悪",
      "back": "dangerous; threatening"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫌悪",
      "back": "dislike; hatred"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミニ",
      "back": "mini"
    },
    {
      "front": "一心に",
      "back": "wholeheartedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "心中",
      "back": "heart; mind"
    },
    {
      "front": "本心",
      "back": "one's mind; one's real intention"
    },
    {
      "front": "気心",
      "back": "disposition; temper"
    },
    {
      "front": "初心",
      "back": "one's original intention"
    },
    {
      "front": "会心",
      "back": "congenial; satisfying"
    },
    {
      "front": "無心",
      "back": "be absorbed in"
    },
    {
      "front": "ローン",
      "back": "(bank) loan"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い上がる",
      "back": "get conceited"
    },
    {
      "front": "思いとどまる",
      "back": "abandon; refrain from"
    },
    {
      "front": "思わく",
      "back": "intention; thought"
    },
    {
      "front": "人見知り",
      "back": "shyness towards strangers"
    },
    {
      "front": "見ず知らず",
      "back": "strange; unknown"
    },
    {
      "front": "知覚",
      "back": "perception; sensation"
    },
    {
      "front": "スペシャル",
      "back": "special"
    },
    {
      "front": "秀才",
      "back": "genius"
    },
    {
      "front": "漫才",
      "back": "comic backchat; comic dialogue"
    },
    {
      "front": "先決",
      "back": "previous decision"
    },
    {
      "front": "可決",
      "back": "approval of a bill"
    },
    {
      "front": "不気味",
      "back": "uncanny; weird"
    },
    {
      "front": "不合理",
      "back": "irrational"
    },
    {
      "front": "不可解",
      "back": "incomprehensible"
    },
    {
      "front": "不作",
      "back": "bad harvest"
    },
    {
      "front": "不能",
      "back": "impossible; impotent"
    },
    {
      "front": "不可",
      "back": "fail; inadvisable"
    },
    {
      "front": "不透明",
      "back": "opaque"
    },
    {
      "front": "元号",
      "back": "era name"
    },
    {
      "front": "名月",
      "back": "full moon; harvest moon"
    },
    {
      "front": "名目",
      "back": "name; pretext"
    },
    {
      "front": "名門",
      "back": "distinguished family or school"
    },
    {
      "front": "高名",
      "back": "fame"
    },
    {
      "front": "無名",
      "back": "obscure; unknown"
    },
    {
      "front": "名作",
      "back": "fine work; masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "front": "品名",
      "back": "name of article"
    },
    {
      "front": "名案",
      "back": "splendid idea"
    },
    {
      "front": "匿名",
      "back": "anonymity; incognito"
    },
    {
      "front": "カルチャー",
      "back": "culture"
    },
    {
      "front": "各々",
      "back": "each"
    },
    {
      "front": "市販",
      "back": "marketing"
    },
    {
      "front": "市",
      "back": "fair; market"
    },
    {
      "front": "上京",
      "back": "going to Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハウス",
      "back": "greenhouse; house"
    },
    {
      "front": "好都合",
      "back": "favorable; fortunate"
    },
    {
      "front": "不都合",
      "back": "inconvenience"
    },
    {
      "front": "都市ガス",
      "back": "town gas"
    },
    {
      "front": "有り様",
      "back": "condition; sight"
    },
    {
      "front": "御中",
      "back": "Messrs."
    },
    {
      "front": "御輿",
      "back": "portable shrine; sacred palanquin"
    },
    {
      "front": "入荷",
      "back": "arrival of goods"
    },
    {
      "front": "ルーム",
      "back": "room"
    },
    {
      "front": "好物",
      "back": "favorite food"
    },
    {
      "front": "物語る",
      "back": "demonstrate; tell a story"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り物",
      "back": "feature; selling point"
    },
    {
      "front": "穀物",
      "back": "cereals; grain"
    },
    {
      "front": "一重",
      "back": "one layer"
    },
    {
      "front": "二重",
      "back": "twofold"
    },
    {
      "front": "二重",
      "back": "two layers"
    },
    {
      "front": "重体",
      "back": "critical state; serious condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "重力",
      "back": "gravity"
    },
    {
      "front": "重心",
      "back": "center of gravity"
    },
    {
      "front": "重症",
      "back": "serious illness"
    },
    {
      "front": "キー",
      "back": "key"
    },
    {
      "front": "分量",
      "back": "quantity"
    },
    {
      "front": "測量",
      "back": "measurement; surveying"
    },
    {
      "front": "気配",
      "back": "indication; sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "気配り",
      "back": "attention to detail"
    },
    {
      "front": "勾配",
      "back": "gradient; slope"
    },
    {
      "front": "スクール",
      "back": "school"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り分け",
      "back": "above all; especially"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り外す",
      "back": "dismantle; remove"
    },
    {
      "front": "気取る",
      "back": "make an affected pose"
    },
    {
      "front": "段取り",
      "back": "plan; program; step"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり取り",
      "back": "banter; exchange"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちり取り",
      "back": "dustpan"
    },
    {
      "front": "搾取",
      "back": "exploitation"
    },
    {
      "front": "テクノロジー",
      "back": "technology"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き届く",
      "back": "be attentive"
    },
    {
      "front": "見届ける",
      "back": "make sure; see with one's own eyes"
    },
    {
      "front": "待ち受ける",
      "back": "await; wait for"
    },
    {
      "front": "力持ち",
      "back": "powerful person"
    },
    {
      "front": "受け持ち",
      "back": "in charge of"
    },
    {
      "front": "打つ",
      "back": "impress"
    },
    {
      "front": "ホール",
      "back": "hall; hole"
    },
    {
      "front": "生前",
      "back": "during one's lifetime"
    },
    {
      "front": "生地",
      "back": "cloth; dough"
    },
    {
      "front": "生長",
      "back": "growth"
    },
    {
      "front": "生物",
      "back": "perishables; uncooked food"
    },
    {
      "front": "生ぬるい",
      "back": "halfway; lukewarm"
    },
    {
      "front": "派生",
      "back": "derivation"
    },
    {
      "front": "往生",
      "back": "passing away"
    },
    {
      "front": "生誕",
      "back": "birth; nativity"
    },
    {
      "front": "生き甲斐",
      "back": "reason for living"
    },
    {
      "front": "中性",
      "back": "neuter gender"
    },
    {
      "front": "人間性",
      "back": "human nature; humanity"
    },
    {
      "front": "気性",
      "back": "disposition; nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "野性",
      "back": "wild nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "無性に",
      "back": "extremely; very much"
    },
    {
      "front": "慢性",
      "back": "chronic"
    },
    {
      "front": "水産",
      "back": "fisheries; marine products"
    },
    {
      "front": "海産物",
      "back": "marine products"
    },
    {
      "front": "活力",
      "back": "vital power; vitality"
    },
    {
      "front": "活気",
      "back": "spirit; vigor"
    },
    {
      "front": "ヒット",
      "back": "hit; popularity"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜学",
      "back": "night school"
    },
    {
      "front": "理学部",
      "back": "science department"
    },
    {
      "front": "学界",
      "back": "academic circles"
    },
    {
      "front": "学",
      "back": "learning; studies"
    },
    {
      "front": "勉学",
      "back": "study"
    },
    {
      "front": "育む",
      "back": "cultivate; foster"
    },
    {
      "front": "強風",
      "back": "strong wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "強情",
      "back": "headstrong; obstinate"
    },
    {
      "front": "インフルエンザ",
      "back": "influenza; the flu"
    },
    {
      "front": "万引き",
      "back": "shoplifting"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き金",
      "back": "trigger"
    },
    {
      "front": "引力",
      "back": "gravitation"
    },
    {
      "front": "引け目",
      "back": "drawback; weakness"
    },
    {
      "front": "引きつる",
      "back": "have a cramp"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き戻す",
      "back": "bring back; restore"
    },
    {
      "front": "洗練",
      "back": "polishing; refinement"
    },
    {
      "front": "見習い",
      "back": "apprentice"
    },
    {
      "front": "不慣れ",
      "back": "inexperienced; unfamiliar"
    },
    {
      "front": "力試し",
      "back": "test of one's ability"
    },
    {
      "front": "体質",
      "back": "physical constitution"
    },
    {
      "front": "気質",
      "back": "temperament"
    },
    {
      "front": "地質",
      "back": "geological features; nature of the soil"
    },
    {
      "front": "質屋",
      "back": "pawnshop"
    },
    {
      "front": "質量",
      "back": "mass"
    },
    {
      "front": "シングル",
      "back": "single; single room"
    },
    {
      "front": "単行本",
      "back": "separate volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "重複",
      "back": "duplication"
    },
    {
      "front": "気難しい",
      "back": "hard to please; moody"
    },
    {
      "front": "難解",
      "back": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "front": "難問",
      "back": "difficult problem"
    },
    {
      "front": "難なく",
      "back": "easily"
    },
    {
      "front": "アウト",
      "back": "out; Out!"
    },
    {
      "front": "難点",
      "back": "difficult point; weakness"
    },
    {
      "front": "値",
      "back": "cost; price"
    },
    {
      "front": "分数",
      "back": "fraction"
    },
    {
      "front": "大多数",
      "back": "greater part; majority"
    },
    {
      "front": "小数点",
      "back": "decimal point"
    },
    {
      "front": "口数",
      "back": "number of accounts; words"
    },
    {
      "front": "半数",
      "back": "half the number"
    },
    {
      "front": "数値",
      "back": "numerical value"
    },
    {
      "front": "数量",
      "back": "quantity; volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "タウン",
      "back": "town"
    },
    {
      "front": "回帰",
      "back": "recurrence; revolution"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い回し",
      "back": "expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "撤回",
      "back": "retraction; withdrawal"
    },
    {
      "front": "八つ当たり",
      "back": "unjustified outburst of anger"
    },
    {
      "front": "目当て",
      "back": "aim; guide"
    },
    {
      "front": "心当たり",
      "back": "idea; knowledge"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い当たる",
      "back": "occur to; strike"
    },
    {
      "front": "配当",
      "back": "apportionment"
    },
    {
      "front": "コミュニケーション",
      "back": "communication"
    },
    {
      "front": "未然",
      "back": "in advance"
    },
    {
      "front": "漠然と",
      "back": "vaguely"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダブル",
      "back": "double"
    },
    {
      "front": "法人",
      "back": "corporation"
    },
    {
      "front": "合法",
      "back": "legality; legitimacy"
    },
    {
      "front": "無法",
      "back": "lawless"
    },
    {
      "front": "不法",
      "back": "unlawfulness"
    },
    {
      "front": "寸法",
      "back": "measurements; plan"
    },
    {
      "front": "新規",
      "back": "newly"
    },
    {
      "front": "法規",
      "back": "laws and regulations"
    },
    {
      "front": "規律",
      "back": "order; regulation"
    },
    {
      "front": "施行",
      "back": "enforcement; execution"
    },
    {
      "front": "経度",
      "back": "longitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "経理",
      "back": "accounting"
    },
    {
      "front": "国営",
      "back": "government-managed"
    },
    {
      "front": "都営",
      "back": "administered by the metropolitan government"
    },
    {
      "front": "旧式",
      "back": "old style; old type"
    },
    {
      "front": "企み",
      "back": "conspiracy; plot"
    },
    {
      "front": "企む",
      "back": "conspire; scheme"
    },
    {
      "front": "企てる",
      "back": "attempt; plot"
    },
    {
      "front": "山林",
      "back": "mountains and forests"
    },
    {
      "front": "重工業",
      "back": "heavy industry"
    },
    {
      "front": "営利",
      "back": "gain; profit"
    },
    {
      "front": "無益",
      "back": "futile; useless"
    },
    {
      "front": "不利益",
      "back": "disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "front": "マスク",
      "back": "face mask"
    },
    {
      "front": "収める",
      "back": "put away; store"
    },
    {
      "front": "収める",
      "back": "achieve; attain"
    },
    {
      "front": "芸能人",
      "back": "celebrity"
    },
    {
      "front": "文芸",
      "back": "literary art"
    },
    {
      "front": "工芸",
      "back": "technical art"
    },
    {
      "front": "芸能",
      "back": "public entertainment"
    },
    {
      "front": "芸",
      "back": "art; trick"
    },
    {
      "front": "製図",
      "back": "drafting; drawing"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄棒",
      "back": "horizontal bars; iron rod"
    },
    {
      "front": "ファースト",
      "back": "fast; first"
    },
    {
      "front": "人造",
      "back": "artificial; man-made"
    },
    {
      "front": "無造作",
      "back": "casual; easy"
    },
    {
      "front": "必読",
      "back": "essential reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "秒読み",
      "back": "countdown"
    },
    {
      "front": "必需品",
      "back": "necessaries"
    },
    {
      "front": "必須",
      "back": "indispensable"
    },
    {
      "front": "見所",
      "back": "good point; highlight"
    },
    {
      "front": "要所",
      "back": "important point"
    },
    {
      "front": "強要",
      "back": "coercion; extortion"
    },
    {
      "front": "要",
      "back": "main point; pivot"
    },
    {
      "front": "テクニック",
      "back": "technique"
    },
    {
      "front": "算数",
      "back": "arithmetic"
    },
    {
      "front": "交差",
      "back": "crossing; intersection"
    },
    {
      "front": "差し引き",
      "back": "balance; deduction"
    },
    {
      "front": "差し当たり",
      "back": "for the time being"
    },
    {
      "front": "偏差値",
      "back": "deviation"
    },
    {
      "front": "分割",
      "back": "division; partition"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り出す",
      "back": "calculate; deduce"
    },
    {
      "front": "割れ目",
      "back": "cleft; crevice"
    },
    {
      "front": "割く",
      "back": "set aside; spare"
    },
    {
      "front": "そのもの",
      "back": "the very thing"
    },
    {
      "front": "無残",
      "back": "atrocious; pitiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "名残惜しい",
      "back": "be sad to leave; be sorry to part"
    },
    {
      "front": "支局",
      "back": "branch office"
    },
    {
      "front": "差し支え",
      "back": "hindrance; objections"
    },
    {
      "front": "支える",
      "back": "maintain; support"
    },
    {
      "front": "返上",
      "back": "return"
    },
    {
      "front": "生き返る",
      "back": "be restored to life; revive"
    },
    {
      "front": "フロント",
      "back": "reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "間借り",
      "back": "renting a room"
    },
    {
      "front": "前借り",
      "back": "advance"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸間",
      "back": "room for rent"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸借",
      "back": "debt and credit; loan"
    },
    {
      "front": "食い込む",
      "back": "eat into"
    },
    {
      "front": "話し込む",
      "back": "have a long talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "売り込む",
      "back": "become well known; sell"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り込む",
      "back": "take in"
    },
    {
      "front": "末日",
      "back": "last day"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏ばて",
      "back": "suffering from the summer heat"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨期",
      "back": "rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "最期",
      "back": "one's last moments"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏期",
      "back": "summer; summertime"
    },
    {
      "front": "冬期",
      "back": "winter; wintertime"
    },
    {
      "front": "最大限",
      "back": "greatest; maximum"
    },
    {
      "front": "最小限",
      "back": "minimum"
    },
    {
      "front": "見限る",
      "back": "desert; give up"
    },
    {
      "front": "無期限",
      "back": "indefinite"
    },
    {
      "front": "コイン",
      "back": "coin"
    },
    {
      "front": "急所",
      "back": "vital part"
    },
    {
      "front": "急性",
      "back": "acute"
    },
    {
      "front": "性急",
      "back": "hasty; impatient"
    },
    {
      "front": "急遽",
      "back": "in a hurry; in haste"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ切り無しに",
      "back": "incessantly"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い切る",
      "back": "resolve"
    },
    {
      "front": "割り切る",
      "back": "divide; give a clear-cut solution"
    },
    {
      "front": "貸し切り",
      "back": "booked; reserved"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり切れない",
      "back": "be unbearable"
    },
    {
      "front": "そもそも",
      "back": "in the first place"
    },
    {
      "front": "賃貸",
      "back": "hiring out; lease"
    },
    {
      "front": "代行",
      "back": "agent; proxy"
    },
    {
      "front": "代理",
      "back": "agency; representation"
    },
    {
      "front": "代代",
      "back": "generation after generation"
    },
    {
      "front": "お代わり",
      "back": "second helping"
    },
    {
      "front": "指切り",
      "back": "pledging by hooking each other's pinkies"
    },
    {
      "front": "指紋",
      "back": "fingerprint"
    },
    {
      "front": "タッチ",
      "back": "touch"
    },
    {
      "front": "制止",
      "back": "check; restraint"
    },
    {
      "front": "定規",
      "back": "rule; ruler"
    },
    {
      "front": "鑑定",
      "back": "appraisal; judgment"
    },
    {
      "front": "暫定",
      "back": "provisional; tentative"
    },
    {
      "front": "予告",
      "back": "advance notice"
    },
    {
      "front": "予知",
      "back": "foreknowledge"
    },
    {
      "front": "予期",
      "back": "anticipation; expectation"
    },
    {
      "front": "予て",
      "back": "already; lately"
    },
    {
      "front": "猶予",
      "back": "postponement"
    },
    {
      "front": "チェーン",
      "back": "chain"
    },
    {
      "front": "解約",
      "back": "dissolution of a contract"
    },
    {
      "front": "要約",
      "back": "summary"
    },
    {
      "front": "束ねる",
      "back": "tie up in a bundle"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウイルス",
      "back": "virus"
    },
    {
      "front": "不変",
      "back": "eternal; unchanging"
    },
    {
      "front": "急変",
      "back": "sudden change"
    },
    {
      "front": "変貌",
      "back": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "front": "帰化",
      "back": "naturalization"
    },
    {
      "front": "合理化",
      "back": "rationalization"
    },
    {
      "front": "化け物",
      "back": "ghost; monster"
    },
    {
      "front": "お化け",
      "back": "ghost"
    },
    {
      "front": "軟化",
      "back": "softening; weakening"
    },
    {
      "front": "磁石",
      "back": "compass; magnet"
    },
    {
      "front": "フィクション",
      "back": "fiction"
    },
    {
      "front": "満更",
      "back": "altogether; wholly"
    },
    {
      "front": "更ける",
      "back": "advance; grow late"
    },
    {
      "front": "日増しに",
      "back": "day by day"
    },
    {
      "front": "水増し",
      "back": "dilution; watering"
    },
    {
      "front": "半減",
      "back": "50 percent reduction"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り気",
      "back": "keenness to do"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗用車",
      "back": "automobile"
    },
    {
      "front": "便乗",
      "back": "advantageous opportunity"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗り回す",
      "back": "drive about"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗じる",
      "back": "take advantage of"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗ずる",
      "back": "taking advantage of"
    },
    {
      "front": "搭乗",
      "back": "boarding; embarkation"
    },
    {
      "front": "キャンパス",
      "back": "campus"
    },
    {
      "front": "下降",
      "back": "descent; subsidence"
    },
    {
      "front": "不時着",
      "back": "emergency landing"
    },
    {
      "front": "必着",
      "back": "to be delivered"
    },
    {
      "front": "定着",
      "back": "fastening; fixing"
    },
    {
      "front": "着々",
      "back": "steadily"
    },
    {
      "front": "癒着",
      "back": "adhesion; connection"
    },
    {
      "front": "スムーズ",
      "back": "smooth"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱水",
      "back": "dehydration"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱走",
      "back": "desertion; escape"
    },
    {
      "front": "国税",
      "back": "national tax"
    },
    {
      "front": "増税",
      "back": "tax increase"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱税",
      "back": "tax evasion"
    },
    {
      "front": "課税",
      "back": "taxation"
    },
    {
      "front": "分立",
      "back": "separation"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち話",
      "back": "stand talking"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち読み",
      "back": "browsing"
    },
    {
      "front": "生い立ち",
      "back": "one's childhood; one's upbringing"
    },
    {
      "front": "あくまで",
      "back": "in the end; stubbornly"
    },
    {
      "front": "出欠",
      "back": "attendance"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠けら",
      "back": "chip; fragment"
    },
    {
      "front": "運行",
      "back": "movement; revolution"
    },
    {
      "front": "運休",
      "back": "suspension of service"
    },
    {
      "front": "運良く",
      "back": "fortunately; luckily"
    },
    {
      "front": "カップル",
      "back": "couple"
    },
    {
      "front": "移植",
      "back": "transplant"
    },
    {
      "front": "言動",
      "back": "speech and behavior"
    },
    {
      "front": "作動",
      "back": "operation"
    },
    {
      "front": "動じる",
      "back": "be moved with emotion"
    },
    {
      "front": "動もすれば",
      "back": "be inclined to"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドキュメント",
      "back": "document"
    },
    {
      "front": "売春",
      "back": "prostitution"
    },
    {
      "front": "早春",
      "back": "early spring"
    },
    {
      "front": "早引き",
      "back": "early leaving"
    },
    {
      "front": "早期",
      "back": "early stage"
    },
    {
      "front": "早々と",
      "back": "early; quickly"
    },
    {
      "front": "風速",
      "back": "wind velocity"
    },
    {
      "front": "減速",
      "back": "deceleration"
    },
    {
      "front": "速やか",
      "back": "quick; swift"
    },
    {
      "front": "後始末",
      "back": "cleaning up; settlement"
    },
    {
      "front": "不始末",
      "back": "mismanagement"
    },
    {
      "front": "ノンフィクション",
      "back": "nonfiction"
    },
    {
      "front": "符号",
      "back": "mark; sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "終着駅",
      "back": "terminal station"
    },
    {
      "front": "終止符",
      "back": "period"
    },
    {
      "front": "臨終",
      "back": "deathbed; one's last moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "出現",
      "back": "appearance; emergence"
    },
    {
      "front": "現役",
      "back": "active service"
    },
    {
      "front": "現に",
      "back": "actually; really"
    },
    {
      "front": "在日",
      "back": "in Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "口実",
      "back": "excuse; pretext"
    },
    {
      "front": "実家",
      "back": "one's parents' home"
    },
    {
      "front": "実話",
      "back": "true story"
    },
    {
      "front": "無実",
      "back": "innocent"
    },
    {
      "front": "実名",
      "back": "one's real name"
    },
    {
      "front": "着実",
      "back": "solid; steady"
    },
    {
      "front": "実在",
      "back": "entity; real existence"
    },
    {
      "front": "マネージャー",
      "back": "manager"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き渡る",
      "back": "pervade"
    },
    {
      "front": "行き過ぎ",
      "back": "going too far"
    },
    {
      "front": "過半数",
      "back": "majority"
    },
    {
      "front": "見過ごす",
      "back": "let go by; overlook"
    },
    {
      "front": "過渡期",
      "back": "transitional period"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり過ごす",
      "back": "let go past"
    },
    {
      "front": "過剰",
      "back": "excess; surplus"
    },
    {
      "front": "仕送り",
      "back": "sending of money"
    },
    {
      "front": "発火",
      "back": "combustion; ignition"
    },
    {
      "front": "発足",
      "back": "inauguration; starting"
    },
    {
      "front": "発覚",
      "back": "disclosure"
    },
    {
      "front": "発送",
      "back": "forwarding; sending"
    },
    {
      "front": "発着",
      "back": "departure and arrival"
    },
    {
      "front": "発する",
      "back": "emit; radiate"
    },
    {
      "front": "発揮",
      "back": "demonstration; display"
    },
    {
      "front": "ネーム",
      "back": "name; name badge"
    },
    {
      "front": "年表",
      "back": "chronological table"
    },
    {
      "front": "表通り",
      "back": "main street"
    },
    {
      "front": "図表",
      "back": "chart; diagram"
    },
    {
      "front": "銀紙",
      "back": "aluminum foil"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちり紙",
      "back": "tissue paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "鼻紙",
      "back": "tissue paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "紙幣",
      "back": "bank note"
    },
    {
      "front": "か弱い",
      "back": "frail; weak"
    },
    {
      "front": "高音",
      "back": "high-pitched sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "低音",
      "back": "bass; low-pitched sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "音読",
      "back": "read aloud"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱音",
      "back": "complaints"
    },
    {
      "front": "漢文",
      "back": "Chinese classics; Chinese writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "火薬",
      "back": "gunpowder"
    },
    {
      "front": "漢方薬",
      "back": "Chinese medicine"
    },
    {
      "front": "製薬",
      "back": "pharmaceutical manufacture"
    },
    {
      "front": "医薬品",
      "back": "pharmaceuticals"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダイヤル",
      "back": "dial"
    },
    {
      "front": "無欲",
      "back": "unselfish"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲する",
      "back": "desire; want; wish"
    },
    {
      "front": "上映",
      "back": "screening"
    },
    {
      "front": "字画",
      "back": "stroke-count"
    },
    {
      "front": "画用紙",
      "back": "drawing paper"
    },
    {
      "front": "画数",
      "back": "stroke-count"
    },
    {
      "front": "絵画",
      "back": "paintings; pictures"
    },
    {
      "front": "画する",
      "back": "mark off; plan"
    },
    {
      "front": "アレルギー",
      "back": "allergy; be allergic"
    },
    {
      "front": "外面",
      "back": "exterior; outside"
    },
    {
      "front": "内面",
      "back": "inside; interior"
    },
    {
      "front": "海面",
      "back": "surface of the sea"
    },
    {
      "front": "面子",
      "back": "face; honor"
    },
    {
      "front": "満面",
      "back": "whole face"
    },
    {
      "front": "他面",
      "back": "other side"
    },
    {
      "front": "赤面",
      "back": "blush; red-faced"
    },
    {
      "front": "紙面",
      "back": "newspapers; space"
    },
    {
      "front": "面",
      "back": "face; look"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダイヤ",
      "back": "train schedule"
    },
    {
      "front": "写生",
      "back": "sketching"
    },
    {
      "front": "複写",
      "back": "copy; duplication"
    },
    {
      "front": "真価",
      "back": "true value"
    },
    {
      "front": "真",
      "back": "reality; truth"
    },
    {
      "front": "真に",
      "back": "indeed; truly"
    },
    {
      "front": "音色",
      "back": "tone"
    },
    {
      "front": "橙色",
      "back": "orange"
    },
    {
      "front": "手形",
      "back": "hand print; promissory note"
    },
    {
      "front": "形見",
      "back": "keepsake; memento"
    },
    {
      "front": "図形",
      "back": "diagram; figure"
    },
    {
      "front": "無形",
      "back": "immaterial; intangible"
    },
    {
      "front": "形作る",
      "back": "form; make; shape"
    },
    {
      "front": "定形",
      "back": "fixed form"
    },
    {
      "front": "変形",
      "back": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "front": "楕円形",
      "back": "oval"
    },
    {
      "front": "体型",
      "back": "figure; form"
    },
    {
      "front": "定型",
      "back": "definite form; type"
    },
    {
      "front": "コットン",
      "back": "cotton"
    },
    {
      "front": "種々",
      "back": "many types; various"
    },
    {
      "front": "思い直す",
      "back": "reconsider"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ち直す",
      "back": "improve; rally"
    },
    {
      "front": "立て直す",
      "back": "rally; reorganize"
    },
    {
      "front": "直に",
      "back": "at once; soon"
    },
    {
      "front": "直に",
      "back": "directly; personally"
    },
    {
      "front": "本線",
      "back": "main line; trunk line"
    },
    {
      "front": "多角",
      "back": "diversified"
    },
    {
      "front": "角",
      "back": "horn; tentacle"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミックス",
      "back": "mix; mixture"
    },
    {
      "front": "共有",
      "back": "common; joint"
    },
    {
      "front": "共用",
      "back": "communal"
    },
    {
      "front": "共々",
      "back": "in common; together"
    },
    {
      "front": "お共",
      "back": "accompaniment"
    },
    {
      "front": "類型",
      "back": "type"
    },
    {
      "front": "同上",
      "back": "as above; ditto"
    },
    {
      "front": "同期",
      "back": "same period"
    },
    {
      "front": "同化",
      "back": "assimilation"
    },
    {
      "front": "同音",
      "back": "homophonous"
    },
    {
      "front": "同類",
      "back": "same class; same kind"
    },
    {
      "front": "同伴",
      "back": "accompanying"
    },
    {
      "front": "同棲",
      "back": "living together"
    },
    {
      "front": "アピール",
      "back": "appeal; attraction"
    },
    {
      "front": "気違い",
      "back": "insanity; lunatic"
    },
    {
      "front": "食い違い",
      "back": "cross-purposes; difference"
    },
    {
      "front": "場違い",
      "back": "out of place; wrong place"
    },
    {
      "front": "違法",
      "back": "illegality"
    },
    {
      "front": "似合い",
      "back": "becoming; well-matched"
    },
    {
      "front": "旅立つ",
      "back": "set off"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨宿り",
      "back": "shelter from the rain"
    },
    {
      "front": "合宿",
      "back": "lodge together"
    },
    {
      "front": "宿屋",
      "back": "hotel; inn"
    },
    {
      "front": "宿",
      "back": "inn; lodging"
    },
    {
      "front": "宿泊",
      "back": "lodging"
    },
    {
      "front": "温もり",
      "back": "warmth"
    },
    {
      "front": "日和",
      "back": "fine weather; weather"
    },
    {
      "front": "共和国",
      "back": "republic"
    },
    {
      "front": "和解",
      "back": "reconciliation; settlement"
    },
    {
      "front": "和歌",
      "back": "Japanese poem"
    },
    {
      "front": "和む",
      "back": "be softened; become calm"
    },
    {
      "front": "カロリー",
      "back": "calorie"
    },
    {
      "front": "服用",
      "back": "dose"
    },
    {
      "front": "入室",
      "back": "entering a room"
    },
    {
      "front": "客室",
      "back": "guest room; stateroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "温室",
      "back": "greenhouse; hothouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "母国語",
      "back": "one's native language"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドクター",
      "back": "doctor; medic"
    },
    {
      "front": "親日",
      "back": "pro-Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "親睦",
      "back": "amity; friendliness"
    },
    {
      "front": "弟子入り",
      "back": "acolyte; follower"
    },
    {
      "front": "弟子",
      "back": "disciple; pupil"
    },
    {
      "front": "息切れ",
      "back": "breathlessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゴール",
      "back": "finish; goal; target"
    },
    {
      "front": "当事者",
      "back": "the person concerned"
    },
    {
      "front": "他者",
      "back": "another person; other people"
    },
    {
      "front": "役者",
      "back": "actor; actress"
    },
    {
      "front": "結末",
      "back": "conclusion; end"
    },
    {
      "front": "結う",
      "back": "do up; dress"
    },
    {
      "front": "果実",
      "back": "berry; fruit"
    },
    {
      "front": "果てしない",
      "back": "boundless; endless"
    },
    {
      "front": "自明",
      "back": "obvious; self-evident"
    },
    {
      "front": "自白",
      "back": "admission; confession"
    },
    {
      "front": "自活",
      "back": "self-support"
    },
    {
      "front": "自問",
      "back": "self doubt"
    },
    {
      "front": "自営業",
      "back": "self-employment"
    },
    {
      "front": "自営",
      "back": "independent"
    },
    {
      "front": "エッセイ",
      "back": "essay"
    },
    {
      "front": "由来",
      "back": "history; origin"
    },
    {
      "front": "由",
      "back": "means; reason"
    },
    {
      "front": "不信",
      "back": "discredit; distrust"
    },
    {
      "front": "送信",
      "back": "transmission"
    },
    {
      "front": "受信",
      "back": "reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "返信",
      "back": "answer; reply"
    },
    {
      "front": "発信",
      "back": "sending of a letter"
    },
    {
      "front": "信ずる",
      "back": "believe; have faith"
    },
    {
      "front": "頼りない",
      "back": "helpless; vague"
    },
    {
      "front": "民話",
      "back": "folk story; folk tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "難民",
      "back": "refugee"
    },
    {
      "front": "民法",
      "back": "civil law"
    },
    {
      "front": "株主",
      "back": "stockholder"
    },
    {
      "front": "主",
      "back": "master; owner"
    },
    {
      "front": "主",
      "back": "master"
    },
    {
      "front": "主として",
      "back": "chiefly; mainly"
    },
    {
      "front": "亭主",
      "back": "husband; master"
    },
    {
      "front": "チャンピオン",
      "back": "champion; titleholder"
    },
    {
      "front": "名義",
      "back": "name; title"
    },
    {
      "front": "義父",
      "back": "father-in-law"
    },
    {
      "front": "義母",
      "back": "mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "front": "利己主義",
      "back": "egoism"
    },
    {
      "front": "口論",
      "back": "argument"
    },
    {
      "front": "論ずる",
      "back": "discuss"
    },
    {
      "front": "総論",
      "back": "introduction; outline"
    },
    {
      "front": "パンフレット",
      "back": "pamphlet"
    },
    {
      "front": "反日",
      "back": "anti-Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "反作用",
      "back": "reaction"
    },
    {
      "front": "反動",
      "back": "backlash; recoil"
    },
    {
      "front": "反面",
      "back": "the other side"
    },
    {
      "front": "反る",
      "back": "curve; warp"
    },
    {
      "front": "対日",
      "back": "toward Japan"
    },
    {
      "front": "接待",
      "back": "reception entertainment"
    },
    {
      "front": "手応え",
      "back": "resistance; response"
    },
    {
      "front": "応接",
      "back": "reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "応対",
      "back": "address; reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "応ずる",
      "back": "accept; comply"
    },
    {
      "front": "マクロ",
      "back": "macro"
    },
    {
      "front": "押し売り",
      "back": "high-pressure sales"
    },
    {
      "front": "口答え",
      "back": "back talk"
    },
    {
      "front": "押し問答",
      "back": "argument"
    },
    {
      "front": "答申",
      "back": "reply; report"
    },
    {
      "front": "応答",
      "back": "answer; response"
    },
    {
      "front": "特売",
      "back": "special sale"
    },
    {
      "front": "特質",
      "back": "characteristic"
    },
    {
      "front": "スプレー",
      "back": "atomizer; spray"
    },
    {
      "front": "個",
      "back": "individual"
    },
    {
      "front": "分別",
      "back": "classification; separation"
    },
    {
      "front": "分別",
      "back": "discretion; prudence"
    },
    {
      "front": "大別",
      "back": "division into major classes"
    },
    {
      "front": "格別",
      "back": "particular"
    },
    {
      "front": "別名",
      "back": "alias; another name"
    },
    {
      "front": "別問題",
      "back": "another question"
    },
    {
      "front": "別個",
      "back": "another; separate"
    },
    {
      "front": "別荘",
      "back": "second home"
    },
    {
      "front": "的中",
      "back": "hitting of the mark"
    },
    {
      "front": "人道的",
      "back": "humane; humanitarian"
    },
    {
      "front": "内向的",
      "back": "introverted"
    },
    {
      "front": "後天的",
      "back": "acquired; learned"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽天的",
      "back": "optimistic"
    },
    {
      "front": "社交的",
      "back": "friendly; sociable"
    },
    {
      "front": "末期的",
      "back": "decadent; terminal"
    },
    {
      "front": "能動的",
      "back": "active"
    },
    {
      "front": "受動的",
      "back": "passive"
    },
    {
      "front": "打算的",
      "back": "calculating; self-centered"
    },
    {
      "front": "性的",
      "back": "sexual"
    },
    {
      "front": "必然的",
      "back": "inevitable"
    },
    {
      "front": "法的",
      "back": "legal; legalistic"
    },
    {
      "front": "画期的",
      "back": "epoch-making; epochal"
    },
    {
      "front": "自発的",
      "back": "spontaneous; voluntary"
    },
    {
      "front": "劇的",
      "back": "dramatic"
    },
    {
      "front": "リモコン",
      "back": "remote-control"
    },
    {
      "front": "並行",
      "back": "parallel; side by side"
    },
    {
      "front": "人並み",
      "back": "like others"
    },
    {
      "front": "町並み",
      "back": "the look of a street"
    },
    {
      "front": "並び",
      "back": "line; side"
    },
    {
      "front": "バレエ",
      "back": "ballet"
    },
    {
      "front": "平年",
      "back": "normal year"
    },
    {
      "front": "和平",
      "back": "peace"
    },
    {
      "front": "均一",
      "back": "equality; uniformity"
    },
    {
      "front": "一等",
      "back": "first class"
    },
    {
      "front": "等分",
      "back": "equal division"
    },
    {
      "front": "下等",
      "back": "inferior; low; lower"
    },
    {
      "front": "等価",
      "back": "equivalence; parity"
    },
    {
      "front": "均等",
      "back": "equality; uniformity"
    },
    {
      "front": "病弱",
      "back": "weak; weakly"
    },
    {
      "front": "ロケット",
      "back": "locket; rocket"
    },
    {
      "front": "寺院",
      "back": "temple"
    },
    {
      "front": "入れ歯",
      "back": "dentures; false teeth"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯向かう",
      "back": "oppose; stand up to"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯車",
      "back": "cog; toothed wheel"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯止め",
      "back": "brake; drag"
    },
    {
      "front": "歯痒い",
      "back": "be irritating"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち去る",
      "back": "leave; quit"
    },
    {
      "front": "死人",
      "back": "corpse; dead person"
    },
    {
      "front": "死去",
      "back": "death; passing away"
    },
    {
      "front": "禁欲的",
      "back": "abstemious"
    },
    {
      "front": "煙い",
      "back": "smoky"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋書",
      "back": "foreign book"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋酒",
      "back": "foreign wine"
    },
    {
      "front": "力一杯",
      "back": "with full force"
    },
    {
      "front": "ターミナル",
      "back": "bus terminal; terminal"
    },
    {
      "front": "危うく",
      "back": "almost; nearly"
    },
    {
      "front": "危うい",
      "back": "dangerous; uncertain"
    },
    {
      "front": "危篤",
      "back": "on the verge of death"
    },
    {
      "front": "危惧",
      "back": "fear; misgivings"
    },
    {
      "front": "保安",
      "back": "preservation of public peace"
    },
    {
      "front": "担保",
      "back": "mortgage; security"
    },
    {
      "front": "思う存分",
      "back": "to one's heart's content"
    },
    {
      "front": "共存",
      "back": "coexistence"
    },
    {
      "front": "シンポジウム",
      "back": "symposium"
    },
    {
      "front": "不本意",
      "back": "reluctant; unwilling"
    },
    {
      "front": "意気地",
      "back": "honor; pride"
    },
    {
      "front": "故意",
      "back": "intention; purpose"
    },
    {
      "front": "有意義",
      "back": "significant; useful"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪意",
      "back": "malicious intent"
    },
    {
      "front": "不意に",
      "back": "suddenly; unexpectedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "要注意",
      "back": "attention required"
    },
    {
      "front": "真意",
      "back": "real intention; true meaning"
    },
    {
      "front": "意",
      "back": "feelings; opinion"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピーク",
      "back": "peak"
    },
    {
      "front": "的確",
      "back": "accurate; precise"
    },
    {
      "front": "率先",
      "back": "initiative; leadership"
    },
    {
      "front": "利率",
      "back": "interest rate"
    },
    {
      "front": "機体",
      "back": "fuselage; machine"
    },
    {
      "front": "有機物",
      "back": "organic matter"
    },
    {
      "front": "無機物",
      "back": "inorganic substance"
    },
    {
      "front": "待機",
      "back": "stand by; waiting"
    },
    {
      "front": "機動隊",
      "back": "riot police"
    },
    {
      "front": "機敏",
      "back": "quickness; sharpness"
    },
    {
      "front": "ランニング",
      "back": "jogging; running"
    },
    {
      "front": "木材",
      "back": "timber; wood"
    },
    {
      "front": "用具",
      "back": "outfit; tool"
    },
    {
      "front": "絵の具",
      "back": "paint"
    },
    {
      "front": "具える",
      "back": "equip; provide with"
    },
    {
      "front": "具わる",
      "back": "furnish; provide"
    },
    {
      "front": "準える",
      "back": "compare; liken"
    },
    {
      "front": "校則",
      "back": "school regulations"
    },
    {
      "front": "備考",
      "back": "remarks"
    },
    {
      "front": "不備",
      "back": "defect; imperfection"
    },
    {
      "front": "予備校",
      "back": "preparatory school"
    },
    {
      "front": "説教",
      "back": "preaching; scolding"
    },
    {
      "front": "教諭",
      "back": "instructor; teacher"
    },
    {
      "front": "行使",
      "back": "employment; use"
    },
    {
      "front": "認め",
      "back": "approval"
    },
    {
      "front": "公明",
      "back": "fairness; justice"
    },
    {
      "front": "公言",
      "back": "public declaration"
    },
    {
      "front": "公使",
      "back": "minister"
    },
    {
      "front": "公営",
      "back": "public management"
    },
    {
      "front": "公定",
      "back": "official"
    },
    {
      "front": "公約",
      "back": "public pledge"
    },
    {
      "front": "公表",
      "back": "proclamation; public announcement"
    },
    {
      "front": "公民館",
      "back": "public hall"
    },
    {
      "front": "シンボル",
      "back": "emblem; symbol"
    },
    {
      "front": "園芸",
      "back": "gardening"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミサイル",
      "back": "missile"
    },
    {
      "front": "洞察",
      "back": "insight; penetration"
    },
    {
      "front": "偵察",
      "back": "scouting"
    },
    {
      "front": "同窓会",
      "back": "alumni association"
    },
    {
      "front": "手際良く",
      "back": "cleverly; skillfully"
    },
    {
      "front": "間際",
      "back": "just before"
    },
    {
      "front": "際限",
      "back": "end; limits"
    },
    {
      "front": "際立つ",
      "back": "be conspicuous"
    },
    {
      "front": "窓際",
      "back": "by the window"
    },
    {
      "front": "ベランダ",
      "back": "veranda"
    },
    {
      "front": "航路",
      "back": "course; sea route"
    },
    {
      "front": "難航",
      "back": "rough going"
    },
    {
      "front": "造船",
      "back": "shipbuilding"
    },
    {
      "front": "成分",
      "back": "component; ingredient"
    },
    {
      "front": "成り行き",
      "back": "course of events"
    },
    {
      "front": "持て成し",
      "back": "hospitality; treatment"
    },
    {
      "front": "成算",
      "back": "prospects of success"
    },
    {
      "front": "既成",
      "back": "established; existing"
    },
    {
      "front": "ロビー",
      "back": "lobby"
    },
    {
      "front": "見失う",
      "back": "lose sight of"
    },
    {
      "front": "過失",
      "back": "error; negligence"
    },
    {
      "front": "喪失",
      "back": "forfeit; loss"
    },
    {
      "front": "川原",
      "back": "dry riverbed"
    },
    {
      "front": "原告",
      "back": "plaintiff"
    },
    {
      "front": "原始",
      "back": "primeval; primitive"
    },
    {
      "front": "原稿",
      "back": "draft; manuscript"
    },
    {
      "front": "資本",
      "back": "capital; funds"
    },
    {
      "front": "資本家",
      "back": "capitalist"
    },
    {
      "front": "請求",
      "back": "demand; request"
    },
    {
      "front": "出願",
      "back": "application"
    },
    {
      "front": "請願",
      "back": "petition"
    },
    {
      "front": "願わくは",
      "back": "I pray; I wish"
    },
    {
      "front": "祈願",
      "back": "prayer"
    },
    {
      "front": "メカニズム",
      "back": "mechanism"
    },
    {
      "front": "正体",
      "back": "true characters"
    },
    {
      "front": "正面",
      "back": "front; frontage"
    },
    {
      "front": "公正",
      "back": "fairness; justice"
    },
    {
      "front": "正す",
      "back": "correct; set right"
    },
    {
      "front": "特異",
      "back": "peculiar; unique"
    },
    {
      "front": "常用漢字",
      "back": "Chinese characters for daily use"
    },
    {
      "front": "常用",
      "back": "common use; daily use"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちょっぴり",
      "back": "just a little; morsel"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩調",
      "back": "pace; step"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り調べ",
      "back": "inquiry; investigation"
    },
    {
      "front": "整数",
      "back": "integer"
    },
    {
      "front": "均整",
      "back": "symmetry"
    },
    {
      "front": "整頓",
      "back": "arrangement"
    },
    {
      "front": "お節料理",
      "back": "festive food for the New Year"
    },
    {
      "front": "使節",
      "back": "ambassador; envoy"
    },
    {
      "front": "節",
      "back": "joint; melody"
    },
    {
      "front": "ドーナツ",
      "back": "donut"
    },
    {
      "front": "証書",
      "back": "bond; certificate"
    },
    {
      "front": "検定",
      "back": "examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "検証",
      "back": "verification"
    },
    {
      "front": "検察",
      "back": "criminal investigation; prosecution"
    },
    {
      "front": "明暗",
      "back": "contrast; light and dark"
    },
    {
      "front": "図示",
      "back": "diagram; illustration"
    },
    {
      "front": "あいつ",
      "back": "that guy"
    },
    {
      "front": "識別",
      "back": "distinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "標本",
      "back": "sample; specimen"
    },
    {
      "front": "標識",
      "back": "beacon; sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "連中",
      "back": "party; those fellows"
    },
    {
      "front": "連合",
      "back": "alliance"
    },
    {
      "front": "続出",
      "back": "one after another"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き続き",
      "back": "continuously"
    },
    {
      "front": "立て続けに",
      "back": "in succession"
    },
    {
      "front": "スパイ",
      "back": "spy"
    },
    {
      "front": "人相",
      "back": "looks; physiognomy"
    },
    {
      "front": "世相",
      "back": "phases of life; social conditions"
    },
    {
      "front": "不相応",
      "back": "unbecoming; unsuited"
    },
    {
      "front": "相違",
      "back": "difference; disparity"
    },
    {
      "front": "相対的",
      "back": "relative"
    },
    {
      "front": "相続",
      "back": "inheritance; succession"
    },
    {
      "front": "談話",
      "back": "conversation; talking"
    },
    {
      "front": "商談",
      "back": "business talk; negotiations"
    },
    {
      "front": "面談",
      "back": "interview"
    },
    {
      "front": "さっさと",
      "back": "quickly; without delay"
    },
    {
      "front": "明記",
      "back": "clarification; specification"
    },
    {
      "front": "書記",
      "back": "clerk; secretary"
    },
    {
      "front": "表記",
      "back": "writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "登記",
      "back": "registration; registry"
    },
    {
      "front": "関門",
      "back": "barrier; gateway"
    },
    {
      "front": "機関車",
      "back": "locomotive"
    },
    {
      "front": "難関",
      "back": "barrier; obstacle"
    },
    {
      "front": "相関",
      "back": "correlation; mutual relationship"
    },
    {
      "front": "病状",
      "back": "condition of a disease"
    },
    {
      "front": "実況",
      "back": "actual conditions"
    },
    {
      "front": "生態",
      "back": "ecology; mode of life"
    },
    {
      "front": "政界",
      "back": "political world"
    },
    {
      "front": "政局",
      "back": "political situation"
    },
    {
      "front": "自治",
      "back": "autonomy"
    },
    {
      "front": "治める",
      "back": "govern"
    },
    {
      "front": "コンプレックス",
      "back": "complex; inferiority complex"
    },
    {
      "front": "選り分ける",
      "back": "classify; sort out"
    },
    {
      "front": "選出",
      "back": "election"
    },
    {
      "front": "選定",
      "back": "choice; selection"
    },
    {
      "front": "予選",
      "back": "preliminary match; primary election"
    },
    {
      "front": "選る",
      "back": "select"
    },
    {
      "front": "立候補",
      "back": "candidacy"
    },
    {
      "front": "補欠",
      "back": "substitute"
    },
    {
      "front": "補正",
      "back": "correction; revision"
    },
    {
      "front": "補佐",
      "back": "assistance; help"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビジネスマン",
      "back": "business man"
    },
    {
      "front": "大脳",
      "back": "cerebrum"
    },
    {
      "front": "脳死",
      "back": "brain death"
    },
    {
      "front": "年頭",
      "back": "beginning of the year"
    },
    {
      "front": "石頭",
      "back": "obstinate"
    },
    {
      "front": "頭脳",
      "back": "brain; brains"
    },
    {
      "front": "顔立ち",
      "back": "features; looks"
    },
    {
      "front": "似顔絵",
      "back": "likeness; portrait"
    },
    {
      "front": "顔なじみ",
      "back": "familiar face; friend"
    },
    {
      "front": "命日",
      "back": "anniversary of death"
    },
    {
      "front": "亡命",
      "back": "exile"
    },
    {
      "front": "命ずる",
      "back": "appoint; order"
    },
    {
      "front": "致命的",
      "back": "fatal"
    },
    {
      "front": "ファスナー",
      "back": "zip fastener; zipper"
    },
    {
      "front": "領空",
      "back": "airspace"
    },
    {
      "front": "領収",
      "back": "receipt"
    },
    {
      "front": "要領",
      "back": "gist"
    },
    {
      "front": "先進国",
      "back": "developed country"
    },
    {
      "front": "進入",
      "back": "penetration entry"
    },
    {
      "front": "直進",
      "back": "straight on"
    },
    {
      "front": "スリップ",
      "back": "skid; slip"
    },
    {
      "front": "推量",
      "back": "conjecture; guess"
    },
    {
      "front": "推敲",
      "back": "polishing; refinement"
    },
    {
      "front": "責める",
      "back": "blame; torture"
    },
    {
      "front": "任期",
      "back": "one's term of office"
    },
    {
      "front": "任意",
      "back": "arbitrary; optional"
    },
    {
      "front": "バイブル",
      "back": "Bible"
    },
    {
      "front": "委任",
      "back": "entrustment"
    },
    {
      "front": "委ねる",
      "back": "entrust"
    },
    {
      "front": "託す",
      "back": "entrust"
    },
    {
      "front": "法務",
      "back": "judicial affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "専務",
      "back": "managing director"
    },
    {
      "front": "公務",
      "back": "official affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "服従",
      "back": "obedience; submission"
    },
    {
      "front": "従える",
      "back": "be accompanied by; conquer"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミシン",
      "back": "sewing machine"
    },
    {
      "front": "集会",
      "back": "gathering; meeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "全集",
      "back": "complete works"
    },
    {
      "front": "集る",
      "back": "extort"
    },
    {
      "front": "採取",
      "back": "collecting; picking"
    },
    {
      "front": "日給",
      "back": "daily wage"
    },
    {
      "front": "初任給",
      "back": "initial salary"
    },
    {
      "front": "チューリップ",
      "back": "tulip"
    },
    {
      "front": "職人",
      "back": "artisan; craftsman"
    },
    {
      "front": "内職",
      "back": "moonlight; side job"
    },
    {
      "front": "無職",
      "back": "unemployed; without occupation"
    },
    {
      "front": "汚職",
      "back": "bribery; corruption"
    },
    {
      "front": "中退",
      "back": "dropping out"
    },
    {
      "front": "引退",
      "back": "retirement"
    },
    {
      "front": "立ち退く",
      "back": "leave; vacate"
    },
    {
      "front": "退く",
      "back": "back; retreat"
    },
    {
      "front": "退ける",
      "back": "drive away; keep away"
    },
    {
      "front": "退ける",
      "back": "drive away"
    },
    {
      "front": "こなす",
      "back": "handle easily"
    },
    {
      "front": "妥当",
      "back": "appropriate; proper"
    },
    {
      "front": "不条理",
      "back": "absurdity"
    },
    {
      "front": "無条件",
      "back": "unconditional; unqualified"
    },
    {
      "front": "持参",
      "back": "bring with one; carry"
    },
    {
      "front": "降参",
      "back": "submission; surrender"
    },
    {
      "front": "加減",
      "back": "adjustment; in moderation"
    },
    {
      "front": "加速",
      "back": "acceleration"
    },
    {
      "front": "究明",
      "back": "investigation; study"
    },
    {
      "front": "追究",
      "back": "thorough investigation"
    },
    {
      "front": "追求",
      "back": "pursuit"
    },
    {
      "front": "加盟",
      "back": "affiliation"
    },
    {
      "front": "そいつ",
      "back": "that person"
    },
    {
      "front": "比",
      "back": "comparison; ratio"
    },
    {
      "front": "比喩",
      "back": "metaphor; simile"
    },
    {
      "front": "判明",
      "back": "clarification; clarity"
    },
    {
      "front": "判事",
      "back": "judge"
    },
    {
      "front": "評論",
      "back": "comment; criticism"
    },
    {
      "front": "評",
      "back": "comment; review"
    },
    {
      "front": "好感",
      "back": "good feeling"
    },
    {
      "front": "感受性",
      "back": "sensibility"
    },
    {
      "front": "感化",
      "back": "influence"
    },
    {
      "front": "感ずる",
      "back": "feel; sense"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひっそり",
      "back": "deserted; quiet"
    },
    {
      "front": "回想",
      "back": "remembrance"
    },
    {
      "front": "想定",
      "back": "hypothesis"
    },
    {
      "front": "発想",
      "back": "conception; expression"
    },
    {
      "front": "連想",
      "back": "association"
    },
    {
      "front": "画像",
      "back": "likeness; portrait"
    },
    {
      "front": "銅像",
      "back": "bronze statue"
    },
    {
      "front": "もとより",
      "back": "from the first"
    },
    {
      "front": "耳障り",
      "back": "stridency"
    },
    {
      "front": "修行",
      "back": "ascetic training"
    },
    {
      "front": "修学旅行",
      "back": "school excursion"
    },
    {
      "front": "修業",
      "back": "learning; study"
    },
    {
      "front": "修める",
      "back": "cultivate; master"
    },
    {
      "front": "軽はずみ",
      "back": "hastiness; rashness"
    },
    {
      "front": "重傷",
      "back": "heavy injury"
    },
    {
      "front": "軽傷",
      "back": "slight injury"
    },
    {
      "front": "傷む",
      "back": "be damaged; rot"
    },
    {
      "front": "しなやか",
      "back": "pliant"
    },
    {
      "front": "換気",
      "back": "ventilation"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き換え",
      "back": "exchange"
    },
    {
      "front": "利害",
      "back": "interests"
    },
    {
      "front": "加害者",
      "back": "assailant; assaulter"
    },
    {
      "front": "傷害",
      "back": "bodily harm; injury"
    },
    {
      "front": "弊害",
      "back": "abuse; evil"
    },
    {
      "front": "うっとり",
      "back": "enchanting"
    },
    {
      "front": "破局",
      "back": "catastrophe; collapse"
    },
    {
      "front": "破産",
      "back": "bankruptcy"
    },
    {
      "front": "後援",
      "back": "backing; support"
    },
    {
      "front": "管",
      "back": "pipe; tube"
    },
    {
      "front": "管轄",
      "back": "control; jurisdiction"
    },
    {
      "front": "只管",
      "back": "at all; in the least"
    },
    {
      "front": "有罪",
      "back": "guilt; guiltiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "無罪",
      "back": "innocence"
    },
    {
      "front": "謝罪",
      "back": "apology"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばれる",
      "back": "found out"
    },
    {
      "front": "人殺し",
      "back": "murder; murderer"
    },
    {
      "front": "殺気",
      "back": "stormy atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "front": "他殺",
      "back": "homicide; murder"
    },
    {
      "front": "相殺",
      "back": "cancellation; offset"
    },
    {
      "front": "虐殺",
      "back": "massacre; slaughter"
    },
    {
      "front": "捕らわれる",
      "back": "be caught"
    },
    {
      "front": "逃げ足",
      "back": "flight; running away"
    },
    {
      "front": "災い",
      "back": "disaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "戦車",
      "back": "tank"
    },
    {
      "front": "終戦",
      "back": "end of the war"
    },
    {
      "front": "反戦",
      "back": "antiwar"
    },
    {
      "front": "争議",
      "back": "dispute; strike"
    },
    {
      "front": "論争",
      "back": "argument; dispute"
    },
    {
      "front": "でっかい",
      "back": "big; huge"
    },
    {
      "front": "乱用",
      "back": "abuse; misuse"
    },
    {
      "front": "乱雑",
      "back": "confusion; disorder"
    },
    {
      "front": "動乱",
      "back": "disturbance; upheaval"
    },
    {
      "front": "紛れ",
      "back": "confusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "紛らす",
      "back": "beguile; divert"
    },
    {
      "front": "珍紛漢紛",
      "back": "gibberish"
    },
    {
      "front": "いろは",
      "back": "iroha; the Japanese syllabary"
    },
    {
      "front": "統治",
      "back": "government; rule"
    },
    {
      "front": "手探り",
      "back": "groping"
    },
    {
      "front": "探究",
      "back": "investigation; search"
    },
    {
      "front": "探る",
      "back": "probe; search into"
    },
    {
      "front": "四捨五入",
      "back": "rounding off"
    },
    {
      "front": "見捨てる",
      "back": "desert; forsake"
    },
    {
      "front": "使い捨て",
      "back": "disposable; throwaway"
    },
    {
      "front": "切り捨てる",
      "back": "cut down; omit"
    },
    {
      "front": "ミクロ",
      "back": "micro; microeconomics"
    },
    {
      "front": "用心深い",
      "back": "careful"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲深",
      "back": "greedy"
    },
    {
      "front": "欲深い",
      "back": "greedy"
    },
    {
      "front": "深み",
      "back": "depth; profundity"
    },
    {
      "front": "浅はか",
      "back": "frivolous; thoughtless"
    },
    {
      "front": "一段落",
      "back": "end of chapter; pause"
    },
    {
      "front": "手落ち",
      "back": "error; omission"
    },
    {
      "front": "落語",
      "back": "rakugo (Japanese comic story)"
    },
    {
      "front": "落ち合う",
      "back": "join; meet"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱落",
      "back": "be omitted; drop out"
    },
    {
      "front": "集落",
      "back": "colony; community"
    },
    {
      "front": "落ちこぼれ",
      "back": "dropout"
    },
    {
      "front": "堕落",
      "back": "corruption; degeneration"
    },
    {
      "front": "セメント",
      "back": "cement"
    },
    {
      "front": "電波",
      "back": "electromagnetic waves; radio waves"
    },
    {
      "front": "波長",
      "back": "wavelength"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒波",
      "back": "cold wave"
    },
    {
      "front": "波乱",
      "back": "disturbance; fluctuation"
    },
    {
      "front": "プロポーズ",
      "back": "proposal of marriage"
    },
    {
      "front": "流行歌",
      "back": "popular song"
    },
    {
      "front": "流石",
      "back": "just as expected; like"
    },
    {
      "front": "電流",
      "back": "electric current"
    },
    {
      "front": "風流",
      "back": "refined elegance"
    },
    {
      "front": "油田",
      "back": "oil field"
    },
    {
      "front": "浮かれる",
      "back": "be gay; become buoyant"
    },
    {
      "front": "しみじみ",
      "back": "fully; keenly"
    },
    {
      "front": "没頭",
      "back": "absorption"
    },
    {
      "front": "銀河",
      "back": "galaxy; Milky Way"
    },
    {
      "front": "運河",
      "back": "canal"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷水",
      "back": "cold water"
    },
    {
      "front": "寒冷",
      "back": "cold; coldness"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷戦",
      "back": "Cold War"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷ややか",
      "back": "cold; frigid"
    },
    {
      "front": "冷や汗",
      "back": "cold sweat"
    },
    {
      "front": "ニュアンス",
      "back": "nuance"
    },
    {
      "front": "凍結",
      "back": "freezing"
    },
    {
      "front": "凍える",
      "back": "be chilled; be frozen"
    },
    {
      "front": "不快",
      "back": "unpleasant"
    },
    {
      "front": "快速",
      "back": "fast train; high speed"
    },
    {
      "front": "快楽",
      "back": "enjoyment; pleasure"
    },
    {
      "front": "適量",
      "back": "proper quantity"
    },
    {
      "front": "適齢期",
      "back": "marriageable age"
    },
    {
      "front": "摘発",
      "back": "exposure; laying bare"
    },
    {
      "front": "摘む",
      "back": "pick; pluck"
    },
    {
      "front": "涼む",
      "back": "cool oneself"
    },
    {
      "front": "染色",
      "back": "dyeing"
    },
    {
      "front": "染み",
      "back": "blot; stain"
    },
    {
      "front": "排日",
      "back": "anti-Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "排気ガス",
      "back": "exhaust gas"
    },
    {
      "front": "排他主義",
      "back": "exclusivism"
    },
    {
      "front": "排斥",
      "back": "expulsion; rejection"
    },
    {
      "front": "退廃的",
      "back": "decadent; degenerating"
    },
    {
      "front": "退廃",
      "back": "decadence"
    },
    {
      "front": "自棄",
      "back": "desperation"
    },
    {
      "front": "投じる",
      "back": "send in; throw"
    },
    {
      "front": "人影",
      "back": "human figure"
    },
    {
      "front": "投影",
      "back": "cast shadow; projection"
    },
    {
      "front": "面影",
      "back": "face; traces"
    },
    {
      "front": "交響曲",
      "back": "symphony"
    },
    {
      "front": "音響",
      "back": "sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "響き",
      "back": "sound"
    },
    {
      "front": "ざっと",
      "back": "roughly"
    },
    {
      "front": "境内",
      "back": "grounds"
    },
    {
      "front": "心境",
      "back": "mental attitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "先入観",
      "back": "bias; preconception"
    },
    {
      "front": "楽観的",
      "back": "optimistic"
    },
    {
      "front": "直観",
      "back": "intuition"
    },
    {
      "front": "夜景",
      "back": "night view"
    },
    {
      "front": "月光",
      "back": "moonlight; moonshine"
    },
    {
      "front": "光線",
      "back": "beam; ray"
    },
    {
      "front": "光景",
      "back": "sight; spectacle"
    },
    {
      "front": "手振り",
      "back": "gesture; movement"
    },
    {
      "front": "揺るがす",
      "back": "shake; shock"
    },
    {
      "front": "揺りかご",
      "back": "cradle; swinging cot"
    },
    {
      "front": "神話",
      "back": "myth; mythology"
    },
    {
      "front": "無神経",
      "back": "insensitive"
    },
    {
      "front": "神業",
      "back": "providence"
    },
    {
      "front": "神父",
      "back": "Father; priest"
    },
    {
      "front": "神主",
      "back": "Shinto priest"
    },
    {
      "front": "さらさら",
      "back": "gently; smoothly"
    },
    {
      "front": "秘める",
      "back": "conceal; keep secret"
    },
    {
      "front": "秘訣",
      "back": "key; secret"
    },
    {
      "front": "密入国",
      "back": "illegal entry"
    },
    {
      "front": "密売",
      "back": "smuggling"
    },
    {
      "front": "親密",
      "back": "close; intimate"
    },
    {
      "front": "ダイナマイト",
      "back": "dynamite"
    },
    {
      "front": "精一杯",
      "back": "with all one's might"
    },
    {
      "front": "精通",
      "back": "informed; thorough knowledge of"
    },
    {
      "front": "厳格",
      "back": "stern; strict"
    },
    {
      "front": "親族",
      "back": "relative"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺体",
      "back": "body; remains"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺言",
      "back": "testament; will"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺失物",
      "back": "lost property"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺産",
      "back": "bequest; inheritance"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺憾",
      "back": "regrettable"
    },
    {
      "front": "チャック",
      "back": "fastener; zipper"
    },
    {
      "front": "耳寄り",
      "back": "ear-grabbing; hot"
    },
    {
      "front": "歩み寄る",
      "back": "compromise; step up"
    },
    {
      "front": "近寄せる",
      "back": "bring close to"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄生",
      "back": "parasite"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄せ集め",
      "back": "mixture; odds and ends"
    },
    {
      "front": "ネオン",
      "back": "neon; neon sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "歴然と",
      "back": "clear"
    },
    {
      "front": "職歴",
      "back": "one's professional experience"
    },
    {
      "front": "女王",
      "back": "belle; queen"
    },
    {
      "front": "王女",
      "back": "Royal princess"
    },
    {
      "front": "王子",
      "back": "prince"
    },
    {
      "front": "王国",
      "back": "kingdom; monarchy"
    },
    {
      "front": "王者",
      "back": "king; monarch"
    },
    {
      "front": "婦女",
      "back": "the fair sex; woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "国宝",
      "back": "national treasure"
    },
    {
      "front": "重宝",
      "back": "convenience; handiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "宝",
      "back": "riches; treasure"
    },
    {
      "front": "宝くじ",
      "back": "public lottery"
    },
    {
      "front": "なめる",
      "back": "lap; lick"
    },
    {
      "front": "改築",
      "back": "rebuilding; remodeling"
    },
    {
      "front": "待ち構える",
      "back": "wait eagerly for"
    },
    {
      "front": "方位",
      "back": "bearing; direction"
    },
    {
      "front": "学位",
      "back": "academic degree"
    },
    {
      "front": "置物",
      "back": "ornament"
    },
    {
      "front": "物置",
      "back": "storeroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "わいわい",
      "back": "excitedly; get excited"
    },
    {
      "front": "近距離",
      "back": "short distance"
    },
    {
      "front": "遠距離",
      "back": "long distance"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き離す",
      "back": "draw apart; separate"
    },
    {
      "front": "停学",
      "back": "suspension from school"
    },
    {
      "front": "円周",
      "back": "circumference"
    },
    {
      "front": "海辺",
      "back": "beach; seaside"
    },
    {
      "front": "天辺",
      "back": "summit; top"
    },
    {
      "front": "囲い",
      "back": "enclosure; fence"
    },
    {
      "front": "囲う",
      "back": "enclose; fence"
    },
    {
      "front": "隣人",
      "back": "neighbor"
    },
    {
      "front": "隣家",
      "back": "neighboring house"
    },
    {
      "front": "隣り合わせ",
      "back": "adjoining"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピント",
      "back": "focus"
    },
    {
      "front": "黄昏",
      "back": "dusk"
    },
    {
      "front": "横文字",
      "back": "European language"
    },
    {
      "front": "横道",
      "back": "side street"
    },
    {
      "front": "横取り",
      "back": "interception"
    },
    {
      "front": "横着",
      "back": "idle; impudent"
    },
    {
      "front": "横たわる",
      "back": "lie down"
    },
    {
      "front": "不断",
      "back": "constant"
    },
    {
      "front": "切断",
      "back": "cut; severance"
    },
    {
      "front": "予断",
      "back": "foregone conclusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "断じて",
      "back": "absolutely; decidedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "断つ",
      "back": "cut off; sever"
    },
    {
      "front": "中継ぎ",
      "back": "broadcasting; relay"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き継ぎ",
      "back": "taking over"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き継ぐ",
      "back": "succeed to; take over"
    },
    {
      "front": "継ぎはぎ",
      "back": "patching together"
    },
    {
      "front": "東欧",
      "back": "East Europe"
    },
    {
      "front": "西欧",
      "back": "the West; West Europe"
    },
    {
      "front": "カトリック",
      "back": "Catholic"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄橋",
      "back": "iron bridge"
    },
    {
      "front": "陸橋",
      "back": "overland bridge"
    },
    {
      "front": "見極める",
      "back": "ascertain; see through"
    },
    {
      "front": "極限",
      "back": "limit; utmost limits"
    },
    {
      "front": "極秘",
      "back": "strict secrecy"
    },
    {
      "front": "極",
      "back": "extremely; very"
    },
    {
      "front": "道端",
      "back": "roadside; wayside"
    },
    {
      "front": "末端",
      "back": "end; tip"
    },
    {
      "front": "発端",
      "back": "beginning; origin"
    },
    {
      "front": "端的",
      "back": "directly"
    },
    {
      "front": "異端",
      "back": "heresy; paganism"
    },
    {
      "front": "端たない",
      "back": "shameful; vulgar"
    },
    {
      "front": "房",
      "back": "cluster; tuft"
    },
    {
      "front": "情緒",
      "back": "emotion; feeling"
    },
    {
      "front": "由緒",
      "back": "history; lineage"
    },
    {
      "front": "貨車",
      "back": "freight car"
    },
    {
      "front": "通貨",
      "back": "currency"
    },
    {
      "front": "あたかも",
      "back": "as if; like"
    },
    {
      "front": "安易",
      "back": "easy; easygoing"
    },
    {
      "front": "難易",
      "back": "difficulty; hardness"
    },
    {
      "front": "密輸",
      "back": "smuggling"
    },
    {
      "front": "輪",
      "back": "ring; wheel"
    },
    {
      "front": "輪ゴム",
      "back": "rubber band"
    },
    {
      "front": "輪郭",
      "back": "contour; outline"
    },
    {
      "front": "復帰",
      "back": "restoration; return"
    },
    {
      "front": "復讐",
      "back": "revenge; vengeance"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ繰り返る",
      "back": "be reversed; capsize; fall over"
    },
    {
      "front": "やり繰り",
      "back": "juggling"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビスケット",
      "back": "biscuit; cookie"
    },
    {
      "front": "渋る",
      "back": "be unwilling; falter"
    },
    {
      "front": "大前提",
      "back": "major premise"
    },
    {
      "front": "携える",
      "back": "carry in one's hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "留年",
      "back": "repetition of a year"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌留多",
      "back": "Japanese playing cards"
    },
    {
      "front": "在留",
      "back": "residence; stay"
    },
    {
      "front": "保留",
      "back": "reservation"
    },
    {
      "front": "留まる",
      "back": "remain; stay behind"
    },
    {
      "front": "自衛",
      "back": "self-defense"
    },
    {
      "front": "厳守",
      "back": "strict observance"
    },
    {
      "front": "お守り",
      "back": "good-luck charm"
    },
    {
      "front": "発起人",
      "back": "originator; proposer"
    },
    {
      "front": "起立",
      "back": "rising; standing up"
    },
    {
      "front": "提起",
      "back": "raising"
    },
    {
      "front": "しょんぼり",
      "back": "crestfallen; depressed"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝言",
      "back": "talking in one's sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝台",
      "back": "bed; sleeping berth"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝返り",
      "back": "turning over in bed"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝返る",
      "back": "betray; go over to the enemy"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝息",
      "back": "breathing of a sleeping person"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝相",
      "back": "one's sleeping posture"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝顔",
      "back": "one's sleeping face"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝冷え",
      "back": "cold caught while sleeping"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝ぼける",
      "back": "be half asleep; be half awake"
    },
    {
      "front": "動静",
      "back": "movements; state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "front": "静寂",
      "back": "quietness; silence"
    },
    {
      "front": "静粛",
      "back": "quiet; silent"
    },
    {
      "front": "ブランコ",
      "back": "swing"
    },
    {
      "front": "趣き",
      "back": "distinctive charm; elegance"
    },
    {
      "front": "車両",
      "back": "rolling stock; vehicle"
    },
    {
      "front": "両端",
      "back": "both ends"
    },
    {
      "front": "破片",
      "back": "broken piece; fragment"
    },
    {
      "front": "断片",
      "back": "fragment; piece"
    },
    {
      "front": "裏通り",
      "back": "back street"
    },
    {
      "front": "表裏",
      "back": "duplicity; front and rear"
    },
    {
      "front": "消印",
      "back": "postmark"
    },
    {
      "front": "印紙",
      "back": "stamp"
    },
    {
      "front": "認め印",
      "back": "informal seal"
    },
    {
      "front": "調印",
      "back": "signature; signing"
    },
    {
      "front": "刷る",
      "back": "print; put in print"
    },
    {
      "front": "日刊",
      "back": "published daily"
    },
    {
      "front": "新刊",
      "back": "new publication"
    },
    {
      "front": "ビラ",
      "back": "leaflet"
    },
    {
      "front": "明細",
      "back": "details; particulars"
    },
    {
      "front": "細やか",
      "back": "modest"
    },
    {
      "front": "体積",
      "back": "capacity; volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "山積",
      "back": "pile"
    },
    {
      "front": "積雪",
      "back": "snow"
    },
    {
      "front": "見積もり",
      "back": "assessment; estimate"
    },
    {
      "front": "積み立て",
      "back": "laying by; reserving"
    },
    {
      "front": "堆積",
      "back": "accumulation; pile"
    },
    {
      "front": "きらい",
      "back": "tendency; trend"
    },
    {
      "front": "翻す",
      "back": "change; flutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "誤字",
      "back": "wrong character"
    },
    {
      "front": "討つ",
      "back": "attack the enemy; kill"
    },
    {
      "front": "添加",
      "back": "addition; additive"
    },
    {
      "front": "添削",
      "back": "correction"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い付ける",
      "back": "order; tell"
    },
    {
      "front": "決め付ける",
      "back": "decide; fix upon"
    },
    {
      "front": "送付",
      "back": "remittance; sending"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き付ける",
      "back": "attract"
    },
    {
      "front": "引っ付く",
      "back": "cling; stick"
    },
    {
      "front": "押し付ける",
      "back": "compel; press against"
    },
    {
      "front": "付け込む",
      "back": "take advantage of"
    },
    {
      "front": "付着",
      "back": "adhesion; cohesion"
    },
    {
      "front": "付加",
      "back": "addition; supplement"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄付",
      "back": "contribution; donation"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝付き",
      "back": "falling asleep; going to sleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝付く",
      "back": "fall asleep"
    },
    {
      "front": "添付",
      "back": "appendix; attached item"
    },
    {
      "front": "付け",
      "back": "account; bill"
    },
    {
      "front": "くるり",
      "back": "curl"
    },
    {
      "front": "ゆらゆら",
      "back": "rock"
    },
    {
      "front": "配属",
      "back": "assignment"
    },
    {
      "front": "従属",
      "back": "subordination"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐったり",
      "back": "run-down; wearily"
    },
    {
      "front": "策略",
      "back": "artifice; stratagem"
    },
    {
      "front": "概論",
      "back": "outline"
    },
    {
      "front": "入念",
      "back": "carefully"
    },
    {
      "front": "念入り",
      "back": "careful; elaborate"
    },
    {
      "front": "念力",
      "back": "psycho-kinesis; will power"
    },
    {
      "front": "理念",
      "back": "concept; idea"
    },
    {
      "front": "専念",
      "back": "concentration"
    },
    {
      "front": "念願",
      "back": "one's heart's desire"
    },
    {
      "front": "念頭",
      "back": "mind; thoughts"
    },
    {
      "front": "観念",
      "back": "concept; idea"
    },
    {
      "front": "断念",
      "back": "abandonment"
    },
    {
      "front": "アスファルト",
      "back": "asphalt"
    },
    {
      "front": "順路",
      "back": "fixed route"
    },
    {
      "front": "序でに",
      "back": "on the way"
    },
    {
      "front": "時効",
      "back": "prescription"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆上せる",
      "back": "get dizzy; go mad over"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆効果",
      "back": "counter result"
    },
    {
      "front": "反逆",
      "back": "rebellion; revolt"
    },
    {
      "front": "逆境",
      "back": "adversity"
    },
    {
      "front": "スリル",
      "back": "thrill"
    },
    {
      "front": "直列",
      "back": "series"
    },
    {
      "front": "同列",
      "back": "same rank"
    },
    {
      "front": "先例",
      "back": "precedent"
    },
    {
      "front": "条例",
      "back": "regulations; rules"
    },
    {
      "front": "判例",
      "back": "precedent"
    },
    {
      "front": "カーネーション",
      "back": "carnation"
    },
    {
      "front": "余談",
      "back": "digression"
    },
    {
      "front": "余す",
      "back": "leave over; let remain"
    },
    {
      "front": "暇潰し",
      "back": "kill time"
    },
    {
      "front": "途切れる",
      "back": "break; pause"
    },
    {
      "front": "てくてく",
      "back": "steadily"
    },
    {
      "front": "席上",
      "back": "at the meeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "即座",
      "back": "immediately"
    },
    {
      "front": "即席",
      "back": "impromptu; improvised"
    },
    {
      "front": "即死",
      "back": "instant death"
    },
    {
      "front": "刻一刻と",
      "back": "moment by moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "彫刻",
      "back": "carving; sculpture"
    },
    {
      "front": "取締役",
      "back": "director"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き締め",
      "back": "tightening"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き締める",
      "back": "brace oneself; tighten"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き締まる",
      "back": "be braced up; tighten"
    },
    {
      "front": "どしどし",
      "back": "constantly; without hesitation"
    },
    {
      "front": "見栄",
      "back": "vanity"
    },
    {
      "front": "栄光",
      "back": "glory"
    },
    {
      "front": "養子",
      "back": "foster child"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦味",
      "back": "bitter taste"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦悩",
      "back": "distress; suffering"
    },
    {
      "front": "貧富",
      "back": "rich and poor"
    },
    {
      "front": "うんと",
      "back": "hard; with effort"
    },
    {
      "front": "辛口",
      "back": "spiciness"
    },
    {
      "front": "辛子",
      "back": "mustard"
    },
    {
      "front": "唐辛子",
      "back": "red pepper"
    },
    {
      "front": "農協",
      "back": "agricultural cooperative"
    },
    {
      "front": "農林",
      "back": "agriculture and forestry"
    },
    {
      "front": "めっきり",
      "back": "remarkably"
    },
    {
      "front": "漁",
      "back": "fishery; fishing"
    },
    {
      "front": "漁る",
      "back": "fish; hunt; search"
    },
    {
      "front": "漁師",
      "back": "fisherman"
    },
    {
      "front": "軽薄",
      "back": "frivolous; insincere"
    },
    {
      "front": "薄まる",
      "back": "be diluted; thin out"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚生",
      "back": "public welfare"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚意",
      "back": "favor; kindness"
    },
    {
      "front": "濃厚",
      "back": "dense; rich; thick"
    },
    {
      "front": "厚かましい",
      "back": "brazen; unabashed"
    },
    {
      "front": "ばったり",
      "back": "unexpectedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "電圧",
      "back": "voltage"
    },
    {
      "front": "迫力",
      "back": "force; power; punch"
    },
    {
      "front": "緊迫",
      "back": "strain; tension"
    },
    {
      "front": "濃縮",
      "back": "concentration"
    },
    {
      "front": "圧縮",
      "back": "compression"
    },
    {
      "front": "縮れる",
      "back": "be wavy; shrink"
    },
    {
      "front": "差し伸べる",
      "back": "hold out; reach out"
    },
    {
      "front": "伸び",
      "back": "growth; stretching"
    },
    {
      "front": "伸びやか",
      "back": "carefree"
    },
    {
      "front": "伸び伸び",
      "back": "at ease"
    },
    {
      "front": "ころころ",
      "back": "changes frequently; rolls around"
    },
    {
      "front": "倍増",
      "back": "doubling; redoubling"
    },
    {
      "front": "超特急",
      "back": "super express"
    },
    {
      "front": "超越",
      "back": "transcending"
    },
    {
      "front": "間抜け",
      "back": "bonehead; idiot"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き抜く",
      "back": "pull out; recruit"
    },
    {
      "front": "インキ",
      "back": "ink"
    },
    {
      "front": "入札",
      "back": "bid; tender"
    },
    {
      "front": "荷札",
      "back": "tag"
    },
    {
      "front": "立て札",
      "back": "bulletin board"
    },
    {
      "front": "落札",
      "back": "successful bid"
    },
    {
      "front": "礼金",
      "back": "fee; reward"
    },
    {
      "front": "朝礼",
      "back": "morning assembly"
    },
    {
      "front": "礼服",
      "back": "formal dress"
    },
    {
      "front": "礼状",
      "back": "letter of thanks"
    },
    {
      "front": "儀礼",
      "back": "courtesy; etiquette"
    },
    {
      "front": "投射",
      "back": "incidence; projection"
    },
    {
      "front": "反射的",
      "back": "reflective; reflexive"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐるっと",
      "back": "spin; turn round"
    },
    {
      "front": "方程式",
      "back": "equation"
    },
    {
      "front": "工程",
      "back": "process of manufacture"
    },
    {
      "front": "程なく",
      "back": "soon"
    },
    {
      "front": "優等生",
      "back": "honor student"
    },
    {
      "front": "優越感",
      "back": "superiority complex"
    },
    {
      "front": "誘拐",
      "back": "abduction; kidnapping"
    },
    {
      "front": "願望",
      "back": "desire; wish"
    },
    {
      "front": "バザー",
      "back": "bazaar"
    },
    {
      "front": "独学",
      "back": "self-study"
    },
    {
      "front": "独楽",
      "back": "top"
    },
    {
      "front": "独断",
      "back": "dogmatism"
    },
    {
      "front": "独りぼっち",
      "back": "solitary"
    },
    {
      "front": "身分",
      "back": "social position"
    },
    {
      "front": "上半身",
      "back": "upper part of the body"
    },
    {
      "front": "身の上",
      "back": "one's career; one's condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "下半身",
      "back": "lower half of one's body"
    },
    {
      "front": "身内",
      "back": "relations; relative"
    },
    {
      "front": "身体",
      "back": "body"
    },
    {
      "front": "身元",
      "back": "one's birth; one's identity"
    },
    {
      "front": "半身",
      "back": "half the body"
    },
    {
      "front": "身軽",
      "back": "agile; light"
    },
    {
      "front": "身投げ",
      "back": "suicide by drowning or jumping"
    },
    {
      "front": "変身",
      "back": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "front": "身寄り",
      "back": "relation; relative"
    },
    {
      "front": "こつ",
      "back": "art; knack; the hang"
    },
    {
      "front": "買い占める",
      "back": "buy up"
    },
    {
      "front": "独り占め",
      "back": "exclusive possession"
    },
    {
      "front": "占い",
      "back": "divination; fortunetelling"
    },
    {
      "front": "占う",
      "back": "divine; tell fortune"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぼろぼろ",
      "back": "old and scruffy"
    },
    {
      "front": "目処",
      "back": "goal; prospects"
    },
    {
      "front": "処女",
      "back": "first; virgin"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲買",
      "back": "brokerage; middleman"
    },
    {
      "front": "お節介",
      "back": "meddlesome"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲介",
      "back": "agent; mediation"
    },
    {
      "front": "厄介",
      "back": "annoyance; trouble"
    },
    {
      "front": "サイレン",
      "back": "siren"
    },
    {
      "front": "照会",
      "back": "application for information"
    },
    {
      "front": "対照",
      "back": "contrast"
    },
    {
      "front": "照れる",
      "back": "be abashed; feel shy"
    },
    {
      "front": "妻子",
      "back": "one's wife and children"
    },
    {
      "front": "稲妻",
      "back": "lightning"
    },
    {
      "front": "互い違い",
      "back": "alternate"
    },
    {
      "front": "互いに",
      "back": "mutually; reciprocally"
    },
    {
      "front": "デマ",
      "back": "lie; rumor"
    },
    {
      "front": "入籍",
      "back": "entry in the family register"
    },
    {
      "front": "書籍",
      "back": "books; publications"
    },
    {
      "front": "在籍",
      "back": "registration"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛読",
      "back": "love reading"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛用",
      "back": "use regularly"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛着",
      "back": "attachment"
    },
    {
      "front": "親愛",
      "back": "affection; love"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛想",
      "back": "civility; hospitality"
    },
    {
      "front": "愛しい",
      "back": "beloved; darling"
    },
    {
      "front": "恋しい",
      "back": "beloved; dear"
    },
    {
      "front": "延滞",
      "back": "arrears"
    },
    {
      "front": "蔓延る",
      "back": "grow thick"
    },
    {
      "front": "うねり",
      "back": "the swell; undulation"
    },
    {
      "front": "祝電",
      "back": "congratulatory telegram"
    },
    {
      "front": "祝福",
      "back": "blessing"
    },
    {
      "front": "裕福",
      "back": "rich; wealthy"
    },
    {
      "front": "純情",
      "back": "pure heart"
    },
    {
      "front": "不純",
      "back": "impure; mixed"
    },
    {
      "front": "抜粋",
      "back": "excerpt; extract"
    },
    {
      "front": "初夢",
      "back": "first dream of the New Year"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪夢",
      "back": "bad dream; nightmare"
    },
    {
      "front": "夢想",
      "back": "daydream; dream"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐるり",
      "back": "all the way round"
    },
    {
      "front": "試行錯誤",
      "back": "trial and error"
    },
    {
      "front": "謹慎",
      "back": "penitence; restraint"
    },
    {
      "front": "作り笑い",
      "back": "forced laugh"
    },
    {
      "front": "苦笑い",
      "back": "bitter smile"
    },
    {
      "front": "無恥",
      "back": "impudence; shamelessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "恥知らず",
      "back": "brazen; shameless person"
    },
    {
      "front": "恥さらし",
      "back": "disgrace; shame"
    },
    {
      "front": "花弁",
      "back": "petal"
    },
    {
      "front": "弁明",
      "back": "explanation"
    },
    {
      "front": "駅弁",
      "back": "station lunch"
    },
    {
      "front": "弁済",
      "back": "payment; repayment"
    },
    {
      "front": "答弁",
      "back": "defense of oneself; reply"
    },
    {
      "front": "弁える",
      "back": "distinguish; tell"
    },
    {
      "front": "擁護",
      "back": "defense; protection"
    },
    {
      "front": "とろとろ",
      "back": "gently; simmering"
    },
    {
      "front": "好転",
      "back": "a turn for the better"
    },
    {
      "front": "代議士",
      "back": "member of the Diet"
    },
    {
      "front": "運転士",
      "back": "driver"
    },
    {
      "front": "患う",
      "back": "fall ill"
    },
    {
      "front": "安否",
      "back": "safety; welfare"
    },
    {
      "front": "賛否",
      "back": "approval or disapproval"
    },
    {
      "front": "否認",
      "back": "denial; negation"
    },
    {
      "front": "裁決",
      "back": "decision; ruling"
    },
    {
      "front": "洋裁",
      "back": "western-style dressmaking"
    },
    {
      "front": "仲裁",
      "back": "arbitration; mediation"
    },
    {
      "front": "裁つ",
      "back": "cut out"
    },
    {
      "front": "裁縫",
      "back": "needlework; sewing"
    },
    {
      "front": "シャンソン",
      "back": "chanson; French music"
    },
    {
      "front": "告訴",
      "back": "legal action"
    },
    {
      "front": "起訴",
      "back": "prosecution"
    },
    {
      "front": "控訴",
      "back": "appeal"
    },
    {
      "front": "迷路",
      "back": "labyrinth; maze"
    },
    {
      "front": "混迷",
      "back": "confusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "みっともない",
      "back": "disgraceful; shameful; unseemly"
    },
    {
      "front": "当惑",
      "back": "confusion; perplexity"
    },
    {
      "front": "困惑",
      "back": "embarrassment"
    },
    {
      "front": "惑わす",
      "back": "fascinate; mislead"
    },
    {
      "front": "魅惑",
      "back": "enchantment; fascination"
    },
    {
      "front": "謎々",
      "back": "puzzle; riddle"
    },
    {
      "front": "名著",
      "back": "famous book; masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "front": "有権者",
      "back": "elector"
    },
    {
      "front": "参政権",
      "back": "suffrage"
    },
    {
      "front": "がんがん",
      "back": "throbbing and aching"
    },
    {
      "front": "侵入",
      "back": "invasion; raid"
    },
    {
      "front": "真偽",
      "back": "authenticity; truth or falsehood"
    },
    {
      "front": "偽",
      "back": "imitation; sham"
    },
    {
      "front": "日替わり",
      "back": "changing on a daily basis"
    },
    {
      "front": "為替",
      "back": "exchange; money order"
    },
    {
      "front": "為す",
      "back": "do; perform"
    },
    {
      "front": "ピリオド",
      "back": "final end; period"
    },
    {
      "front": "代償",
      "back": "compensation"
    },
    {
      "front": "償う",
      "back": "make up for; recompense"
    },
    {
      "front": "賞金",
      "back": "award; prize"
    },
    {
      "front": "賞状",
      "back": "certificate of merit; commendation"
    },
    {
      "front": "寄贈",
      "back": "donation; presentation"
    },
    {
      "front": "給与",
      "back": "allowance; pay"
    },
    {
      "front": "贈与",
      "back": "donation; presentation"
    },
    {
      "front": "こつこつ",
      "back": "steadily"
    },
    {
      "front": "財界",
      "back": "business world"
    },
    {
      "front": "財閥",
      "back": "conglomerate"
    },
    {
      "front": "隔てる",
      "back": "partition; separate"
    },
    {
      "front": "承る",
      "back": "listen to; take"
    },
    {
      "front": "出納",
      "back": "receipts and expenses"
    },
    {
      "front": "未納",
      "back": "in arrears; unpaid"
    },
    {
      "front": "納税",
      "back": "tax payment"
    },
    {
      "front": "どっしり",
      "back": "dignified; massive"
    },
    {
      "front": "収拾",
      "back": "control"
    },
    {
      "front": "体得",
      "back": "acquisition; learning"
    },
    {
      "front": "心得る",
      "back": "know; understand"
    },
    {
      "front": "習得",
      "back": "acquisition; learning"
    },
    {
      "front": "拾得",
      "back": "find"
    },
    {
      "front": "得る",
      "back": "can; get"
    },
    {
      "front": "見損なう",
      "back": "fail to see; misjudge"
    },
    {
      "front": "損益",
      "back": "profit and loss"
    },
    {
      "front": "損得",
      "back": "advantage and disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "front": "損ねる",
      "back": "offend; ruin"
    },
    {
      "front": "やくざ",
      "back": "gangster; yakuza"
    },
    {
      "front": "燃費",
      "back": "mileage; petrol consumption"
    },
    {
      "front": "可燃物",
      "back": "combustibles; flammable materials"
    },
    {
      "front": "不燃物",
      "back": "incombustibles"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼きもち",
      "back": "jealousy"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼酎",
      "back": "Japanese liquor; shochu"
    },
    {
      "front": "とかく",
      "back": "often"
    },
    {
      "front": "燥ぐ",
      "back": "frolic"
    },
    {
      "front": "季語",
      "back": "season word"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾電池",
      "back": "battery"
    },
    {
      "front": "乾季",
      "back": "dry season"
    },
    {
      "front": "酸性",
      "back": "acidity"
    },
    {
      "front": "素人",
      "back": "amateur; decent woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "素質",
      "back": "makings; nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "要素",
      "back": "constituent; element"
    },
    {
      "front": "素顔",
      "back": "face without makeup"
    },
    {
      "front": "炭酸",
      "back": "carbonic acid; soda"
    },
    {
      "front": "炭",
      "back": "charcoal"
    },
    {
      "front": "彼方",
      "back": "other side; there"
    },
    {
      "front": "彼岸",
      "back": "equinox"
    },
    {
      "front": "岸辺",
      "back": "bank; shore"
    },
    {
      "front": "中庭",
      "back": "courtyard"
    },
    {
      "front": "庭園",
      "back": "garden; park"
    },
    {
      "front": "びっしり",
      "back": "full; tightly"
    },
    {
      "front": "吹き出す",
      "back": "blast out; blow out"
    },
    {
      "front": "吹雪",
      "back": "snowstorm"
    },
    {
      "front": "吹き込む",
      "back": "blow into; breathe into"
    },
    {
      "front": "発散",
      "back": "emission; radiation"
    },
    {
      "front": "散々",
      "back": "severely; thoroughly"
    },
    {
      "front": "散らし",
      "back": "handbill; leaflet"
    },
    {
      "front": "散らす",
      "back": "scatter"
    },
    {
      "front": "根っ子",
      "back": "root; stump"
    },
    {
      "front": "根元",
      "back": "base; root"
    },
    {
      "front": "根性",
      "back": "nature"
    },
    {
      "front": "垣根",
      "back": "fence; hedge"
    },
    {
      "front": "みっちり",
      "back": "fully; hard"
    },
    {
      "front": "草食",
      "back": "herbivore"
    },
    {
      "front": "道草",
      "back": "dawdle; loiter"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑草",
      "back": "weed"
    },
    {
      "front": "草原",
      "back": "grassland; prairie"
    },
    {
      "front": "草履",
      "back": "Japanese sandals; zori"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼び名",
      "back": "given name"
    },
    {
      "front": "呼び捨て",
      "back": "address informally"
    },
    {
      "front": "及ぼす",
      "back": "cause; exert"
    },
    {
      "front": "オートメーション",
      "back": "automation"
    },
    {
      "front": "貧血",
      "back": "anemia"
    },
    {
      "front": "血圧",
      "back": "blood pressure"
    },
    {
      "front": "溶け込む",
      "back": "fuse into; melt into"
    },
    {
      "front": "溶く",
      "back": "dissolve; melt"
    },
    {
      "front": "変容",
      "back": "transfiguration"
    },
    {
      "front": "容疑者",
      "back": "suspect"
    },
    {
      "front": "容態",
      "back": "one's condition"
    },
    {
      "front": "容積",
      "back": "capacity; volume"
    },
    {
      "front": "容赦",
      "back": "forgiveness; pardon"
    },
    {
      "front": "おんぶ",
      "back": "piggy back"
    },
    {
      "front": "背負う",
      "back": "carry on one's back; shoulder"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄骨",
      "back": "steel frame"
    },
    {
      "front": "背骨",
      "back": "backbone; spine"
    },
    {
      "front": "拳骨",
      "back": "fist"
    },
    {
      "front": "滑走路",
      "back": "runway"
    },
    {
      "front": "イデオロギー",
      "back": "ideology"
    },
    {
      "front": "折り返し",
      "back": "lapel; turning point"
    },
    {
      "front": "折紙",
      "back": "origami; paper for folding"
    },
    {
      "front": "折",
      "back": "at the time; occasion"
    },
    {
      "front": "折り畳み",
      "back": "collapsible"
    },
    {
      "front": "健気",
      "back": "brave; praiseworthy"
    },
    {
      "front": "どっさり",
      "back": "loads"
    },
    {
      "front": "診療所",
      "back": "clinic"
    },
    {
      "front": "療養",
      "back": "recuperation"
    },
    {
      "front": "食中毒",
      "back": "food poisoning"
    },
    {
      "front": "毒薬",
      "back": "poisonous drug"
    },
    {
      "front": "菌",
      "back": "bacteria; germ"
    },
    {
      "front": "清い",
      "back": "clean; honest"
    },
    {
      "front": "清掃",
      "back": "cleaning"
    },
    {
      "front": "マンホール",
      "back": "manhole"
    },
    {
      "front": "潔白",
      "back": "innocent; pure"
    },
    {
      "front": "潔く",
      "back": "bravely"
    },
    {
      "front": "潔い",
      "back": "gallant; manly"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛び切り",
      "back": "by far; exceptionally"
    },
    {
      "front": "飛躍",
      "back": "jump; leap"
    },
    {
      "front": "跳躍",
      "back": "jump; leap"
    },
    {
      "front": "再三",
      "back": "again and again"
    },
    {
      "front": "再度",
      "back": "a second time"
    },
    {
      "front": "再起",
      "back": "comeback; recovery"
    },
    {
      "front": "ノイローゼ",
      "back": "nervous breakdown; neurosis"
    },
    {
      "front": "編入",
      "back": "admission; inclusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "編み物",
      "back": "knitting"
    },
    {
      "front": "編成",
      "back": "organization"
    },
    {
      "front": "放火",
      "back": "arson; setting alight"
    },
    {
      "front": "見放す",
      "back": "abandon; desert"
    },
    {
      "front": "放任",
      "back": "leave to one's own devices"
    },
    {
      "front": "放つ",
      "back": "emit; set free"
    },
    {
      "front": "放れる",
      "back": "get free"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひしひしと",
      "back": "acutely; severely"
    },
    {
      "front": "警報",
      "back": "alarm; warning signal"
    },
    {
      "front": "監禁",
      "back": "confinement"
    },
    {
      "front": "視力",
      "back": "eyesight"
    },
    {
      "front": "軽視",
      "back": "neglect"
    },
    {
      "front": "直視",
      "back": "direct look"
    },
    {
      "front": "巨視的",
      "back": "macroscopic"
    },
    {
      "front": "警視庁",
      "back": "Metropolitan Police Office"
    },
    {
      "front": "白衣",
      "back": "white coat; white robe"
    },
    {
      "front": "更衣室",
      "back": "changing room"
    },
    {
      "front": "脱衣",
      "back": "undressing"
    },
    {
      "front": "アリバイ",
      "back": "alibi"
    },
    {
      "front": "正装",
      "back": "formal dress; full uniform"
    },
    {
      "front": "装う",
      "back": "dress oneself; make up"
    },
    {
      "front": "法令",
      "back": "laws and ordinances"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮面",
      "back": "disguise; mask"
    },
    {
      "front": "仮説",
      "back": "hypothesis"
    },
    {
      "front": "演技",
      "back": "acting; performance"
    },
    {
      "front": "悲観的",
      "back": "pessimistic"
    },
    {
      "front": "固形",
      "back": "solid"
    },
    {
      "front": "固苦しい",
      "back": "formal; strict"
    },
    {
      "front": "美女",
      "back": "beautiful woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "美化",
      "back": "beautification"
    },
    {
      "front": "美容",
      "back": "beauty"
    },
    {
      "front": "おでこ",
      "back": "forehead"
    },
    {
      "front": "博学",
      "back": "erudition"
    },
    {
      "front": "博愛",
      "back": "philanthropy"
    },
    {
      "front": "促成",
      "back": "promotion of growth"
    },
    {
      "front": "督促",
      "back": "reminder; urging"
    },
    {
      "front": "プロテスタント",
      "back": "Protestant"
    },
    {
      "front": "望遠鏡",
      "back": "telescope"
    },
    {
      "front": "顕微鏡",
      "back": "microscope"
    },
    {
      "front": "奇妙",
      "back": "queer; strange"
    },
    {
      "front": "妙",
      "back": "strangeness"
    },
    {
      "front": "怪奇",
      "back": "mystery; wonder"
    },
    {
      "front": "あながち",
      "back": "not necessarily"
    },
    {
      "front": "特訓",
      "back": "crash course; special training"
    },
    {
      "front": "講和",
      "back": "peace; reconciliation"
    },
    {
      "front": "助教授",
      "back": "assistant professor"
    },
    {
      "front": "お手伝いさん",
      "back": "house maid; maid"
    },
    {
      "front": "遺伝",
      "back": "inheritance"
    },
    {
      "front": "伝う",
      "back": "follow; go along"
    },
    {
      "front": "つやつや",
      "back": "glossy"
    },
    {
      "front": "名声",
      "back": "fame; reputation"
    },
    {
      "front": "発声",
      "back": "vocalization"
    },
    {
      "front": "音声",
      "back": "sound; voice"
    },
    {
      "front": "競う",
      "back": "compete with; contend"
    },
    {
      "front": "競馬",
      "back": "horse racing"
    },
    {
      "front": "大騒ぎ",
      "back": "racket; uproar"
    },
    {
      "front": "物騒",
      "back": "dangerous; insecure"
    },
    {
      "front": "騒めく",
      "back": "be noisy"
    },
    {
      "front": "お神興",
      "back": "portable shrine"
    },
    {
      "front": "興す",
      "back": "cause to rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずらす",
      "back": "shift"
    },
    {
      "front": "奮発",
      "back": "effort; treat"
    },
    {
      "front": "奮う",
      "back": "rouse up"
    },
    {
      "front": "夏至",
      "back": "summer solstice"
    },
    {
      "front": "冬至",
      "back": "winter solstice"
    },
    {
      "front": "到来",
      "back": "advent; arrival"
    },
    {
      "front": "殺到",
      "back": "rush"
    },
    {
      "front": "倒置",
      "back": "inversion"
    },
    {
      "front": "圧倒",
      "back": "overpower; overwhelm"
    },
    {
      "front": "けじめ",
      "back": "distinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "傾げる",
      "back": "incline; lean"
    },
    {
      "front": "硬化",
      "back": "hardness; stiffness"
    },
    {
      "front": "硬貨",
      "back": "coin"
    },
    {
      "front": "膨大",
      "back": "expansion; swelling"
    },
    {
      "front": "張本人",
      "back": "author; originator"
    },
    {
      "front": "張り出す",
      "back": "jut out; project"
    },
    {
      "front": "見張る",
      "back": "guard; watch"
    },
    {
      "front": "強張る",
      "back": "become stiff; stiffen"
    },
    {
      "front": "膨張",
      "back": "expansion; growth"
    },
    {
      "front": "縄張り",
      "back": "one's territory"
    },
    {
      "front": "それとなく",
      "back": "indirectly"
    },
    {
      "front": "風刺",
      "back": "sarcasm; satire"
    },
    {
      "front": "突き抜ける",
      "back": "go through; penetrate"
    },
    {
      "front": "突き刺す",
      "back": "pierce; stab"
    },
    {
      "front": "楯突く",
      "back": "defy; rebel"
    },
    {
      "front": "前触れ",
      "back": "previous notice; sign"
    },
    {
      "front": "触れ合い",
      "back": "contact; touch"
    },
    {
      "front": "触れ合う",
      "back": "come in contact"
    },
    {
      "front": "顔触れ",
      "back": "personnel"
    },
    {
      "front": "タンカー",
      "back": "tanker"
    },
    {
      "front": "避暑",
      "back": "summering"
    },
    {
      "front": "不可避",
      "back": "inevitable"
    },
    {
      "front": "退避",
      "back": "evacuation; refuge"
    },
    {
      "front": "逃避",
      "back": "escape; evasion"
    },
    {
      "front": "避妊",
      "back": "contraception"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍人",
      "back": "military man; soldier"
    },
    {
      "front": "空軍",
      "back": "air force"
    },
    {
      "front": "海軍",
      "back": "navy"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍国主義",
      "back": "militarism"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍拡",
      "back": "expansion of armaments"
    },
    {
      "front": "将軍",
      "back": "general; shogun"
    },
    {
      "front": "陸軍",
      "back": "army"
    },
    {
      "front": "軍縮",
      "back": "reduction of armaments"
    },
    {
      "front": "将棋",
      "back": "Japanese chess; shogi"
    },
    {
      "front": "こそこそ",
      "back": "secretly; sneak"
    },
    {
      "front": "兵役",
      "back": "military service"
    },
    {
      "front": "徴兵",
      "back": "conscription"
    },
    {
      "front": "中核",
      "back": "core; kernel"
    },
    {
      "front": "核心",
      "back": "core; heart"
    },
    {
      "front": "核兵器",
      "back": "nuclear weapons"
    },
    {
      "front": "おなら",
      "back": "fart"
    },
    {
      "front": "銃",
      "back": "gun; rifle"
    },
    {
      "front": "弾圧",
      "back": "oppression"
    },
    {
      "front": "丸め込む",
      "back": "cajole; coax"
    },
    {
      "front": "丸み",
      "back": "roundness"
    },
    {
      "front": "衝動",
      "back": "impulse; urge"
    },
    {
      "front": "目撃",
      "back": "observation"
    },
    {
      "front": "直撃",
      "back": "direct hit"
    },
    {
      "front": "どたばた",
      "back": "noise; thumping"
    },
    {
      "front": "水爆",
      "back": "hydrogen bomb"
    },
    {
      "front": "爆撃",
      "back": "bombardment; bombing"
    },
    {
      "front": "暴風雨",
      "back": "rainstorm; tempest"
    },
    {
      "front": "中絶",
      "back": "abortion; interruption"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶好",
      "back": "best; splendid"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶え間なく",
      "back": "continually; unceasingly"
    },
    {
      "front": "絶交",
      "back": "breaking off friendship"
    },
    {
      "front": "廃絶",
      "back": "extinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "断絶",
      "back": "severance"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎこちない",
      "back": "awkward; clumsy"
    },
    {
      "front": "滅多",
      "back": "reckless; seldom"
    },
    {
      "front": "消滅",
      "back": "disappearance; extinction"
    },
    {
      "front": "点滅",
      "back": "flashing; flickering"
    },
    {
      "front": "自滅",
      "back": "self-destruction"
    },
    {
      "front": "破滅",
      "back": "destruction; ruin"
    },
    {
      "front": "防水",
      "back": "waterproof"
    },
    {
      "front": "防御",
      "back": "defense; protection"
    },
    {
      "front": "防音",
      "back": "soundproof"
    },
    {
      "front": "防災",
      "back": "disaster prevention"
    },
    {
      "front": "防戦",
      "back": "defensive battle"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちらりと",
      "back": "glance"
    },
    {
      "front": "妨げる",
      "back": "disturb; hinder"
    },
    {
      "front": "海底",
      "back": "sea bottom"
    },
    {
      "front": "徹底",
      "back": "thoroughness"
    },
    {
      "front": "反抗",
      "back": "opposition; resistance"
    },
    {
      "front": "そわそわ",
      "back": "restlessly; uneasily"
    },
    {
      "front": "敵対",
      "back": "antagonism; hostility"
    },
    {
      "front": "脅かす",
      "back": "endanger; threaten"
    },
    {
      "front": "大勢",
      "back": "general trend"
    },
    {
      "front": "威勢",
      "back": "dash; power"
    },
    {
      "front": "威嚇",
      "back": "intimidation; threat"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐縮",
      "back": "feel obliged; grateful"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐る恐る",
      "back": "cautiously; fearfully"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐怖",
      "back": "fear"
    },
    {
      "front": "恐慌",
      "back": "panic; scare"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぷんぷん",
      "back": "be in a huff; fume"
    },
    {
      "front": "拒む",
      "back": "decline; refuse"
    },
    {
      "front": "綿",
      "back": "cotton plant; cotton wool"
    },
    {
      "front": "無縁",
      "back": "unrelated"
    },
    {
      "front": "縁起",
      "back": "luck; omen"
    },
    {
      "front": "血縁",
      "back": "blood relation"
    },
    {
      "front": "縁",
      "back": "edge; frame; hem"
    },
    {
      "front": "縁",
      "back": "chance; fate"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちらちら",
      "back": "fluttering"
    },
    {
      "front": "繊細",
      "back": "delicate; fine"
    },
    {
      "front": "維新",
      "back": "restoration"
    },
    {
      "front": "忍ぶ",
      "back": "bear; perform by stealth"
    },
    {
      "front": "忍耐",
      "back": "patience; perseverance"
    },
    {
      "front": "爪先",
      "back": "tip of a toe; toe"
    },
    {
      "front": "爪楊枝",
      "back": "toothpick"
    },
    {
      "front": "すいすい",
      "back": "smoothly"
    },
    {
      "front": "桁",
      "back": "beam; column"
    },
    {
      "front": "手柄",
      "back": "great deed"
    },
    {
      "front": "家柄",
      "back": "lineage; social standing of a family"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り柄",
      "back": "merit; worth"
    },
    {
      "front": "身柄",
      "back": "one's person"
    },
    {
      "front": "枯れ木",
      "back": "dead tree"
    },
    {
      "front": "枯れ葉",
      "back": "dead leaf"
    },
    {
      "front": "無謀",
      "back": "recklessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "謀る",
      "back": "scheme"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぽっかり",
      "back": "gaping"
    },
    {
      "front": "歌謡曲",
      "back": "popular song"
    },
    {
      "front": "民謡",
      "back": "folk song"
    },
    {
      "front": "誇り",
      "back": "pride"
    },
    {
      "front": "瓶詰め",
      "back": "bottling"
    },
    {
      "front": "誠意",
      "back": "good faith; sincerity"
    },
    {
      "front": "いそいそ",
      "back": "cheerfully"
    },
    {
      "front": "大盛り",
      "back": "large helping"
    },
    {
      "front": "目盛り",
      "back": "division; scale"
    },
    {
      "front": "盛り",
      "back": "heat; height; prime"
    },
    {
      "front": "待ち兼ねる",
      "back": "wait impatiently"
    },
    {
      "front": "鈍間",
      "back": "dull fellow"
    },
    {
      "front": "どろどろ",
      "back": "muddy; syrupy"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉱物",
      "back": "mineral"
    },
    {
      "front": "鎖国",
      "back": "national isolation"
    },
    {
      "front": "風鈴",
      "back": "wind chimes"
    },
    {
      "front": "鈴",
      "back": "bell"
    },
    {
      "front": "破綻",
      "back": "bankruptcy; failure"
    },
    {
      "front": "ねだる",
      "back": "coax; nag; pester"
    },
    {
      "front": "感銘",
      "back": "deep impression"
    },
    {
      "front": "俗語",
      "back": "slang"
    },
    {
      "front": "通俗的",
      "back": "common; popular"
    },
    {
      "front": "日光浴",
      "back": "sunbathe"
    },
    {
      "front": "浴衣",
      "back": "informal summer kimono; yukata"
    },
    {
      "front": "浴びせる",
      "back": "pour on"
    },
    {
      "front": "浴槽",
      "back": "bathtub"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぞろぞろ",
      "back": "in succession"
    },
    {
      "front": "滝",
      "back": "falls; waterfall"
    },
    {
      "front": "潜在",
      "back": "dormant; latent"
    },
    {
      "front": "潜む",
      "back": "be latent; lurk in"
    },
    {
      "front": "濁す",
      "back": "make cloudy; make turbid"
    },
    {
      "front": "浸る",
      "back": "be addicted to; be soaked in"
    },
    {
      "front": "びしょ濡れ",
      "back": "be soaked"
    },
    {
      "front": "潮",
      "back": "current; tide"
    },
    {
      "front": "汁",
      "back": "juice; soup"
    },
    {
      "front": "うやむや",
      "back": "ambiguous; vague"
    },
    {
      "front": "水滴",
      "back": "water drop"
    },
    {
      "front": "滴",
      "back": "drop"
    },
    {
      "front": "潤い",
      "back": "moisture; profit"
    },
    {
      "front": "浪人",
      "back": "lordless samurai; unsuccessful examinee"
    },
    {
      "front": "浮浪者",
      "back": "loafer; vagabond"
    },
    {
      "front": "感嘆",
      "back": "admiration"
    },
    {
      "front": "嘆き",
      "back": "grief; lamentation"
    },
    {
      "front": "弱虫",
      "back": "weakling"
    },
    {
      "front": "害虫",
      "back": "harmful insect"
    },
    {
      "front": "はらはら",
      "back": "suspensefully"
    },
    {
      "front": "怠る",
      "back": "be remiss; neglect"
    },
    {
      "front": "怠惰",
      "back": "idleness; laziness"
    },
    {
      "front": "懸念",
      "back": "anxiety; concern"
    },
    {
      "front": "懸かる",
      "back": "be suspended; have a prize on"
    },
    {
      "front": "憩い",
      "back": "relaxation; rest"
    },
    {
      "front": "恩人",
      "back": "benefactor; patron"
    },
    {
      "front": "恩知らず",
      "back": "ingrate; ingratitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "恩返し",
      "back": "repayment of kindness"
    },
    {
      "front": "うとうと",
      "back": "doze"
    },
    {
      "front": "知恵",
      "back": "intelligence; wisdom"
    },
    {
      "front": "恩恵",
      "back": "benefit; blessing"
    },
    {
      "front": "歪む",
      "back": "be crooked"
    },
    {
      "front": "耕す",
      "back": "plow; till"
    },
    {
      "front": "大豆",
      "back": "soybean"
    },
    {
      "front": "小豆",
      "back": "adzuki bean"
    },
    {
      "front": "白粉",
      "back": "powder"
    },
    {
      "front": "たらたら",
      "back": "dribbling; dripping"
    },
    {
      "front": "粘土",
      "back": "clay; modeling clay"
    },
    {
      "front": "粘着",
      "back": "affixing"
    },
    {
      "front": "消灯",
      "back": "lights out"
    },
    {
      "front": "灯台",
      "back": "lighthouse"
    },
    {
      "front": "灯",
      "back": "lantern; light"
    },
    {
      "front": "灯す",
      "back": "burn; light"
    },
    {
      "front": "肺炎",
      "back": "pneumonia"
    },
    {
      "front": "間一髪",
      "back": "by a hair's breadth"
    },
    {
      "front": "散髪",
      "back": "haircut"
    },
    {
      "front": "しくしく",
      "back": "sobbing"
    },
    {
      "front": "盲腸",
      "back": "appendix; cecum"
    },
    {
      "front": "尻",
      "back": "bottom; buttocks"
    },
    {
      "front": "会釈",
      "back": "slight bow"
    },
    {
      "front": "釈放",
      "back": "liberation; release"
    },
    {
      "front": "釈迦",
      "back": "Lord Buddha; Sakyamuni"
    },
    {
      "front": "白鳥",
      "back": "swan"
    },
    {
      "front": "居酒屋",
      "back": "bar; pub"
    },
    {
      "front": "住居",
      "back": "dwelling; house"
    },
    {
      "front": "別居",
      "back": "separation"
    },
    {
      "front": "芝居",
      "back": "drama; play"
    },
    {
      "front": "うねる",
      "back": "surge; undulate"
    },
    {
      "front": "据え置き",
      "back": "deferment; leaving as it stands"
    },
    {
      "front": "根掘り葉掘り",
      "back": "in great detail"
    },
    {
      "front": "堀",
      "back": "ditch; moat"
    },
    {
      "front": "アベック",
      "back": "couple"
    },
    {
      "front": "転覆",
      "back": "overturning"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨戸",
      "back": "shutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "瀬戸物",
      "back": "ceramics; china; porcelain"
    },
    {
      "front": "戸締まり",
      "back": "closing of the doors"
    },
    {
      "front": "戸惑う",
      "back": "be puzzled"
    },
    {
      "front": "井戸",
      "back": "well"
    },
    {
      "front": "扇子",
      "back": "folding fan"
    },
    {
      "front": "換気扇",
      "back": "ventilation fan"
    },
    {
      "front": "扇ぐ",
      "back": "fan"
    },
    {
      "front": "うずうず",
      "back": "impatience"
    },
    {
      "front": "羽織",
      "back": "haori; Japanese half-length coat"
    },
    {
      "front": "羽撃く",
      "back": "flap the wings"
    },
    {
      "front": "右翼",
      "back": "right wing"
    },
    {
      "front": "左翼",
      "back": "left field; left wing"
    },
    {
      "front": "翼",
      "back": "wing"
    },
    {
      "front": "左遷",
      "back": "demotion; relegation"
    },
    {
      "front": "潜水艦",
      "back": "submarine"
    },
    {
      "front": "不毛",
      "back": "fruitless; infertile"
    },
    {
      "front": "羊毛",
      "back": "wool"
    },
    {
      "front": "羊",
      "back": "sheep"
    },
    {
      "front": "びくびく",
      "back": "scared"
    },
    {
      "front": "鯨",
      "back": "whale"
    },
    {
      "front": "抜群",
      "back": "outstanding"
    },
    {
      "front": "群れる",
      "back": "crowd together"
    },
    {
      "front": "吸い殻",
      "back": "cigarette butt"
    },
    {
      "front": "殻",
      "back": "husk; shell"
    },
    {
      "front": "肥満",
      "back": "obesity"
    },
    {
      "front": "肥える",
      "back": "fatten; grow fertile"
    },
    {
      "front": "よちよち",
      "back": "toddling"
    },
    {
      "front": "胴上げ",
      "back": "tossing in the air"
    },
    {
      "front": "胴体",
      "back": "body; torso"
    },
    {
      "front": "腕力",
      "back": "muscular strength"
    },
    {
      "front": "腕白",
      "back": "naughtiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "脇見",
      "back": "looking aside"
    },
    {
      "front": "脇役",
      "back": "supporting actor"
    },
    {
      "front": "脇",
      "back": "under arm"
    },
    {
      "front": "立脚",
      "back": "viewpoint"
    },
    {
      "front": "すれすれ",
      "back": "very close to"
    },
    {
      "front": "肝臓",
      "back": "liver"
    },
    {
      "front": "肝",
      "back": "courage; liver"
    },
    {
      "front": "文脈",
      "back": "context"
    },
    {
      "front": "動脈",
      "back": "artery"
    },
    {
      "front": "脈絡",
      "back": "logical connection"
    },
    {
      "front": "日暮れ",
      "back": "dusk; nightfall"
    },
    {
      "front": "野暮",
      "back": "rustic; unrefined"
    },
    {
      "front": "茂る",
      "back": "be luxuriant; grow thick"
    },
    {
      "front": "まごまご",
      "back": "awkwardly; confusedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "荒々しい",
      "back": "rough; wild"
    },
    {
      "front": "憎悪",
      "back": "abhorrence; hatred"
    },
    {
      "front": "大仏",
      "back": "great statue of Buddha"
    },
    {
      "front": "坊主",
      "back": "Buddhist priest; shaven head"
    },
    {
      "front": "旋律",
      "back": "melody"
    },
    {
      "front": "螺旋",
      "back": "screw; spiral"
    },
    {
      "front": "斡旋",
      "back": "mediation"
    },
    {
      "front": "てきぱき",
      "back": "briskly; promptly"
    },
    {
      "front": "達筆",
      "back": "good handwriting"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆記",
      "back": "note taking"
    },
    {
      "front": "筆順",
      "back": "stroke order"
    },
    {
      "front": "随筆",
      "back": "essay"
    },
    {
      "front": "水筒",
      "back": "canteen"
    },
    {
      "front": "お袋",
      "back": "one's mother"
    },
    {
      "front": "引き裂く",
      "back": "separate; tear off"
    },
    {
      "front": "裂く",
      "back": "split up; tear"
    },
    {
      "front": "分布",
      "back": "distribution"
    },
    {
      "front": "若布",
      "back": "seaweed; wakame"
    },
    {
      "front": "公布",
      "back": "promulgation"
    },
    {
      "front": "ふわりと",
      "back": "gently"
    },
    {
      "front": "包囲",
      "back": "encirclement; siege"
    },
    {
      "front": "包装",
      "back": "packing; wrapping"
    },
    {
      "front": "抱っこ",
      "back": "hug"
    },
    {
      "front": "泡",
      "back": "bubble; foam"
    },
    {
      "front": "句読点",
      "back": "punctuation marks"
    },
    {
      "front": "禁句",
      "back": "tabooed word"
    },
    {
      "front": "節句",
      "back": "seasonal festival"
    },
    {
      "front": "挙げ句",
      "back": "finally; in the end"
    },
    {
      "front": "くよくよ",
      "back": "fretting; worrying"
    },
    {
      "front": "養殖",
      "back": "cultivation; culture"
    },
    {
      "front": "飽き",
      "back": "weariness"
    },
    {
      "front": "服飾",
      "back": "dress and its ornaments"
    },
    {
      "front": "飢える",
      "back": "starve"
    },
    {
      "front": "飢餓",
      "back": "hunger; starvation"
    },
    {
      "front": "飢饉",
      "back": "famine"
    },
    {
      "front": "凡人",
      "back": "ordinary person"
    },
    {
      "front": "克明",
      "back": "precise; scrupulous"
    },
    {
      "front": "克服",
      "back": "conquest; subjugation"
    },
    {
      "front": "百姓",
      "back": "farmer; peasant"
    },
    {
      "front": "転嫁",
      "back": "blame; imputation"
    },
    {
      "front": "嫁ぐ",
      "back": "wed"
    },
    {
      "front": "乳児",
      "back": "baby; infant"
    },
    {
      "front": "へとへと",
      "back": "exhausted; tired"
    },
    {
      "front": "幼なじみ",
      "back": "childhood friend"
    },
    {
      "front": "幻覚",
      "back": "hallucination"
    },
    {
      "front": "幻想",
      "back": "fantasy; illusion"
    },
    {
      "front": "幻",
      "back": "illusion; phantom"
    },
    {
      "front": "牧畜",
      "back": "livestock farming"
    },
    {
      "front": "蓄える",
      "back": "save; store up"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちぐはぐ",
      "back": "mismatch"
    },
    {
      "front": "肉眼",
      "back": "naked eye"
    },
    {
      "front": "眼差し",
      "back": "expression; look"
    },
    {
      "front": "眠気",
      "back": "sleepiness"
    },
    {
      "front": "不眠",
      "back": "sleeplessness"
    },
    {
      "front": "瞬く",
      "back": "twinkle; wink"
    },
    {
      "front": "瞳",
      "back": "one's eyes; pupil"
    },
    {
      "front": "雨垂れ",
      "back": "raindrops"
    },
    {
      "front": "垂らす",
      "back": "hang down; suspend"
    },
    {
      "front": "封建主義",
      "back": "feudalism"
    },
    {
      "front": "封建的",
      "back": "feudal; old-fashioned"
    },
    {
      "front": "がらりと",
      "back": "suddenly"
    },
    {
      "front": "気掛かり",
      "back": "anxiety; concern"
    },
    {
      "front": "見せ掛け",
      "back": "outward appearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "言い掛かり",
      "back": "false accusation"
    },
    {
      "front": "取り掛かる",
      "back": "commence; undertake"
    },
    {
      "front": "突っ掛ける",
      "back": "to slip on, slip into"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぶっきらぼう",
      "back": "brusque; curt"
    },
    {
      "front": "拍子",
      "back": "beat; the moment"
    },
    {
      "front": "脈拍",
      "back": "pulsation; pulse"
    },
    {
      "front": "一握り",
      "back": "a handful"
    },
    {
      "front": "握力",
      "back": "grasping power"
    },
    {
      "front": "握り寿司",
      "back": "nigirizushi; sushi"
    },
    {
      "front": "ざわざわ",
      "back": "murmuring; noisy"
    },
    {
      "front": "括る",
      "back": "bind; fasten; tie up"
    },
    {
      "front": "輝かしい",
      "back": "bright; brilliant"
    },
    {
      "front": "艶",
      "back": "charm; gloss"
    },
    {
      "front": "模擬試験",
      "back": "mock examination"
    },
    {
      "front": "擬装",
      "back": "camouflage; disguise"
    },
    {
      "front": "凝る",
      "back": "become stiff"
    },
    {
      "front": "抑止",
      "back": "deterrent"
    },
    {
      "front": "抑揚",
      "back": "intonation"
    },
    {
      "front": "仰向け",
      "back": "facing upward"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぱちぱち",
      "back": "crackle"
    },
    {
      "front": "遂行",
      "back": "execution"
    },
    {
      "front": "未遂",
      "back": "attempted"
    },
    {
      "front": "成し遂げる",
      "back": "carry out; complete"
    },
    {
      "front": "巡り会う",
      "back": "come across; meet by chance"
    },
    {
      "front": "巡回",
      "back": "patrol; round"
    },
    {
      "front": "巡査",
      "back": "patrolman; police"
    },
    {
      "front": "しゃっくり",
      "back": "hiccough; hiccup"
    },
    {
      "front": "逸れる",
      "back": "go astray"
    },
    {
      "front": "偶像",
      "back": "idol; image"
    },
    {
      "front": "恒久",
      "back": "permanency; perpetuity"
    },
    {
      "front": "恒例",
      "back": "established custom"
    },
    {
      "front": "戒め",
      "back": "caution; commandment"
    },
    {
      "front": "戒める",
      "back": "caution against"
    },
    {
      "front": "幾日",
      "back": "many days"
    },
    {
      "front": "幾分",
      "back": "partially; somewhat"
    },
    {
      "front": "幾何",
      "back": "geometry"
    },
    {
      "front": "幾度",
      "back": "many times"
    },
    {
      "front": "アンダーライン",
      "back": "underline"
    },
    {
      "front": "悔い",
      "back": "regret; repentance"
    },
    {
      "front": "侮る",
      "back": "despise; make light of"
    },
    {
      "front": "傍観",
      "back": "observer; spectator"
    },
    {
      "front": "傍聴",
      "back": "attendance; hearing"
    },
    {
      "front": "打撲",
      "back": "blow; stroke"
    },
    {
      "front": "撲滅",
      "back": "eradication"
    },
    {
      "front": "いんちき",
      "back": "cheating; dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "front": "普段着",
      "back": "everyday wear"
    },
    {
      "front": "宮",
      "back": "Imperial Court; shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "front": "宣告",
      "back": "sentence; verdict"
    },
    {
      "front": "審判",
      "back": "referee; umpire"
    },
    {
      "front": "えくぼ",
      "back": "dimple"
    },
    {
      "front": "寛大",
      "back": "generous; magnanimous"
    },
    {
      "front": "寛ぐ",
      "back": "make oneself at home; relax"
    },
    {
      "front": "乗組員",
      "back": "crew"
    },
    {
      "front": "組閣",
      "back": "cabinet; ministry"
    },
    {
      "front": "閣僚",
      "back": "cabinet members"
    },
    {
      "front": "博覧会",
      "back": "exhibition; fair"
    },
    {
      "front": "検閲",
      "back": "censorship; inspection"
    },
    {
      "front": "等閑",
      "back": "neglect"
    },
    {
      "front": "しとしと",
      "back": "falling gently"
    },
    {
      "front": "格闘",
      "back": "fight; tussle"
    },
    {
      "front": "闘争",
      "back": "conflict; fight"
    },
    {
      "front": "暗闇",
      "back": "in darkness"
    },
    {
      "front": "哀れ",
      "back": "pathos; pity"
    },
    {
      "front": "哀れむ",
      "back": "pity; sympathize"
    },
    {
      "front": "懐疑",
      "back": "doubt; skepticism"
    },
    {
      "front": "懐",
      "back": "bosom; mind"
    },
    {
      "front": "ねばねば",
      "back": "sliminess"
    },
    {
      "front": "追悼",
      "back": "mourning"
    },
    {
      "front": "悼む",
      "back": "grieve over; mourn"
    },
    {
      "front": "唯一",
      "back": "the only; unique"
    },
    {
      "front": "唯",
      "back": "merely; simply"
    },
    {
      "front": "対称",
      "back": "symmetry"
    },
    {
      "front": "平穏",
      "back": "calmness; quiet"
    },
    {
      "front": "穏健",
      "back": "moderate; temperate"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠陥",
      "back": "defect; fault"
    },
    {
      "front": "陥る",
      "back": "fall in; fall into"
    },
    {
      "front": "鬼",
      "back": "devil; fiend; ogre"
    },
    {
      "front": "術語",
      "back": "technical term; terminology"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪魔",
      "back": "demon; devil"
    },
    {
      "front": "魔法",
      "back": "magic; sorcery"
    },
    {
      "front": "魔術",
      "back": "magic; sorcery"
    },
    {
      "front": "もがく",
      "back": "struggle"
    },
    {
      "front": "魂",
      "back": "soul; spirit"
    },
    {
      "front": "碑",
      "back": "monument"
    },
    {
      "front": "大砲",
      "back": "cannon; gun"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄砲",
      "back": "firearm; gun"
    },
    {
      "front": "賄賂",
      "back": "bribe; payoff"
    },
    {
      "front": "頻発",
      "back": "frequent occurrence"
    },
    {
      "front": "回顧",
      "back": "reminiscence"
    },
    {
      "front": "煩う",
      "back": "worry about"
    },
    {
      "front": "びりびり",
      "back": "in pieces; in shreds"
    },
    {
      "front": "有頂天",
      "back": "ecstasy; exaltation"
    },
    {
      "front": "頂点",
      "back": "apex; peak"
    },
    {
      "front": "頂き",
      "back": "unexpected gain"
    },
    {
      "front": "先頃",
      "back": "the other day"
    },
    {
      "front": "悪循環",
      "back": "vicious circle"
    },
    {
      "front": "循環",
      "back": "circulation; cycle"
    },
    {
      "front": "創作",
      "back": "creation; fiction writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "ありありと",
      "back": "clearly"
    },
    {
      "front": "刈る",
      "back": "clip; reap"
    },
    {
      "front": "処刑",
      "back": "execution; punishment"
    },
    {
      "front": "罰点",
      "back": "black mark; X mark"
    },
    {
      "front": "罰則",
      "back": "penal regulations"
    },
    {
      "front": "賞罰",
      "back": "reward and punishment"
    },
    {
      "front": "署名",
      "back": "autograph; signature"
    },
    {
      "front": "おろおろ",
      "back": "bewildered; tearful"
    },
    {
      "front": "孝行",
      "back": "family duty"
    },
    {
      "front": "親孝行",
      "back": "filial piety"
    },
    {
      "front": "不孝",
      "back": "undutifulness"
    },
    {
      "front": "親不孝",
      "back": "lack of filial piety"
    },
    {
      "front": "老後",
      "back": "one's old age"
    },
    {
      "front": "老化",
      "back": "aging"
    },
    {
      "front": "老眼",
      "back": "farsightedness; presbyopia"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑煮",
      "back": "rice cakes boiled with vegetables"
    },
    {
      "front": "煮込む",
      "back": "boil well; stew"
    },
    {
      "front": "煮詰める",
      "back": "boil down"
    },
    {
      "front": "うろつく",
      "back": "hang around; loiter"
    },
    {
      "front": "水蒸気",
      "back": "steam; water vapor"
    },
    {
      "front": "蒸発",
      "back": "evaporation; mysterious disappearance"
    },
    {
      "front": "蒸す",
      "back": "be stuffy; steam"
    },
    {
      "front": "蒸かす",
      "back": "steam"
    },
    {
      "front": "痛ましい",
      "back": "heartbreaking; piteous"
    },
    {
      "front": "熱烈",
      "back": "ardent; fervent"
    },
    {
      "front": "痛烈",
      "back": "scathing; sharp"
    },
    {
      "front": "熟語",
      "back": "compound word; idiom"
    },
    {
      "front": "早熟",
      "back": "forward; precocious"
    },
    {
      "front": "いざこざ",
      "back": "quarrel"
    },
    {
      "front": "暗黙",
      "back": "tacit"
    },
    {
      "front": "待ち伏せ",
      "back": "ambush"
    },
    {
      "front": "伏せる",
      "back": "keep secret; turn downward"
    },
    {
      "front": "文献",
      "back": "literature"
    },
    {
      "front": "献立",
      "back": "menu"
    },
    {
      "front": "献血",
      "back": "blood donation"
    },
    {
      "front": "騰貴",
      "back": "rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "暴騰",
      "back": "sudden rise"
    },
    {
      "front": "ごしごし",
      "back": "scrub hard"
    },
    {
      "front": "卸売り",
      "back": "wholesale"
    },
    {
      "front": "卸す",
      "back": "sell wholesale"
    },
    {
      "front": "忘却",
      "back": "forgetfulness"
    },
    {
      "front": "棄却",
      "back": "rejection"
    },
    {
      "front": "麻薬",
      "back": "drug; narcotic"
    },
    {
      "front": "敗北",
      "back": "defeat; setback"
    },
    {
      "front": "床の間",
      "back": "alcove"
    },
    {
      "front": "起床",
      "back": "arising; getting up"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝床",
      "back": "bed"
    },
    {
      "front": "ちらつく",
      "back": "flicker"
    },
    {
      "front": "擦る",
      "back": "crush; rub"
    },
    {
      "front": "物干し",
      "back": "clotheshorse"
    },
    {
      "front": "軒",
      "back": "row"
    },
    {
      "front": "香ばしい",
      "back": "nice-smelling"
    },
    {
      "front": "冒す",
      "back": "inflict; risk"
    },
    {
      "front": "よろよろ",
      "back": "staggering"
    },
    {
      "front": "尊重",
      "back": "esteem; respect"
    },
    {
      "front": "尊ぶ",
      "back": "honor; respect"
    },
    {
      "front": "敬遠",
      "back": "keeping at a distance"
    },
    {
      "front": "敬意",
      "back": "regard; respect"
    },
    {
      "front": "失敬",
      "back": "rudeness"
    },
    {
      "front": "敬老",
      "back": "respect for the aged"
    },
    {
      "front": "下敷き",
      "back": "being buried; pencil board"
    },
    {
      "front": "敷地",
      "back": "ground; site"
    },
    {
      "front": "敷布団",
      "back": "mattress"
    },
    {
      "front": "敷居",
      "back": "threshold; windowsill"
    },
    {
      "front": "風呂敷",
      "back": "wrapping cloth"
    },
    {
      "front": "勇ましい",
      "back": "bold; brave"
    },
    {
      "front": "劣等感",
      "back": "inferiority complex"
    },
    {
      "front": "卑劣",
      "back": "base; mean"
    },
    {
      "front": "激動",
      "back": "turmoil; violent shaking"
    },
    {
      "front": "かさかさ",
      "back": "dried out; dried up"
    },
    {
      "front": "持ち堪える",
      "back": "hold out; survive"
    },
    {
      "front": "甚だしい",
      "back": "excessive; tremendous"
    },
    {
      "front": "宴会",
      "back": "dinner party; reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "披露宴",
      "back": "wedding reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎょっと",
      "back": "shock"
    },
    {
      "front": "円盤",
      "back": "disk; flying saucer"
    },
    {
      "front": "算盤",
      "back": "Japanese abacus; soroban"
    },
    {
      "front": "基盤",
      "back": "base; bedrock"
    },
    {
      "front": "民衆",
      "back": "populace; the people"
    },
    {
      "front": "聴衆",
      "back": "audience"
    },
    {
      "front": "振る舞う",
      "back": "behave oneself; entertain"
    },
    {
      "front": "足踏み",
      "back": "step; stepping"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑踏",
      "back": "hustle and bustle"
    },
    {
      "front": "踏み切る",
      "back": "launch out; take off"
    },
    {
      "front": "踏ん張る",
      "back": "hold out; keep one's footing"
    },
    {
      "front": "舞踏",
      "back": "dancing"
    },
    {
      "front": "埋め立て",
      "back": "reclamation"
    },
    {
      "front": "埋まる",
      "back": "be buried under; be filled up"
    },
    {
      "front": "堂々と",
      "back": "grandly; magnificent"
    },
    {
      "front": "中堅",
      "back": "nucleus; the mainstay"
    },
    {
      "front": "堅実",
      "back": "sound; steady"
    },
    {
      "front": "狂わす",
      "back": "drive crazy"
    },
    {
      "front": "猫背",
      "back": "bent back; stoop"
    },
    {
      "front": "猫舌",
      "back": "sensitive to hot food"
    },
    {
      "front": "せがむ",
      "back": "pester"
    },
    {
      "front": "猟",
      "back": "game; hunting"
    },
    {
      "front": "狙い",
      "back": "aim; target"
    },
    {
      "front": "表彰",
      "back": "award; commendation"
    },
    {
      "front": "表彰状",
      "back": "certificate of commendation"
    },
    {
      "front": "淑やか",
      "back": "graceful; ladylike"
    },
    {
      "front": "座禅",
      "back": "Zen meditation"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉄筋",
      "back": "reinforced with iron"
    },
    {
      "front": "粗大",
      "back": "coarse; rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "粗末",
      "back": "coarse; inferior"
    },
    {
      "front": "粗い",
      "back": "coarse; rough"
    },
    {
      "front": "でかでかと",
      "back": "in a big way"
    },
    {
      "front": "宅地",
      "back": "residential land"
    },
    {
      "front": "官邸",
      "back": "official residence"
    },
    {
      "front": "邦人",
      "back": "fellow countryman; Japanese"
    },
    {
      "front": "むっつり",
      "back": "moodily; sulkily"
    },
    {
      "front": "善悪",
      "back": "good and evil"
    },
    {
      "front": "善意",
      "back": "favorable sense; good intention"
    },
    {
      "front": "善",
      "back": "good; goodness"
    },
    {
      "front": "善く善く",
      "back": "very carefully"
    },
    {
      "front": "善くも",
      "back": "how dare"
    },
    {
      "front": "修繕",
      "back": "repair"
    },
    {
      "front": "綱渡り",
      "back": "tightrope walking"
    },
    {
      "front": "にやりと",
      "back": "quick grin"
    },
    {
      "front": "網羅する",
      "back": "comprehend; encompass"
    },
    {
      "front": "お絞り",
      "back": "steamed towel; wet towel"
    },
    {
      "front": "紅白",
      "back": "red and white"
    },
    {
      "front": "紅葉",
      "back": "Japanese maple; red leaves"
    },
    {
      "front": "松",
      "back": "pine"
    },
    {
      "front": "杉",
      "back": "cryptomeria; Japanese cedar"
    },
    {
      "front": "塩分",
      "back": "salinity"
    },
    {
      "front": "入梅",
      "back": "beginning of the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "梅雨",
      "back": "rainy season"
    },
    {
      "front": "塩梅",
      "back": "condition; seasoning"
    },
    {
      "front": "むっと",
      "back": "be annoyed"
    },
    {
      "front": "栓",
      "back": "plug; stopper"
    },
    {
      "front": "十字架",
      "back": "cross; crucifix"
    },
    {
      "front": "架空",
      "back": "fictitious; overhead"
    },
    {
      "front": "呆気",
      "back": "amazement"
    },
    {
      "front": "呆然と",
      "back": "blankly; dazedly"
    },
    {
      "front": "阿呆",
      "back": "fool; idiot"
    },
    {
      "front": "碁",
      "back": "go"
    },
    {
      "front": "空虚",
      "back": "emptiness; inanity"
    },
    {
      "front": "虚無",
      "back": "nihility; nothingness"
    },
    {
      "front": "虚栄心",
      "back": "vanity"
    },
    {
      "front": "虚構",
      "back": "fabrication; fiction"
    },
    {
      "front": "謙虚",
      "back": "humble; modest"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴりぴり",
      "back": "on edge; smarting"
    },
    {
      "front": "戯れ",
      "back": "joke"
    },
    {
      "front": "戯れる",
      "back": "joke; sport"
    },
    {
      "front": "不慮",
      "back": "accidental; unexpected"
    },
    {
      "front": "白痴",
      "back": "idiocy; idiot"
    },
    {
      "front": "くどくど",
      "back": "repetitively"
    },
    {
      "front": "岬",
      "back": "cape; headland"
    },
    {
      "front": "太鼓",
      "back": "drum; professional jester"
    },
    {
      "front": "喚く",
      "back": "cry out; shout; yell"
    },
    {
      "front": "示唆",
      "back": "hint; suggestion"
    },
    {
      "front": "唆す",
      "back": "incite; instigate"
    },
    {
      "front": "欠如",
      "back": "lack; shortage"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぽたぽた",
      "back": "drop by drop"
    },
    {
      "front": "奴",
      "back": "chap; guy; thing"
    },
    {
      "front": "漬かる",
      "back": "be immersed"
    },
    {
      "front": "口笛",
      "back": "whistle"
    },
    {
      "front": "汽笛",
      "back": "steam whistle"
    },
    {
      "front": "店舗",
      "back": "shop; store"
    },
    {
      "front": "蛍",
      "back": "firefly; glowfly"
    },
    {
      "front": "ひそひそ",
      "back": "whispered conversation"
    },
    {
      "front": "摩る",
      "back": "rub"
    },
    {
      "front": "焼き芋",
      "back": "baked sweet potato"
    },
    {
      "front": "薩摩芋",
      "back": "sweet potato"
    },
    {
      "front": "豪華",
      "back": "gorgeous; splendid"
    },
    {
      "front": "侮蔑",
      "back": "contempt; scorn"
    },
    {
      "front": "蔑む",
      "back": "despise"
    },
    {
      "front": "手拭い",
      "back": "facecloth; towel"
    },
    {
      "front": "拭う",
      "back": "mop; wipe"
    },
    {
      "front": "扶助",
      "back": "support; sustenance"
    },
    {
      "front": "摂氏",
      "back": "centigrade"
    },
    {
      "front": "詠む",
      "back": "compose"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉢",
      "back": "basin; flowerpot"
    },
    {
      "front": "巻き込む",
      "back": "involve; roll"
    },
    {
      "front": "寝巻き",
      "back": "pajamas"
    },
    {
      "front": "巻き添え",
      "back": "involvement"
    },
    {
      "front": "鉢巻",
      "back": "headband"
    },
    {
      "front": "渦巻き",
      "back": "coil; whirlpool"
    },
    {
      "front": "襟巻き",
      "back": "muffler; scarf"
    },
    {
      "front": "めきめき",
      "back": "rapidly; remarkably"
    },
    {
      "front": "陶酔",
      "back": "fascination; intoxication"
    },
    {
      "front": "陳腐",
      "back": "old-fashioned; trite"
    },
    {
      "front": "祭る",
      "back": "worship as god"
    },
    {
      "front": "冠婚葬祭",
      "back": "ceremonial occasions"
    },
    {
      "front": "冠",
      "back": "coronet; crown"
    },
    {
      "front": "執行",
      "back": "execution; performance"
    },
    {
      "front": "執着",
      "back": "attachment; tenacity"
    },
    {
      "front": "執念",
      "back": "tenacity of purpose; vindictiveness"
    },
    {
      "front": "固執",
      "back": "adherence; persistence"
    },
    {
      "front": "執筆",
      "back": "writing"
    },
    {
      "front": "執る",
      "back": "conduct; transact"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぐっしょり",
      "back": "soaked"
    },
    {
      "front": "疎外",
      "back": "alienation; estrangement"
    },
    {
      "front": "疎遠",
      "back": "alienation; estrangement"
    },
    {
      "front": "疎ら",
      "back": "sparse; sparsely"
    },
    {
      "front": "皇后",
      "back": "empress; queen"
    },
    {
      "front": "琴",
      "back": "harp; koto"
    },
    {
      "front": "慈悲",
      "back": "compassion; mercy"
    },
    {
      "front": "慈善",
      "back": "charity"
    },
    {
      "front": "悠々",
      "back": "comfort; leisure"
    },
    {
      "front": "懲役",
      "back": "imprisonment; penal servitude"
    },
    {
      "front": "凹む",
      "back": "become hollow; get dented; sink"
    },
    {
      "front": "せかせか",
      "back": "fidgety; restless"
    },
    {
      "front": "華麗",
      "back": "magnificent"
    },
    {
      "front": "鯉",
      "back": "carp"
    },
    {
      "front": "瓦",
      "back": "tile-roofing"
    },
    {
      "front": "煉瓦",
      "back": "brick"
    },
    {
      "front": "渚",
      "back": "beach; waterside"
    },
    {
      "front": "窪み",
      "back": "cavity; hollow; pit"
    },
    {
      "front": "鎌",
      "back": "sickle"
    },
    {
      "front": "栗",
      "back": "chestnut"
    },
    {
      "front": "虎",
      "back": "drunkard; tiger"
    },
    {
      "front": "熊",
      "back": "bear"
    },
    {
      "front": "舅",
      "back": "one's father-in-law"
    },
    {
      "front": "綴り",
      "back": "spelling"
    },
    {
      "front": "籤",
      "back": "lottery; raffle"
    },
    {
      "front": "おみ籤",
      "back": "written fortune"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぽかんと",
      "back": "agape; blankly"
    },
    {
      "front": "雛",
      "back": "chick; fledgling"
    },
    {
      "front": "尤もらしい",
      "back": "plausible"
    },
    {
      "front": "雑巾",
      "back": "cleaning cloth; rag"
    },
    {
      "front": "俄雨",
      "back": "shower"
    },
    {
      "front": "俄",
      "back": "improvised; suddenly; temporary"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぽつりぽつり",
      "back": "drop by drop"
    },
    {
      "front": "僻み",
      "back": "bias; warped view"
    },
    {
      "front": "僻む",
      "back": "be jaundiced"
    },
    {
      "front": "僧侶",
      "back": "bonze; Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "front": "凄まじい",
      "back": "terrible"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぴんぴん",
      "back": "full of beans; lively"
    },
    {
      "front": "凧",
      "back": "kite"
    },
    {
      "front": "仄か",
      "back": "faint; subtle"
    },
    {
      "front": "仄めかす",
      "back": "hint"
    },
    {
      "front": "嘲る",
      "back": "scorn; sneer"
    },
    {
      "front": "むかむか",
      "back": "feel disgusted"
    },
    {
      "front": "叩き",
      "back": "feather duster"
    },
    {
      "front": "呪い",
      "back": "curse; spell"
    },
    {
      "front": "呪う",
      "back": "curse; use a charm"
    },
    {
      "front": "吊る",
      "back": "hang; suspend"
    },
    {
      "front": "そそっかしい",
      "back": "careless"
    },
    {
      "front": "吃る",
      "back": "stutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "姑",
      "back": "one's mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "front": "孕む",
      "back": "conceive; get pregnant"
    },
    {
      "front": "宥める",
      "back": "calm down; soothe"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぎざぎざ",
      "back": "jagged; notches"
    },
    {
      "front": "嵌まる",
      "back": "fit; put in"
    },
    {
      "front": "庇う",
      "back": "protect; stick up for"
    },
    {
      "front": "捻挫",
      "back": "sprain"
    },
    {
      "front": "捻じる",
      "back": "be twisted; twist"
    },
    {
      "front": "手摺り",
      "back": "handrail; railing"
    },
    {
      "front": "手古摺る",
      "back": "not know what to do with"
    },
    {
      "front": "ウィークデー",
      "back": "weekday"
    },
    {
      "front": "見惚れる",
      "back": "be fascinated by; look admiringly at"
    },
    {
      "front": "自惚れる",
      "back": "be conceited; be vain"
    },
    {
      "front": "惚け",
      "back": "idiot; jet lag"
    },
    {
      "front": "惚れる",
      "back": "admire; be charmed by"
    },
    {
      "front": "惚ける",
      "back": "pretend ignorance"
    },
    {
      "front": "惚ける",
      "back": "grow senile"
    },
    {
      "front": "がらんと",
      "back": "deserted"
    },
    {
      "front": "洒落",
      "back": "pun; witticism"
    },
    {
      "front": "澱む",
      "back": "stagnate"
    },
    {
      "front": "汲み取る",
      "back": "drain; take into consideration"
    },
    {
      "front": "吹き溜まり",
      "back": "drift"
    },
    {
      "front": "爺さん",
      "back": "gramps; grandpa"
    },
    {
      "front": "くたばる",
      "back": "drop dead"
    },
    {
      "front": "狐",
      "back": "fox; vixen"
    },
    {
      "front": "萎れる",
      "back": "wilt; wither"
    },
    {
      "front": "芯",
      "back": "centre; core; lead"
    },
    {
      "front": "啓蒙",
      "back": "enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "front": "ぼやぼや",
      "back": "absent-minded"
    },
    {
      "front": "茸",
      "back": "mushroom"
    },
    {
      "front": "這う",
      "back": "crawl; creep"
    },
    {
      "front": "隙間",
      "back": "crack; gap"
    },
    {
      "front": "隙",
      "back": "gap; space"
    },
    {
      "front": "隈なく",
      "back": "every nook and cranny"
    },
    {
      "front": "ずきずき",
      "back": "throbbing pain"
    },
    {
      "front": "暈す",
      "back": "make out of focus"
    },
    {
      "front": "暈ける",
      "back": "be out of focus"
    },
    {
      "front": "晒す",
      "back": "rinse; wash"
    },
    {
      "front": "股",
      "back": "peach; the thigh"
    },
    {
      "front": "からりと",
      "back": "suddenly changed"
    },
    {
      "front": "椀",
      "back": "bowl"
    },
    {
      "front": "椀ぐ",
      "back": "pick; pluck"
    },
    {
      "front": "お椀",
      "back": "bowl"
    },
    {
      "front": "杜撰",
      "back": "careless; slipshod"
    },
    {
      "front": "樽",
      "back": "barrel; cask; keg"
    },
    {
      "front": "桶",
      "back": "bucket; pail"
    },
    {
      "front": "煽る",
      "back": "fan; flap; stir up"
    },
    {
      "front": "こしらえる",
      "back": "make; manufacture"
    },
    {
      "front": "瑞々しい",
      "back": "fresh-looking; young and fresh"
    },
    {
      "front": "禿",
      "back": "bald; treeless"
    },
    {
      "front": "禿げる",
      "back": "grow bald; lose hair"
    },
    {
      "front": "袴",
      "back": "hakama"
    },
    {
      "front": "暖簾",
      "back": "credit; shop curtain"
    },
    {
      "front": "縞",
      "back": "stripes"
    },
    {
      "front": "どよめく",
      "back": "resound"
    },
    {
      "front": "舵",
      "back": "helm; manage; rudder"
    },
    {
      "front": "耽る",
      "back": "indulge; wallow in"
    },
    {
      "front": "蟹",
      "back": "crab"
    },
    {
      "front": "蝉",
      "back": "cicada"
    },
    {
      "front": "ハイウエー",
      "back": "highway"
    },
    {
      "front": "跪く",
      "back": "kneel down"
    },
    {
      "front": "錨",
      "back": "anchor; cable"
    },
    {
      "front": "錆",
      "back": "patina; rust"
    },
    {
      "front": "しーんと",
      "back": "deadly quiet"
    },
    {
      "front": "閃く",
      "back": "flash"
    },
    {
      "front": "霞",
      "back": "dimness of sight; mist"
    },
    {
      "front": "蝕む",
      "back": "eat into; undermine"
    },
    {
      "front": "煎餅",
      "back": "biscuit; rice cracker"
    },
    {
      "front": "鯛",
      "back": "sea bream; tai"
    },
    {
      "front": "鰯",
      "back": "sardine"
    },
    {
      "front": "はぐれる",
      "back": "get lost; stray"
    },
    {
      "front": "鯵",
      "back": "mackerel"
    },
    {
      "front": "麒麟",
      "back": "Chinese unicorn; giraffe"
    },
    {
      "front": "遡る",
      "back": "go back over"
    },
    {
      "front": "颯爽と",
      "back": "dashing; smart"
    },
    {
      "front": "だらだらする",
      "back": "be inefficient; idle away"
    },
    {
      "front": "亡骸",
      "back": "corpse; remains"
    },
    {
      "front": "骸骨",
      "back": "skeleton"
    },
    {
      "front": "雲雀",
      "back": "skylark"
    },
    {
      "front": "麻雀",
      "back": "mahjong"
    },
    {
      "front": "流暢",
      "back": "flowing; fluent"
    },
    {
      "front": "匙",
      "back": "spoon"
    },
    {
      "front": "棘",
      "back": "thorn"
    },
    {
      "front": "甦る",
      "back": "come back to life again; revive"
    },
    {
      "front": "脛",
      "back": "shin"
    },
    {
      "front": "掟",
      "back": "regulations; rules"
    },
    {
      "front": "佇む",
      "back": "stand still"
    },
    {
      "front": "がぶりと",
      "back": "with relish"
    },
    {
      "front": "俯せ",
      "back": "face down"
    },
    {
      "front": "儚い",
      "back": "ephemeral; evanescent; fleeting"
    },
    {
      "front": "壺",
      "back": "pot"
    },
    {
      "front": "奢る",
      "back": "be extravagant; treat"
    },
    {
      "front": "彷徨う",
      "back": "roam; wander"
    },
    {
      "front": "こちこち",
      "back": "frightened"
    },
    {
      "front": "旁",
      "back": "construction; make up"
    },
    {
      "front": "浚う",
      "back": "dredge"
    },
    {
      "front": "涎",
      "back": "slaver; slobber"
    },
    {
      "front": "灌漑",
      "back": "irrigation"
    },
    {
      "front": "焜炉",
      "back": "portable cooking stove"
    },
    {
      "front": "痣",
      "back": "birthmark; bruise"
    },
    {
      "front": "がたんと",
      "back": "nosedive, with a crash"
    },
    {
      "front": "瘤",
      "back": "bump; lump"
    },
    {
      "front": "窶れる",
      "back": "be wasted; be worn out"
    },
    {
      "front": "籠",
      "back": "basket; cage; coop"
    },
    {
      "front": "籠もる",
      "back": "hide away"
    },
    {
      "front": "絨緞",
      "back": "carpet"
    },
    {
      "front": "じろり",
      "back": "glancing look"
    },
    {
      "front": "縋る",
      "back": "cling"
    },
    {
      "front": "縺れる",
      "back": "become tangled"
    },
    {
      "front": "罠",
      "back": "snare; trap"
    },
    {
      "front": "聊か",
      "back": "bit; somewhat"
    },
    {
      "front": "茣蓙",
      "back": "grass matting; mat"
    },
    {
      "front": "どたどた",
      "back": "clomping; tramping"
    },
    {
      "front": "蜘蛛",
      "back": "spider"
    },
    {
      "front": "蜻蛉",
      "back": "dragonfly"
    },
    {
      "front": "褪せる",
      "back": "fade; go off"
    },
    {
      "front": "訛り",
      "back": "accent"
    },
    {
      "front": "謳う",
      "back": "express; stipulate"
    },
    {
      "front": "貪欲",
      "back": "avarice; greed"
    },
    {
      "front": "貪る",
      "back": "be greedy; covet"
    },
    {
      "front": "贔屓",
      "back": "favoritism"
    },
    {
      "front": "なら",
      "back": "if; if so"
    },
    {
      "front": "蹌踉めく",
      "back": "stagger"
    },
    {
      "front": "蹲る",
      "back": "crouch; squat"
    },
    {
      "front": "躱わす",
      "back": "exchange"
    },
    {
      "front": "銜える",
      "back": "grasp in the mouth"
    },
    {
      "front": "餡こ",
      "back": "anko; red bean jam"
    },
    {
      "front": "鬘",
      "back": "toupee; wig"
    },
    {
      "front": "靡く",
      "back": "flutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "黴",
      "back": "mold; mould"
    }
  ]
}
